[Music]
[Música]
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
ST
ST
[Music]
[Música]
ah
ah
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
B
B
[Music]
[Música]
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
controversy with
polémica con
[Music]
[Música]
the must be is
el must be is
the you see it
the you see
all ok
all ok
[Music]
[Música]
ca
ca
elef the [Music] [
elef el
Applause]
[Aplausos]
okay let's go michar er let's go to the
vale vamos michar er vamos a pasar la
last question Okay then you call me
última pregunta Vale entonces tú me
pet please don't interrupt me you
mascota por favor no me interrumpas tú
call me pet Forgive me again I
me llamas mascota Perdóname otra vez te
'll
lo voy a
tell you and in
decir y en
ls you are you are
eles eres eres
[Music]
[Música]
you are you are
eres
F you are you are you are
eres eres F eres eres eres
please don't interrupt me you
eres por favor no me interum tú me
call me Forgive me again I'll tell you call
llamas Perdóname otra vez te lo voy a
again you
vez tú me
call me please you are you are you are you are you are you are you are
llamas por favor eres eres
well you are Fer d you are Fer d you are you are you are you are
pueses eres Fer d eres Fer d eres eres
you are Fer  d you are feri you are feri you are feri you are ferii you are Fer you are feri you are fi you are F you are F you are F you are you are fi you are F you are F you are F you are Fer you are Fer you are Fer you are Fer you are fuer you fueri you are fuer you are fueri you are fueri you are fuer you are ...
eres eres ereser d eres Fer d eres feri
[Music]
[Música]
Repin each
repin cadaa
Since if I argue it's to get to know you
des que si discuto es para conocerte
better there's no fog that can darken
más no hay nieblas que pueda oscurecer
this
este
[Music]
[Música]
love I know that
amor lo
we will walk through moments we never
sé que pasearemos por momentos que no
imagined that the pain will be so strong
imaginamos que el dolor será tan fuerte
we will think about
pensaremos en
leaving each other but this feeling of ours
dejarnos pero este sentimiento nuestro
will put in check the wounds that they
pondrá en jaque las heridas que le
cause to the soul breathe me
causem al alma respirame por
please because this path is
favor porque esta vía se nos
escaping us why do I want to see it
escapa para que quiero ver
shine why do I want to see the
brillar para que quiero ver brillar la
star shine in the sky If by my side I have
estrella en el cielo Si a mi lado tengo
the most beautiful in the firmament I do
la más bella del firmamento
n't know if you will understand me and what I'm
no sé si me entenderás y esto que te
telling you you have to feel the way your heart
cuento hay que sentir el corazón como
smiles
sonríe Por
Inside what I want I want to
dentro que quiero que quiero
see if by my side I have the
verar si a mi lado tengo del
firmament I don't know if you will understand me there's
firmamento no sé si me entenderás hay
done that and I'm telling you that I felt the way your
hecho que y ti te cuento que sentí
heart smiles
corazón como sonríe
contentedly
conento
[Music]
[Música]
Oh
Oh
eh [ __ ] It's that I wanted to upload some things
eh [__] Es que quería subir unas cosas
But anyway I'll do it later when I get out of
Pero bueno Luego lo hago cuando me vaya
bed how are you
la cama qué tal estáis
family not like the [ __ ] that datter
familia no como la [__] del datter que
usually puts Well This is Manuel Muñoz I
suele poner Bueno Este es Manuel Muñoz
recommend everything that I wouldn't put
os recomiendo todo que los yo no pondría
more than okay okay okay
más de
alanne you are the
alanne tú eres la
boss So  what you say so I have no choice
jefa Así que lo que tú digas así
but to obey you what
que no me queda otra que obedecer tú lo
the boss says what the internet says
que diga la jefa lo que diga la lne
well how are we let's square the
bueno Qué tal estamos vamos a cuadrar la
screen have you seen what happened with Katy Angel I
pantalla has visto lo de Katy Ángel
have
tengo
something to see I don't know where to
algo a ver es que no sé por dónde
start
empezar
wait for it damn great very
espérate
good very good what they
buenísima buenísimo buenísimo lo que me
're telling me I'm super good Well
están diciendo Yo estoy super bien Bueno
how have you been I haven't said anything What have I
cómo habéis estado no he dicho nada Qué
said well let's see I have a lot of
he dicho el bueno a ver Tengo muchas
things I have a
cosas
lot of things to comment on let's see it
tengo muchas cosas que comentar a ver
turns out there is some news it turns out there is
resulta que hay una noticia resulta que
some very strong news but very
hay una noticia muy fuerte pero muy
strong at a very serious level I mean there is some
fuerte a nivel muy grave o sea hay una
very strong very serious news okay very
noticia muy fuerte muy grave vale muy
strong and very serious that no one is
fuerte y muy grave que nadie está
commenting on and they sent it to me by
comentando y a mí me la han mandado por
email a couple of days ago Well I don't know if
email hace un par de días Bueno no sé si
a couple of days yes a couple of days or
un par de días sí hace un par de días o
three since they sent it to me What
tres ya que me la han mandado Lo que
happens I say Well yes yes I am able to
pasa que digo Bueno si si soy capaz de
find out the name then I will comment on it
averiguar el nombre pues ya la comentaré
but the thing is I haven't been able to
pero es que no he sido capaz de
find out the name nor can I say it if
averiguar el nombre ni lo puedo decir si
the media isn't saying it I wouldn't be able to
no lo están diciendo los medios no
say the name Because of course
podría yo decir el nombre Porque claro
we are obviously talking about something
evidentemente estamos hablando de algo
very serious okay we are talking about something
muy grave vale estamos hablando de algo
very serious and no  we could give it a name
muy grave y no podríamos ponerle nombre
if the press or the police don't do it
si la prensa o la policía no se lo pone
okay what I do have here translated the
vale lo que sí tengo aquí traducido el
article I'll
artículo
read it to you okay a tiktoker and a
os lo leo vale detenido un tiktoker y un
friend arrested for
amigo por una agresión
sexual assault the events happened on Saturday
sexual los hechos sucedieron el sábado
at a home okay so it turns out
en un domicilio vale o sea resulta ser
that in a house where there are tiktokers okay
que en una casa donde hay tiktokers vale
a tiktoker already resides in Andorra and
un tiktoker ya reside en andorra y por
apparently the other was like moving
lo visto el otro estaba como moviendo
the paperwork to be able to reside in
los papeles para para poder residir
Andorra okay the police arrested two
andorra vale polia arrestó ayer a dos
young men aged 24 and 27 yesterday as the perpetrators of
jóvenes de 24 y 27 años como autores de
a sexual assault that occurred in the
una agresión sexual que se produjo en la
early hours of Saturday according to reports this
madrugada del sábado según informa esta
afternoon one of those involved is a
tarde uno de los implicados es un
tiktoker who has been living in the country for
tiktoker residente en el país desde hace
a year so he's giving you a lot of pizzas
un año o sea te está dando muchas pizzas
I'm really screwed about tiktoker
Yo es que de tiktoker la verdad que voy
eh really screwed And I have no
jodid dissimo eh jodid simo Y no tengo
idea I mean I don't know if you're talking to me about a
ni idea O sea no conozco si me hablas de
youtuber surely if he tells me Well
youtuber seguramente si me dice Pues
look he's been in Andorra for three months I'll tell you
mira lleva tres meses en andorra te digo
this or that okay But this surely
este o aquel vale Pero esto seguramente
if you ask people who are more into the
si le preguntas a gente que lleve más el
tiktoker thing and also live in Andorra
tema titoker y además Viva en andorra
delox or Ricky Eddie or one of these
delox o Ricky Eddie o alguno de estos
surely reading this news knows
seguramente leyendo esta noticia saben
who they're talking about I just can't
de quién hablan Yo es que no puedo
Even if I suspected someone I wouldn't
Aunque sospechara de alguien no le
give him a name because it's not possible
pondría nombre porque es que no se puede
because if not everyone is putting it
porque es que si no todos están poniendo
here you can't put the name yourself
aquí no lo puedes poner tú el nombre
ok eh And the other is a friend of his who
vale eh Y el otro es un amigo suyo que
was processing the authorization to
estaba tramitando la autorización para
reside in the country Well it seems to me that they are
residir en el país Bueno pues me da que
not going to accept it anymore the events
ya no se la van a aceptar los hechos
would have occurred at a home it's that on
habrían ocurrido en un domicilio es que
top of that he even tells you the address I mean
encima te dice hasta la dirección o sea
those who are there this
es que los que están allí esto
surely tomorrow I will ask any
seguramente mañana pregunto a cualquiera
of those who live there in Andorra and they
de los que viven allí en andorra y lo
know it I mean they will surely have
saben o sea es que seguramente habrán
heard even the commotion there I mean
escuchado hasta el jaleo allí o sea
tomorrow I'm going to ask several
mañana se lo voy a preguntar a varios
youtubers and they are going to know it are going to know Yes
youtuber y van a saberlo van a saber Sí
the kid from there you know is he
el niño de allí sabes es que te está
telling you even where he lives look at an
diciendo hasta donde vive mira en un
address in the block where
domicilio de la mazana en el que se
a party was being organized well let's
estaba organizando una fiesta bueno a
see it wouldn't have to be it it couldn't it wouldn't have to
ver no tendría por qué ser no podría no
be where Viva El Chaval
tendría por qué ser donde Viva El chaval
Maybe it's a house where he goes to
A lo mejor es una casa a la que acude de
party but it's not
fiesta pero no es la
his when the two young people would have
suya cuando los dos jóvenes habrían
allegedly  sexually assaulted a
presuntamente agredido sexualmente a una
20 year old girl sources initially rule out
chica de 20 años las fuentes descartan
that the boys had
inicialmente que los chicos hubiesen
supplied drugs to the girl although they are
suministrado drogas a la chica Aunque
waiting for the result of TX
están a la espera del resultado de TX
guys this issue is serious eh I mean this
chicos este tema es serio eh o sea este
issue is very big
tema es muy gordo
eh la apple is close to Andorra La
eh la mazana está cerca de andorra La
bella surely the youtubers when
bella seguramente los youtubers cuando
When they see this news it's that nobody has
Cuando vean esta noticia es que nadie ha
commented on this news nobody surely
comentado esta noticia nadie seguramente
many will see it now in this
muchos lo van a ver ahora en este
extract okay surely the youtubers
extracto vale seguramente los youtubers
when those who live in Andorra who
cuando los que viven en andorra que nos
watch us okay When they see this extract they will
ven vale Cuando vean este extracto van a
know who the article refers to
saber qui a quién se refiere el artículo
sweat a kiss a kiss
sudor un beso un beso
the order service explains that the
el servicio de orden explica que la
victim was treated from the first
víctima fue atendida desde el primer
moment being hospitalized in the
momento siendo hospitalizada en el área
Mental Health area and filed the complaint
de Salud Mental y presentó la denuncia
on
el
Sunday I understand that this is
domingo entiendo que esto es el fin de
last weekend no Of course because today is
semana pasado no Claro porque hoy es
last weekend okay the agents
semana pasado vale los agentes
arrested the young men at the
detuvieron a los jóvenes ante los
first signs the statement indicates
primeros indicios señala el comunicado
both young men have been brought before the
ambos jóvenes han pasado a disposición
court this afternoon well
judicial esta tarde bueno
eh well then some
Eh bueno pues
events this surely those from
movidotas esto seguramente los de
Andorra El auron the millor all those who
andorra El auron el millor todos los que
live there know who it is know who they
viven allí saben quién es saben a quién
are  referring to why this is very
se están refiriendo porque esto es muy
small I mean Andorra is very small it
pequeño o sea andorra es muy pequeño no
's not like I
es como yo que
know it's not like my chalet just joking just joking
sé no es como el chalet mío es broma es
[ __ ] then
broma cabrones que luego se creen la
people think I'm rich and don't want to
gente que soy rico y no me quieren
become a member okay let's see Andorra is
hacerse miembro vale a ver andorra es
small everyone knows each other I'm going to look into the
pequeño todos se conocen voy a ver el
members issue let's see how it goes I'm going to see
tema miembros a ver cómo va voy a ver
how the members are doing why do I want to
cómo van los miembros para que quiero
see the stars shine in the sky If
ver brillar las estrellas en el cielo Si
by my side I have the most beautiful in the
a mi lado tengo la más bella del
firmament I don't know if let's see members
firmamento no sé si que a ver
bang down
pum bajón
2249 bang host in our mouths guys
2249 pum [__] en nuestra boca chavales
the gentlemen just surpassed and also
la señoreros acaba de superar y además
fooled you the
os ha vacilado la
gentlemen just fooled you How many have I
señoreros acaba de vacilar Cuántos he
said please repeat it in the chat
dicho por favor repetírmelo en el chat
repeat it in the chat please to put it
repetímelo en el chat porfa para ponerlo
the bar p the ladies just fooled you
la barra p la señorías acaba de vacilar
guys bang in all the big mouth kid
chavales pum en todo el bocón chaval
can you repeat it in the chat finally
podéis repetírmelo en el chat por fin
Oh my mother my mother my mother V
Oh madre mía madre mía madre mía V
host tomorrow the gentlemen were laughing at
[__] mañana la señor ería riéndose de
the kids
la chavalería
eh the end of Javi Oliveira is near  let's
eh el fin de Javi oliveira está cerca a
see let's see
ver a ver
wait 2 2 49
espera 2 2 49
okay lamentable eh
vale lamentable eh
family 2 2 49
familia 2 2 49
lamentable how do I explain this
lamentable cómo le explico yo esto
tomorrow how do we explain this tomorrow to
mañana cómo le explicamos esto mañana a
the lordship pum he gave you your mouth eh he
la señoría pum os ha dado la boca eh os
gave you your mouth eh he gave you a
han dado en la boca eh os han dado
hard time well let's see let's see some
fuerte bueno a ver vamos a ver alguna
other little things jire man jire you
que otra cosilla jire hombre jire tú
're still here take another m a
estás por aquí todavía toma ya otro m un
kiss jire Thank you very much let's see
beso jire Muchas gracias a ver
various things let's see while
varias movidas vamos a ver mientras que
luare sends me something that happened
luare me manda una cosa que ha pasado
apparently something happened in the
por lo visto ha pasado algo en el
live of apparently it
directo
happened apparently
de por lo visto ha pasado por lo visto
something happened in Ali's live that
ha pasado algo en el directo del Ali que
we'll have it in a little while okay
lo vamos a tener dentro de un rato vale
luar is preparing it for me don't
me lo está preparando luar no os
worry
agobieis
eh let's see in the meantime other
eh vamos a ir viendo de mientras otras
little things
cosillas
okay Well I think that I think we're going to
vale Bueno yo creo que yo creo que vamos
start with this topic and it is that
a empezar por este tema y es que
Lali you know that in the last few days
Lali sabéis que en los últimos días
we have been commenting on
hemos estado comentando el acercamiento
Ricky's approach to a new girl okay
de Ricky a una nueva chica vale en
first of all Well there are signs of flirting
primer lugar Pues hay indicios de tonteo
Hey maybe a friend  we know it looks like
Oye a lo mejor una amiga no lo sabemos
a girlfriend it looks like
tiene pinta de ser una novia tiene pinta
someone she's getting to know
de ser alguien a quien está conociendo
okay romá thank you very much handsome how
vale romá muchas gracias guapísimo Cómo
are you But well she hasn't confirmed it and
estás Pero bueno no lo ha confirmado y
while she doesn't confirm it Well there's
mientras que no lo confirme Pues hay
doubt unless we see them
duda a no ser que ya sea que los veamos
28 months taking pictures together okay
28 meses haciéndose fotos juntos vale
then you would say Well it
entonces ya dirías tú Bueno pues me
seems to me that they're a bit of a couple we've
parece a mí que son un poco pareja hemos
been commenting on the stories that they've
estado comentando pues las historias que
uploaded together we've been
han subido juntos hemos estado
commenting on things it doesn't seem like
comentando cosillas no parece ser que
every night well they have dates and
todas las noches pues tienen citas y
such Well there's romance here I understand
demás Bueno aquí hay romance Yo entiendo
this as romance then the next day
esto como romance luego al día siguiente
we have also been commenting
hemos estado comentando
Juan Palma Thank you very much
también Juan Palma Muchas gracias muchas
thank you very much but ugh Thank you very much but it's
gracias pero Uf Muchas gracias pero la
going to cost you now eh I mean I think the
os va a costar ya eh o sea creo que la
gentlemen get like 300 members I
señoreros saca como 300 miembros me
remember the other day even good I don't
acuerdo que el otro día incluso buena no
know if it was good per percha he told you if we
sé si fue buen per percha os dijo si
reach
llegamos a
2800 I'll put the rest for the 3000
2800 yo pongo el resto para los 3000
big prick eh misfire
pinchazo gordo eh gatillazo
Eh The next day we were commenting on
Eh Al día siguiente estuvimos comentando
the criticism that Ricky Eddie was receiving
las críticas que estaba recibiendo Ricky
because Well because the the
Eddie porque Bueno pues porque el el el
profile the profile more or less  no the
perfil el perfil más o menos no el
girl's profile because it would have some
perfil de chica pues tendría algunas
coincidences with
coincidencias con el target de
Lali's target let's see this girl I don't know is different
Lali a ver esta chica no sé es diferente
Lali has more tattoos I don't know I have no
Lali tiene más tatuaje No lo sé no tengo
idea honestly I have no idea I don't
ni idea la verdad no tengo ni idea no
know any of them well Lali's profile we
las conozco a ninguna bueno el perfil de
already know a little no but I
Lali ya lo conocemos un poco no pero no
have no idea what this girl will be like I
tengo ni idea de cómo será esta chica no
can't play her Simply because she has
la puedo jugar Simplemente porque tenga
a tattoo of a snake and another
un tatuaje de una serpiente y otro
tattoo on her neckline like they were
tatuaje en el escote como estaban
saying yesterday that I don't know if it's
diciendo ayer que que no sé si será
true But listen to me The thing is that
verdad Pero escúchame La Movida es que
today is amazing today is
lo de hoy es flipante lo de hoy es
amazing keep pressing the like button
flipante ir pulsando el botón de like
because your asses are going to open
porque se os va a abrir el culo en
as soon as I say the next
cuanto os diga la siguiente
sentence I say it
frase la digo
eh I say it I
eh la digo la
say it
digo
Lali has been
Lali ha estado hoy
attacking both
atacando tanto a
Ricky and the new
Ricky como a la nueva
girl today okay
chica vale
eh From what I'm checking now on
eh Por lo que estoy comprobando ahora en
her profile from what I'm checking
su perfil por lo que estoy comprobando
now on her
ahora en su
profile she has
perfil
removed the
ha quitado los
likes okay but apart from removing
likes vale pero es que aparte de quitar
the
los
likes something happened before entering
likes ha pasado algo antes de entrar
because we have The screenshots we have The
porque tenemos Las capturas tenemos Las
screenshots okay But there is something very curious
capturas vale Pero hay algo muy curioso
in the last
en los últimos
likes from quite a few
likes de bastantes
days not quite a few days No lie the
días no de bastantes días No mentira los
last likes or so It turns out that the
últimos likes o sea Resulta ser que los
last likes I don't know if he did it
últimos likes no sé si lo habrá hecho
with the intention that live boom
con la intención de que en directo pum
someone would put the likes and eat it
alguien se metan los likes y se lo coma
but it so happens that at
pero da la casualidad de que por lo
least 20 15 a lot of likes okay of
menos 20 15 un montón de likes vale de
the last ones are
los últimos son
very explicit gore also eh very
gore muy explícito además eh gore muy
explicit gore but the likes in which he
explícito pero los likes en los que
shared a tweet where both
compartía twit donde se atacaba tanto a
the girl and Ricky were attacked he has removed them what's
la chica como a Ricky los ha quitado qué
happening we have a screenshot we
es lo que pasa que tenemos captura
have a screenshot he sent it to me he
tenemos captura me lo ha mandado me lo
sent it to me gu otaku okay guade gossip
ha mandado gu otaku vale guade chismoso
gossip
chismoso
bastard gossip and Gossip bastard okay
cabrón chismoso y Cotilla cabrón vale
luare The
luare Ya está subiéndome el
topic is already uploading okay handsome tomorrow we'll talk in the
tema vale guapo mañana hablamos por la
morning when I'm in the little [ __ ] a big
mañana que estoy en el canijo un
kiss
besote
eh
eh
my goodness It's so noticeable that this guy does
madre mía Cómo se nota que el pavo este
n't know how to be alone and tries to prove
no sabe estar solo e intenta demostrar
something by being with another so quickly how
algo estando con otra tan rápido qué
embarrassed I am
vergüenza me da
Jury okay Ali likes this
Jurado vale le gusta Ali este
tweet one this girl pretends to be his
tweet uno esta chica aparenta ser su
daughter
hija
Hello hello hello let's see can I even
Hola hola hola a ver puedo incluso
buy that the target profile can  be
comprar que el target perfil pueda ser
similar to Ali or that it's a
similar al Ali o que sea una bandera
red flag for some reasons well I don't know
roja por algunos motivos bueno no lo sé
that's very subjective but man that she
eso ya es muy subjetivo pero hombre que
looks like his daughter It's not that Ricky is very
parezca su hija No es que Ricky es muy
young let's see Ricky Ricky is very
jovencillo a ver Ricky Ricky es muy
young I think Ricky is like 25
joven creo que Ricky tiene como 25
no Ricky is a kid And that girl who will
no Ricky es un crío Y esa chica queé
be 20 maybe
tendrá 20 a lo mejor
not Javi would you return to the Gameplay I want to see
no Javi volverías a los Gameplay quiero
you play Super Mario Wonder Uy how
verte jugar Super Mario Wonder Uy qué
cool very cool
chulo chulísimo
very cool I don't rule it out but it's just that I do
chulísimo no lo descarto pero es que no
n't have time I just don't have time Look
tengo tiempo es que no tengo tiempo Mira
the next day that I can afford to spend
el siguiente día que me pueda permitir
6 hours making
pegarme 6 horas haciendo
content that is not gossip that we don't
contenido que no sea salseo que no
have any theme let's put together the
tengamos ningún tema vamos a montar la
Lego mini that I have here is that I have to
mini de Lego que la tengo aquí es que la
put it together okay but the thing is that
tengo que montar ya vale pero es que
every day I have a theme luckily
todos los días tengo temita por suerte
every day and a theme okay because
todos los días y temita vale porque es
also in order not to break the schedule the
que además para no romper el horario la
diet the rest or the training the
dieta el desc o el entrenamiento el
schedule is what if you are already
horario es el que si os estáis dando
realizing things are going in a square way
cuenta ya las cosas van cuadricular
I am respecting schedules of the time
estoy respetando horarios de a la hora
that the videos are uploaded on the three
que se suben los vídeos en los tres
channels okay if anything it moves a little
canales vale si acaso se mueve un poco
the main one is okay but more or less
el del principal vale pero más o menos
for more or less Van Van around the
por más o menos Van Van rondando la
same time
misma hora
okay Hi Javi a little hello I am the one you
vale Hola Javi un saludito yo soy el que
call a pregnant woman A hug and
llamas mujer embarazada Un abrazo y
greetings to @ cacahuetes secret who will
saludos para @ cacahuetes secreto que
see this video cacao 4 Love cacao 4 you
verá este video cacao 4 Love cacao 4
get me into some moves that I don't
me metéis en unas movidas que yo no las
understand how are you the one I call a
entiendo cómo que tú eres el que llamo
pregnant woman Why do I call you a
embarazada Por qué te llamo mujer
pregnant woman Javi correct the title
embarazada Javi corrige el título
correct it you who are a moderator Chocho how
corrígelo tú que eres moderadora [__]
much to ask me for the wrench and we don't
que mucho pedirme la llave inglesa y no
squeeze Well I don't know if you can but
apretamos Bueno tú no sé si puedes pero
Iván can surely Iván or
el Iván puede seguro el Iván o
him or some of this the luare or something that
el o alguno de esto el luare o algo que
happens to him the title
le pasa el título
tiktoker arrested for the worst
tiktoker detenidos por lo peor mensajes
intimate messages from Katy Ángel Lali returns to the
íntimos de Katy Ángel Lali vuelve a la
charge what's wrong with the title what's wrong with
carga no le pasa al título que le pasa
the title Boomer What's wrong with the title
el título Boomer Qué le pasa al título
Boomer well let's see what we
Boomer bueno a ver que nos
two get into Why does the
enrollamos dos Por qué el payaso de
editing clown always end up going out with the
ediciones acaba saliendo siempre con el
same prototype of woman if he ever
mismo prototipo de mujer si es que llega
does it Which he hates
a hacerlo Al cual odia
publicly but let's see but how does
públicamente pero vamos a ver pero cómo
he like
l le da like a
this arrested is wrong me  you guys are getting on my
esto detenidos está mal me estáis
nerves a bit detidos it's
tocando un poco las narices detidos es
true detidos Hey but detidos I
verdad detidos Oye pero detidos me
think it's great to monetize detidos
parece muy bien para monetizar detidos
detidos Hey detidos Okay, let's see,
detidos Oye detidos Está bien a ver
taking into account how I speak in
teniendo en cuenta como yo hablo en la
real life, we're not going to get tiki
vida real tampoco nos vamos a poner tiki
micki with how I speak in writing you ca
micki con como hablo en en escrito
n't put melted in the title
no podéis poner derretidos en el título
please three Where are the parents of the
porfa tres Dónde están los padres de las
girls who think it's a good idea to go out with this
chicas que ven buena idea salir con este
parasite boom and then he also likes
parásito pum y luego le da like también
one who says love in 2023 replacing
a uno que dice el amor en 2023 sustituir
couples like they were
parejas como si fueran
socks and another like please tell me
calcetines y otro like dime por favor
that he didn't make a relationship public again mother of
que no hizo pública una relación otra
beautiful love mother of beautiful love mother of
hermoso madre del amor hermosa madre del
beautiful love come on eh come on why do I
hermoso va saco eh va
want to see the
saco para que quiero ver brillar las
stars shine in the
estrellas en el
sky If I have the ma by my side Hey I'm
cielo Si a mi lado tengo la má Oye me
getting a little lazy the
está dando un poco pereza el canal
main channel when will it reach
principal cuándo va a llegar a los
500,000 the main channel I'm counting on
500000 el canal principal cuento con que
everyone here to be
todos los que estáis aquí estáis
subscribed to Javi oliveira
suscritos a Javi oliveira
let's see I'm going to do the test there are
a ver voy a voy a hacer la prueba hay
few people but I'm going to do the  test I understand I do
poca gente pero voy a hacer la prueba
n't understand I
entiendo no entiendo quiero entender
want to
quiero
understand I want to understand I do
entender
n't see it here
no lo veo aquí
look I want to
mira quiero
understand here is the
entender aquí está la
mini
mini
uncle can you believe that I saw this this this
tío te puedes creer que he visto esto
and he wanted me that it was uncle Sur
esto esto y me quería que era el tío Sur
at IB's house I said the elite didn't sign him
en casa de IB he dicho no lo fichó la
anymore all right listen to me I want to
élite ya del todo bueno escúchame quiero
understand that this miniature that you're
entender que esta miniatura que estáis
seeing p Javi Oliveira main channel
viendo p Javi oliveira canal principal
I want to understand that you're all
quiero entender que todos estáis
subscribed to the Main Channel
suscritos al Canal principal
no Let's see it's that you're all
no A ver es que estáis todo el mundo
saying Obviously obviously let's see review it
diciendo Obvio obvio a ver repasarlo
everyone before moving on to the
todo el mundo antes de pasar al
next extract main channel Javi
siguiente extracto canal principal Javi
Oliveira okay man we have to reach
oliveira vale hombre que hay que llegar
500,000 I think I think eh I think eh I
ya a los 500.000 Creo creo eh creo eh
think we have to reach
creo que hay que llegar a los
500,000 Javi Oliveira okay the video We'll
500.000 Javi oliveira vale el vídeo
see it later when you finish the
Luego lo vemos cuando terminéis el
live when we finish the live you
directo cuando terminemos el directo os
go over there I'm seeing that there are
vais para allá Es que estoy viendo que
people who are subscribing now
hay gente que se está suscribiendo ahora
when I'm
cuando lo estoy
saying it I'm seeing that there are people who
diciendo estoy viendo que hay gente que
are subscribing now when I'm saying it
se está suscribiendo ahora cuando lo
kid I swear eh p and every time I
chaval te lo juro eh p y cada vez que
update more people [ __ ] How
actualizo más gente [__] Qué poca
shameless there are people  here that is not
vergüenza hay gente aquí que no está
subscribed to the
suscrita al Canal
main Channel there is this channel that is not
principal hay de este canal que no está
main Channel but what a
principal pero qué
drag I am subscribed with both
fumada estoy suscrito con las dos
accounts with all the accounts that you
cuentas con todas las cuentas que
have on YouTube check it out okay
tengáis en YouTube repasarlo vale
subscribe to the main Channel you see what's
suscribiros al Canal principal viste que
going to be a Minecraft series
dasas va a ser una serie de Minecraft
Tell him to invite you because I haven't seen it I
Dile que te invite pues no lo hab visto
missed the greats of the
hecho en falta a los grandes del Canal
Javi Channel pix the SIM of n yf We love you
Javi pix el SIM de n yf Se os quiere
smiling face cacao 4 Love cacao 4 Love
cara sonriente cacao 4 Love cacao 4 Love
cacao 4 Love Those are the greats of the
cacao 4 Love Esos son los grandes del
Channel you the big donors no pixi
Canal tú los grandes donadores no pixi
left a lot of money here before I don't know
se dejaba aquí una pasta antes no sé a
where it went yes it's true that
dónde se habrá ido sí que es verdad que
pixi has been subscribed for a while I checked
pixi lleva tiempo eh revisado suscrito
okay come on okay I see that
venga vale venga vale veo que se habéis
like 40 50 people have subscribed of those who
suscrito como 40 50 personas de las que
are here right now okay Okay
estáis aquí ahora mismo bueno Vale
eh I'm going there in order because I have something
eh vo aí por orden porque tengo una cosa
Okay I'm going in
Vale voy a ir por
order Hello wait eh I'm preparing it that I hadn't
orden Hola espera eh lo preparo que no
prepared it
preparado
okay this that you have heard right now
vale esto que habéis escuchado ahora
has been heard for a second half a
mismo se ha escuchado un segundito medio
second that I have missed it is not a
segundito que se me ha escapado no es un
little dangerous it is  a little curious
poco peligroso es un poco curioso
eh according to what they send me by email This is the
eh según me mandan por email Este es el
context Okay I'm going to read the email and
contexto Vale Voy a leer el email y
put what they send me okay this has
poner lo que me mandan vale esto por lo
apparently been published on tiktok it
visto se ha publicado en tiktok
is obviously public if not I would not
evidentemente es público si no yo no lo
publish it like It's logical Hi Javi I'm
publicaría como Es lógico Hola Javi te
writing to you because it's the first time that I
escribo porque es la primera vez que
get to the gossip before you and
llego antes que tú al chisme y a lo
maybe you're interested I followed Katy
mejor te interesa yo seguía a Katy
When I was little but I grew up and her
Cuando era pequeño pero crecí y sus
videos stopped interesting me I didn't know
vídeos dejaron de interesarme no sabía
anything about her until a week ago a
nada de ella hasta hace una semana un
little more than tiktok was filled with
poquito más que tiktok se llenó de
videos of her crying it turns out that she
vídeos suyos llorando resulta que ella
explained that Carmelo granado had been
explicó que oso Carmelo granado le había
unfaithful to her For the last
estado siendo infiel Durante los últimos
four or five years they had been
cu o 5 años ellos llevaban como unos 18
together for about 18 years things would stay there if it
años juntos la cosa se quedaría ahí si
weren't because two or three days ago they
no fuese porque hace dos o tres días le
hacked YouTube Instagram and tiktok in
hackearon YouTube Instagram y tiktok en
which they started uploading
el cual empezaron a subir conversaciones
somewhat dirty conversations of them with another
un poco guarrillas de ellas con otro
influencer known for talking about how to
influencer conocido por hablar de cómo
take care of puppies the influencer in
cuidar a los perritos el influencer en
question is called Ninja I knew that as
cuestión se llama Ninja yo sabía que en
soon as I recovered the account he would delete the
cuanto recuperase la cuenta borraría los
videos so I kept them  I'm going to
vídeos así que me los guardé voy a
put them together in the email but I warn you that
juntarlos al correo pero te aviso de que
they are quite creepy, the conversations
dan bastante grima las conversaciones
are very explicit apart from the
son muy explícitas aparte de las
conversations with Tommy the influence of the
conversaciones con Tommy el influ de los
puppies, emails
perritos también se filtraron correos
between Katy and Oso were also leaked where she wrote
entre Katy y oso donde ella escribía
word for word everything they had to
palabra por palabra todo lo que debían
say about networks, I mean they are emails, damn
decir sobre redes o sea son email [__]
how strong word for word everything they
qué fuerte palabra por palabra todo lo
had to say on networks about the
que tenían que decir en redes sobre la
breakup and on what day, well this, this. In
ruptura y en qué día bueno esto esto En
part I can understand it, I understand it
parte lo puedo entender lo entiendo
because it is an agreement, I mean, you break up with
porque es un acuerdo o sea tú rompes con
your partner and you both are media-savvy, you
tu pareja y los dos sois mediáticos os
agree on what type of
ponéis de acuerdo en qué tipo de
statement to release, what to say and such. I don't
comunicado lanzar qué decir y tal no me
think it's bad, I don't think it's bad either, okay,
parece mal tampoco me parece mal vale a
unless it's a lie, I know that it
no ser que sea una mentira yo que sé que
affects someone and is super scary,
afecte a alguien y sea super espantoso
no, in the last video that Katy uploaded to
no en el último vídeo que subió Katy a
YouTube to which you reacted, she tells
YouTube al que tú reaccionaste cuenta
how he became aggressive with her and
como él se puso agresivo con ella y le
broke a collar she was wearing,
rompió un collar que llevaba puesto
apart from other things that are super
aparte de más cosas que son super
beasts So I hope it's real and not
bestias Así que espero que sea real y no
that they are playing with such serious things
que estén jugando con cosas tan serias
just to gain fame, greetings Thank you very much, I
solo por ganar fama un saludo Mil
don't know what's worth it, let's see This is what
gracias no sé qué vale a ver Esto es lo
has been
que se ha
spread This  This is what has been spread Let's
difundido Esto es lo que se ha difundido
see, let's
A ver vamos a
see, hosa, but what a deal, what a deal, eh,
verlo hosa pero qué movida qué movida eh
what a deal And what a coincidence it seems to me that
qué movida Y qué casualidad me parece
this is leaked now too, I tell you
que se filtre esto ahora también te digo
Hello Well, eh, let's see, you can do whatever
Hola Bueno eh a ver yo puedes hacer lo
you want really,
que quieras realmente
eh, if you want to threaten me or if you want to
eh si me quieres amenazar o si quieres
do everything you want, well, I
hacer todo lo que quieres pues bueno yo
will act accordingly later,
luego actuaré en consecuencia
eh, I don't think it's that bad, I mean,
eh tampoco creo que sea para tanto o sea
Tommy and
yo Tommy y
esadi are there, he's there, the
esadi está ahí está ahí el
boy is there, the boy is
chico está ahí el
the boy in the chat Hey,
chico está el chico en el chat Oye
want to
quiere
upload Hey, wanna
subir Oye quies
upload Javi, be careful because Ninja
subir Javi lleva cuidado porque Ninja ha
said to report salsa channels,
dicho de denunciar a canales de salsero
there's a video
hay un vídeo
exposing him and say which channels to report,
exponiendo y decir qué canales denunciar
but if this is viral on tiktok,
pero si esto es viral en tiktok
dude, let's see if you want, I'll listen to them
churri a ver si tú quieres los escucho
alone and and and that's it, and we don't
yo solo y y y ya está y no le damos
spread the audios, if you're ashamed, I
difusión a los audios si te da vergüenza
respect that, but then I understand that they are
respeto pero entonces entiendo que son
real, I don't
reales
understand that they are real, no no, no, don't
no entiendo que son reales
delete the boy's messages,
no no no borris los mensajes del chico
eh, tomy, do you want to upload
eh tomy quieres subir a explicar
something, give your version, comment on something,
algo a dar tu versión a comentar algo
everyone is here, but well, it's that
aquí está todo el mundo pero bueno es
I'm
que yo
freaking out, your Mods are blocking me  now it does
flipo me están bloqueando tus Mods ahora
n't come out verified Hey but I didn't
no sale verificado Oye pero no lo
block him who's blocking him
bloqueé quién lo está
eh tesa you banned the boy why did you
eh tesa has baneado al chico por qué lo
ban him
has baneado
tesa I don't understand why you
tesa no entiendo por qué la has
banned her because I speak in capital letters but come on let's
baneado porque hablo por mayúscula pero
see tesa the boy is there is
vamos vamos a ver tesa que está el chico
the protagonist of the story and
está el protagonista de la historia y
take it let's see tesa the
coge vamos a ver tesa está el
protagonist of the story and with all your
protagonista de la historia y con to tu
Papo and with all your Papo bans him because he
Papo y con to tu Papo lo banea porque
wrote in capital letters I can't have
escribió en mayúscula no puedo tener
stronger and more powerful moderators
moderadores más fuertes y más potentes
eh Let's see
eh A ver
Tommy wants to upload I haven't read in the
Tommy quiere subir no he leído en el
chat that Tommy wants to upload of course
chat que tomy quiere subir por supuesto
No no no he's threatening to see it's normal
No no no está amenazando a ver es normal
if it's his privacy and he doesn't want it to be
si es su intimidad y no quiere que se
shared What happens is that I understand that
comparta Lo que pasa que entiendo que
this is viral, I mean from what they
esto es viral o sea por lo que me han
sent me in the email it is viral if the
mandado a mí en el email es viral si el
boy doesn't want us to put it up we don't
chico no quiere que lo pongamos no lo
put it up but man, we give him the
ponemos pero hombre le damos la
opportunity Let him upload it and tell us about it,
oportunidad Que suba y nos lo comente de
conversations have
m se han compartido conversaciones
also been shared and I know it feels very bad okay it's
también y sé que sienta muy mal vale es
a bit of a panada because if this has I don't
un poco panada porque si esto tiene no
know how many millions of views on tiktok
sé cuántos millones de visitas en tiktok
then I'm not going to make it viral anymore  But
pues no lo voy a viralizar yo más Pero
well if the boy doesn't want us to
bueno si el chico no quiere que lo
put it and he's here explicitly we don't
pongamos y está aquí explícitamente no
put it he said he wants to upload he did
lo ponemos ha dicho que quiere subir
n't say he wants to upload
no ha dicho que quiere subir
no Javi that the Bot banned him first but do
no Javi que el Bot lo baneo primero pero
n't ban anyone it's that you don't ban
que no lo banis a nadie es que no banis
anyone it's that I'm always watching how
a nadie es que estoy siempre viendo cómo
bane bans people let's see I'm going to
bane banea a la peña a ver voy a
unban the
quitarle el baneo al
boy I'm banned on three of my accounts
chico estoy Ban en tres cuentas mías
But why did I ban the kid tomy I'm going to
Pero por qué bane al chaval tomy voy a
look at you on instagram but I'm
mirarte en instagram pero una cosa sí
going to do one thing tomy I'm not going to share it
voy a hacer tomy No lo voy a compartir
but while I look for you on Instagram
pero mientras que te busco en Instagram
and while I unban you eh I'm going to
y mientras que te quito el baneo eh voy
listen to it privately to know
a escucharlo yo en privado para saber de
what it's about okay I mean I'm going to listen to it
lo que va vale o sea voy a escucharlo yo
with everything muted to know what it's about okay I
con todo silenciado para saber de lo que
don't share it Look mute the
va vale no lo comparto Mira silencio los
microphones okay for me to listen to it in
micros vale para escucharlo yo en la
privacy to know what the
intimidad para saber de lo que va las
conversations are about and I upload you and comment okay
conversaciones y te subo y comenta vale
King while I unban you
Rey mientras que te quito el baneo
while I unban you and I
mientras que te quito el baneo y te
look for you on instagram to invite you okay It
busco en instagram para invitarte vale
's already
Ya está
unblocked okay okay okay perf perf
desbloqueado vale vale vale perf perf
tomy I'll eat you everything  the cimbrel my
tomy Te como todo el cimbrel mi Javi
handsome Javi TR a kiss lampur don't interrupt me
guapo TR un beso lampur no me interrumpa
now what the [ __ ] [ __ ] the protagonist is here
ahora que [__] [__] que está aquí el
tomy I'm going to listen to it in
protagonista tomy voy a escucharlo en
private to know what it's about at
privado para saber de lo que va por lo
least a little to see if they are yes if they are
menos un poco a ver si son si son cosas
sexual things there's not much more to
sexuales tampoco hay mucho más que
listen to but anyway I'm going to listen to it a
escuchar pero bueno voy a escucharlo un
little bit because I have three I have
poco por encima porque tengo tres tengo
three videos silence them Look
tres vídeos los silenci Mira no lo
nobody is listening to it Tom I'm talking to you Now I'm
escucha nadie Tom que te hablo Ahora por
talking to you Now on Instagram don't go
te hablo Ahora por Instagram no te vayas
please okay okay I'm going to I'm going to
porfa
look for the kid
vale vale voy a voy a buscar al Chaval
on
en
Instagram Okay I'm going to look I'm going to look for
instagram Vale Voy a buscar voy a buscar
the kid on Instagram and I'm going to try to
al Chaval en Instagram y voy a intentar
talk to
hablar con
him he told me in theory that if he uploads I did
él que me ha dicho en teoría que si sube
n't see a to the
no vi un
bathroom but nothing one second one second
al baño pero nada un segund un segund
Inn It's okay I'm going to look for it
Inn De nada vale lo voy a buscar
eh tomy if you can open it for me please
eh tomy si me puedes abrir tú por favor
on Instagram I'd appreciate it and I'll upload it
en instagram te lo agradezco y te subo
but
pero ya
okay okay let's
vale
see if we have it let's
vale a ver si lo
see if we have it I do
tenemos a ver si lo
n't know if I would upload with a camera it's that I do
tenemos no sé si subiría con cámara es
n't know who the boy is I'm going to
que no sé quién es el chico voy a
look for him on YouTube first wait his
buscarlo en YouTube primero espérate se
name is
llama
Tommy and scadi I'm going to look for him on YouTube
Tommy y scadi voy a buscarlo en YouTube
to see who he
para ver quién
is  has gone aalen this guy
es ha ido aalen este chico
Ah but this guy
Ah pero este chico
idalen Let's see let's see if he
idalen A ver vamos a ver vamos a ver si
talks to me let's see if he talks to me this
me habla vamos a ver si me habla esto
This is some [ __ ] eh Let's see this is a
Esto es una movida eh A ver esto es un
this is some very intense gossip no Let's see let's
esto es un salseo muy intenso no A ver
see this
vamos a ver esta
[ __ ] let's see I'm going to look for him because he hasn't
movida a ver voy a buscarlo porque él no
talked to me
me ha hablado
Tommy Here I have it here I
Tommy Aquí lo tengo aquí lo
have it Send a
tengo Envía
message
mensaje
okay okay we have it we have it
vale vale lo tenemos lo
but it's that this I I
tenemos pero es que esto yo yo lo de lo
this channel I
de este canal Yo es que no lo entiendo
just don't understand it I don't know why Why do you watch this channel I mean I this channel I just don't understand it or rather we're here following one and suddenly the one with the conversations appears in the chat this It
las conversaciones en el chat esto Solo
can only happen here the truth is things
puede pasar aquí la verdad las cosas
as they are it's wrong for me to say it but
como son está mal que yo lo diga pero
this is how it is but the guy doesn't answer me or anything
esto es así pero no me contesta ni nada
Uh he doesn't answer me let's see I know it was him
Eh no me contesta a ver Sé que era él
because it was
porque estaba
verified it
verificado
was a coincidence he
ha sido casualidad me
tells me how to join I'll
dice cómo me
send you the link Wait I'm
uno te mando link Espera estoy
preparing the link so the kid can join
preparando el link para que el chaval
so I want to see
entre para que quiero ver brillar
the Ramóns shine Today is the day
las Ramón Hoy es el día
yes luare has put the link to the
si luare te ha puesto el link de los
audios for you  Why can't we hear them
audios por qué no podemos escucharlos
if they're public I have no
nosotros si son públicos no me queda la
doubt what the hell they were saying cacao 4 Love
duda que puñetas decían cacao 4 Love
cacao 4 Love cacao 4 Love cacao 4 Love
cacao 4 Love cacao 4 Love cacao 4 Love
cacao 4
cacao 4
Love what I'm seeing on Twitter is
Love lo que estoy viendo en Twitter es
a [ __ ] wonder eh what I'm
una [__] maravilla eh lo que estoy
seeing on Twitter is a [ __ ] wonder it
viendo en Twitter es una [__] maravilla
really has no
de verdad no tiene
name let's
nombre a
see why I want to see the
ver para qué quiero ver brillar las
stars shine in the sky If by my side I have
estrellas en el cielo Si a mi lado tengo
the most beautiful in the
la más bella del
firmament I don't know if she'll
firmamento no sé si me
understand this that I
entenderá esto que te
have for you what I want your heart how it
tengo lo que quiero yo tu corazón como
fits
me queda por
inside
dentro
for what I want to see the
para qu Quiero ver brillar las
stars shine in the
estrellas en
sky if by my side I have the most beautiful
elano si a mi lado tengo la más bella
in the
del
firmament I don't know if you'll
firmamento no sé si me
understand this that I have for you
entenderás esto que te tengo
[Music]
[Música]
like a smile inside a kiss so I'm going to
como sonr por dentro un beso so voy a
mute the news a little while I
silenciar un poco las notis mientras que
'm talking to the kid
estoy hablando con el chaval
okay I want to see the
vale Quiero ver brillar las
stars shine there we have it there we have it
estrellas ahí lo tenemos ahí lo tenemos
kid you don't have to hit accept on the
chaval no tienes que darle aceptar a la
camera and
cámara y
accept the camera and the mic tomy
al acepta la cámara y el micro tomy que
otherwise it won't
si no no te
come in kids and breaking the
entra chavales y reventando el
link
lien
hello hello hello hello
hola hola
hello we'll see you there tomy Wait  one
hola ahí te vemos tomy Espérate un
moment Wait a moment I'm going to
momento Espérate un momento que lo voy a
put it so that it's more or less visible
poner para que sea más o menos visible
you hear me well
tú me escuchas bien
No I can't hear
No yo no te escucho a
you we can't hear you eh
ti a ti no te escuchamos eh
tomy And now now we hear you tomy
tomy Y ahora ahora te escuchamos tomy
What's up How are you How's everything okay and
Qué pasa Cómo estás Qué tal todo bien y
you I'm okay hoo but Wait a moment let me
tú yo bien hoo pero Espérate un momento
attach the camera and we start
que acople la cámara y empezamos
okay do you want me to reduce the quality
vale quieres que reduzca la la calidad
of my camera or is it that you don't your
de mi cámara o es que no te no se te
camera doesn't move let's see I'm going to reduce it I'm going to
cámara a ver voy voy a reducir la la voy
put it lower okay Fix it and I'll
poner más bajo vale Arréglalo y yo lo
put it like this and that's it and it seems like I'm
pongo así y ya y ya parece que te estoy
looking at you to see if Now if it moves or
mirando a ver si se Ahora si me mueve o
not What's up you're frozen
no Qué va estás congelado
dude well
tío pues
Oh
Oh
F
F
what's up tomy you put it in without let's
qué va tomy la has metido sin a
see I'm going eh it
ver voy eh
says There it is
dice
no what's up dude you look
no qué va tío se te ve
black
negro
[Music]
[Música]
well you have it activated surely down
pues la tienes activada seguro abajo
where it says stop camera and Activate
donde pone detener cámara y Activar
camera s yes yes no now but I know Of course
cámara s sí sí no ahora pero se Claro
but it's that I have the feeling that I
pero es que tengo la sensación que me me
freeze Yeah yes it freezes Why is it a
congelo Sí sí se congela Por qué es una
Webcam Well I don't know it's not one it's a it's
Webcam Pues no sé no es una es una es
a camera would you prefer that I put the  webcam
una cámara prefieres que ponga la webcam
by webcam of course it's going to give less
por la webcam claro va a dar menos
problems okay come on I'm going to give it I'm going to
problemas vale venga voy a dar voy a
put the webcam down you have a key or
poner la webcam abajo tienes una llave o
rather down you have like a nut you give it
sea abajo tienes como una tuerca le das
and change the camera and that's it no
y cambias la cámara y ya está no hace
need to leave
falta salir
Okay there okay let's see the difference it's
Bueno ahí vale a ver la diferencia es
brutal eh Let's see it seems like we
brutal eh A ver parece que parece que
're talking with a cell phone But okay
estamos hablando con un móvil Pero bueno
but okay at least I can see you at
pero bueno por lo menos que te vea por
least a little more now you
lo menos que sea un poquito más ahora me
see me frozen or not No now you can see you
ves congelado o no No ahora se te ve
Now you can see it's the other camera that doesn't
Ahora se te ve es la otra cámara que no
admit them Okay but now you see me like a
admite Bueno pero ahora me ves como
ghost not a little Okay a little
un un fantasma no un poco Bueno un poco
a little but okay here we usually see
un poco pero bueno aquí solemos ver
Many ghosts it seems like this the
Muchos fantasmas parece esto el programa
Jiménez show nothing happens
de Jiménez no pasa nada
What's up Tomy nice to meet you I didn't
Qué pasa tomy encantado de conocerte no
know you I don't have the pleasure of
te conocía no tengo el gusto de
knowing you eh How come you were
conocerte eh Cómo es que estabas por
here when we were just talking about the
aquí cuando estábamos justo hablando del
subject well coincidentally because I was just and I just
tema pues pues casualidad porque justo
uploaded the video of everything you
e acabo de subir el vídeo de de todo lo
're talking about I uploaded it an hour ago
que estás hablando lo subí hace una hora
and And before I was on YouTube I put Tommy
y Y antes estaba en YouTube puse Tommy
keat for and I see your live and I see such that
keat para y veo tu directo y veo tal que
we're going to talk intimate messages and since
vamos a hablar mensajes íntimos y como
I've been all weekend eh  very nervous
yo llevo todo el fin de eh muy nervioso
about this issue and I am uh
sobre este tema y estoy
so you get an idea tomorrow
eh sea para que te hagas una idea mañana
I'm going to go to the police station in Madrid because
voy a ir a la comisaría de Madrid porque
I have one I have very good contacts in
tengo una tengo muy buenos contactos en
the police because I'm going to make videos with
la policía porque voy a hacer vídeos con
them okay And I'm going to report all the
ellos vale Y voy a denunciar a todos los
content creators who have used uh
creadores de contenido que han usado eh
their reach WhatsApp groups
su alcance grupos de WhatsApp grupos de
Telegram groups Instagram groups tiktok
Telegram grupos de Instagram tiktok
YouTube short and who have helped
YouTube short y que han ayudado a
spread the content of my
difundir el contenido de mis
conversations I'm going to report them all
conversaciones todos los voy a denunciar
because this According to the law whether in
porque esto Según la ley que sea en
Spain or in Mexico it is from one to five years in
España o en México es de un a 5 años de
prison or I mean it's that simple Well there it
cárcel o sea es así de simple Bueno ahí
happens that people that people
se po pasa que la gente que la gente
like how it is like it has already been leaked
como como es como ya ha estado filtrado
on some sites people like think that
por algunos sitios la gente como cree
as it has already been seen you can
que como ya se ha visto tú lo puedes
spread it But this there That's where these
difundir Pero esto ahí Ahí es donde se
these creators are wrong you ca
equivocan estos estos creadores tú esto
n't do this it doesn't matter that
no puedes hacer da igual que todo el
everyone who is in 50,000 networks a
mundo que esté en 50.000 redes una
private conversation if you share it
conversación privada si tú la compartes
if you share it you are committing a
si tú la compartes estás cometiendo un
crime well let's see
delito bueno a ver yo te explico una
something tomy I'll call you Tommy no yes yes yes
cosa tomy te llamo Tommy no sí sí sí
Look and let's see at the moment that you have
Mira e a ver yo en el momento que tú has
came in and you asked for it I respect you
entrado y lo has pedido Yo te respeto
with me they have done it on some occasion
conmigo lo han hecho en alguna ocasión
okay I mean I respect you and if you ask
vale o sea yo te respeto y si tú pides
that it not be played it does not play let's
que no se reproduzca no se reproduce a
see I have heard it and it is not anything out
ver lo he escuchado y tampoco es nada
of this world I also tell you but no no let's
del otro mundo también te digo pero no
see because because the
no a ver porque porque porque la
conversation that you posted is the
conversación que tú pusiste es la
conversation that I had with him with this
conversación que yo tuve con el con el
husband Lu the one that you have
marido este Lu la de la de la que tienes
with kti that I have also
con kti que también también la he
heard in this at this time
escuchado en este en este tiempo
while you were going up let's see it is not anything
mientras que tú subías a ver no es nada
out of this world I understand that no Let's see no no it's that there is no
del otro mundo entiendo que no A ver no
one from this world
no te es que no hay nadie del otro mundo
they are conversations that two people of
son conversaciones que dos personas de
30 years could have perfectly for
30 años podrían tener perfectamente para
me that is not the problem it is that I am
mí eso no es el problema es que yo soy
a very private person and my
una persona muy privada y mi relación
private relationship has always been private so it does
privada siempre ha sido privada entonces
not make me happy at all to see
a mí no me hace ninguna gracia ver
messages that I have written to a person in
mensajes que he escrito a una persona en
a private environment messages that are
un entorno privado mensajes que son
intimate it does not make me happy at all and
íntimos a mí no me hace ninguna gracia y
and for this reason uh for this reason I have had
y por esta razón eh por esta razón he
all the videos taken down okay And
hecho bajar todos los vídeos vale Y
tomorrow I am going to report six
mañana voy a denunciar seis creadores de
content creators let's see I understand what happens that
contenido a ver lo entiendo lo que pasa
you will see uh that it does not work that you are
que verás tú eh que no funciona que tú
going to  the police station and complaints I'm
vas a la comisaría y denuncias te lo
telling you so you know in case you want to
digo para que tú lo sepas por si quieres
sue someone you have to hire
demandar a alguien tienes que contratar
a lawyer and you have to file
a un abogado y tienes que poner demandas
civil lawsuits Eh yes yes yes no no but I have it
civiles Eh sí sí sí no no pero yo tengo
anymore don't worry first I'm going to I'm going to
ya no te preocupes primero voy a voy a
file the complaint but in Mexico for
hacer la denuncia pero en México por
example because bu that's the least of it eh tomy
ejemplo porque bu es lo de meno eh tomy
here you are at the moment Look, I've been through that about
aquí tú en el momento Mira yo he pasado
me, audio
por eso de mí se han publicado audio
captures and such have been published and I know that it's not a
capturas y tal y yo sé que no es plato
pleasant experience yes it's true that
de buen gusto sí que es verdad que una
once it's so viral on tiktok And it
vez que está tan virales en tiktok Y
's so viral everywhere,
está tan virales en todos lados pues
well it's a little difficult to stop
como que ya es un poco difícil de frenar
But if you appear in the chat and
Pero si tú apareces por el chat y me lo
ask me directly, no, I have no choice
pides directamente yo no a mí no me
but to respect you, but
queda otra que respetarte lo que pero
normally, normally on tiktok, on tiktok you ca
norment norment en tiktok en tiktok ya
n't find them anymore, okay
no ya no les puedes encontrar vale
because eh we have reported everything on
porque eh hemos denunciado en todo en
tiktok and all the creators who have
tiktok y todos los creadores que han
posted these videos have a Warning I ca
puesto estos vdeos tienen una un Warning
n't hear you eh No I'm not
No te escucho eh No no estoy
listening to you oh open up and everyone who has
escuchándote ah abre y todos los que han
posted the videos has a Warning on
puesto los vídeos tienen un Warning en
their  account CX Okay
su cuenta CX Vale
and that And since it's not there now, eh, if I
y Y eso Y como ahora no está eh si yo
let eh all the creators eh share
dejo eh todos los creadores eh compartir
the content without saying anything, well this
los contenidos sin decir nada pues esto
never stops okay And I don't want to go
nunca se para vale Y yo no quiero entrar
on tiktok and see my private conversations
en tiktok y ver conciones privadas mías
and that's why I'm very hard on all the
y por eso soy muy duro con todos los
creators and I mean, it doesn't matter the
creadores y es decir que da igual el
size of the creator, there are creators with
tamaño del creador hay creadores de
10,000 followers, they have posted the video,
10,000 seguidores han puesto el el video
they are in the complaint and what I do is I
están en la denuncia y yo lo que hago es
record the eh, I download the video, I take
que grabo el eh descargo el video hago
screenshots of everything and I
capturas de pantallas de todo y todo
pass all this to my lawyer in Mexico and
esto lo pasó a mi abogado de México y me
I'm going to pay him whatever it takes because he
yo le voy a pagar lo que sea porque él
has
me ha
told me not to worry in that sense,
dicho no te preocupes en ese sentido que
in that sense I repeat
en ese sentido Ya te vuelvo a repetir
that I have been through the same thing and we
que yo he pasado por lo mismo y te
understand you perfectly and what is
entendemos perfectamente y lo que se
spoken between two people, the first thing is
hablen entre dos personas lo primero es
that you are not committing any crime,
que no estás cometiendo ningún delito
they are conversations that a
son conversaciones que pueden tener un
boy and a girl can have anywhere and
chico y una chica en cualquier parte y
as an adult and that's it and and don't
de adulto y ya está y y que no te
worry about that, we understand a
preocupes por eso entendemos una
question this why is it Why are
pregunta esto por qué se Por qué se
these conversations published Why are they
publica estas conversaciones Por qué se
made public because it is revenge
hacen públicas porque es una venganza
because it's revenge from her ex-husband, let's
porque es una venganza del ex marido a
see, I'm involved in it against Migration
ver yo estoy metido ahí en contra migré
because the woman who is Katy Angel,
porque la la mujer que es Katy Angel
okay, eh, is reporting
vale eh está denunciando se está está
her ex-husband is reporting her ex-husband for all the
denunciando su ex marido de todas las
infidelities she has had for
infidelidades que ha tenido durante
many years, okay, eh, the man, the man
muchos años vale eh el hombre el hombre
is a disgusting man, yes, and to get
es es un hombre asqueroso sí y él para
revenge on her, he is leaking the
vengarse de ella está filtrando las
conversations because one day he ran
conversaciones porque él un día corrió
her cell phone and took photos with his cell phone
su móvil y tomo tomó fotos con su móvil
of our conversations and he
de nuestras conversaciones y esto lo ha
published this, he quadroked his tiktok account and
publicado ha quado su cuenta de tiktok y
published it to get revenge, okay,
lo ha publicado para vengarse Vale
so he's also going to go to jail. I
entonces él también va a ir a la cárcel
mean, don't worry, it's only a
O sea no te preocupes eso es solamente
matter of time, okay, because it's very
cuestión de tiempo vale porque es muy
serious to do revenge revenge for or
grave hacer revenge revenge por o lo que
whatever, okay, what he did is very serious,
sea vale e muy grave lo que ha hecho él
if he was the one who did it like
si ha sido él el que ha hecho así como
you're telling me, it's super serious, I don't
tú me lo estás diciendo es super grave
know what country he lives in, I don't know if he lives in
no sé en qué país vive no sé si vive en
Venezuela, he lives in Venezuela or Mexico,
Venezuela él vive o o venezola o México
but anyway, we're going to report it
pero de todas forma lo vamos a denunciar
to everyone and everyone. And then what happened was
con todos y todos los Y luego qué pasó
that he did this with
que él hizo esto con la cuenta de de
Katy Angel's account, okay, then we got
Katy Angel vale luego nosotros
Kanger's account back and  we
recuperamos la cuenta de kanger y
delete everything but there are many creators
borramos todo pero hay muchos creadores
okay instead of just talking about
vale que en lugar de solamente hablar de
gossip that Ah there was this there was that no
chisme que Ah hubo esto hubo eso no
they have shared everything And worse than
ellos han compartido todo Y peor que
this is that they have created
esto es que han creado grupos de
WhatsApp or Instagram groups and they have and have
Whatsapp o de Instagram y han y han
published each of the conversations
publicado cada una de las conversaciones
word for word in the groups and
palabra por palabra en los grupos y eso
I cannot forgive that they have deleted Endo
yo no lo puedo perdonar han borado Endo
for example ton Toni Look for example I
por ejemplo ton Toni Mira por ejemplo yo
swear that I did not have the slightest
te juro que yo no tenía la más mínima
bad intention against you when I was
mala intención contra ti cuando estaba
watching it they sent it to me they told me
viéndolo me la han mandado me han dicho
that it was viral And if you ask me I will not
que era viral Y si tú me pides no lo
put it But you do not understand that there is also no
pongo Pero no entiende que también no
bad intention on the part of everyone no
hay mala intención por parte de todos no
but I do not say but Listen to me I am not saying
pero no digo pero Escúchame yo no digo
that there is bad intention neither from you nor from
que hay mala intención ni de ti ni de
the others that is what it means
los demás eso es lo que quiere decir
but if you are harming me And you are
pero si tú me estás perjudicando Y estás
damaging my honor by making people who had
dañando mi honor haciendo que gente que
not seen these conversations
no había visto estas conversaciones lo
see it Thank you you know And these Well me and
ven Gracias a ti sabes Y estos Pues yo y
then there It has been luck and it has been
entonces ahí Ha sido suerte y ha sido
that I see you live and I tell you
que yo te vea en directo y que te diga
Hey no lotino destiny destiny Tom
Oye no lotino el destino el destino Tom
no why But you know what happens Javier
no porque Pero sabes qué pasa Javier
Because if I see this an hour
Porque si yo esto lo veo una hora
later I your live  I'll record it and I'll
después yo tu directo lo grabo y mañana
report you tomorrow too, you know what because
te denuncio también sabes lo que porque
I don't know you if you're
yo no te conozco si tú me estás
harming me ig Then I hadn't been
perjudicando ig Entonces no había sido
bad, I have to defend my
mala yo me tengo que defender mis
interests, I understand it,
intereses yo yo lo entiendo a
surely if you had contacted me,
seguramente si me hubieras contactado
crazy, but we're not going to get into a
loquito pero que no vamos a entrar a una
discussion about that, I think
discusión de eso yo pienso que no
nothing would happen, it hasn't happened, I think
pasaría nada no ha pasado paso yo pienso
no, I think nothing would happen in
que no Yo pienso que no pasaría nada en
the sense that something when you
el sentido de que una cosa ya cuando
have millions of views, I'm sorry that it
tienes millones de visitas Lo siento que
's your privacy and that it hurts you, but if
sea tu intimidad y que te duela pero si
something that has millions of views,
una cosa que tiene millones de visitas
by much, I'm married that this doesn't matter
por much ha me caso que esto no importa
if you, if you're like if it's that you
si tú si tú es como si es que es que tú
tell me Look, they've killed 100
me dices Mira eh han matado a 100
people and I've killed one person already,
personas y yo he matado a una persona ya
but it doesn't matter, you know what I mean, I do
pero es que da igual sabes lo quier
n't think it's the same, but
decir no creo que sea lo mismo pero
well, we're not going to get into that, in that, I
bueno no vamos a entrar en ese en ese Te
'm comparing you, noea, it's not
estoy te estoy comparando para noea no
happened, it's not people, they have committed a
ha pasado no es gente han hecho un
crime and then you repeat the crime,
crimen y que tú luego repites el crimen
that's not happening, Tomy, Tomy, we're not going to
que no pas tomy tomy que no vamos a
get into that loop because I really
entrar a ese bucle porque de verdad que
understand you, okay, I respect you  and I
te entiendo vale que te respeto y que te
understand you, don't worry, no, I think
entiendo no te preocupes no yo yo pienso
one thing about the law, some moves
una cosa sobre la ley una movidas en
based on many things that have happened to us
base a muchas cosas que nos han pasado
here, but we're not going to discuss that
aquí pero que no vamos a discutir eso
because that's not the point, the point is, uh,
porque no es el punto el punto es eh
these conversations of yours with this
estas conversaciones tuyas Con esta
girl with Katy, these conversations about
chica con Katy estas conversaciones de
when they are, is it from once the
cuándo son es de una vez que ya ha
breakup has already happened or is it from before, no, let's see,
pasado la ruptura o es anterior no a ver
uh, these conversations come right
eh estas conversaciones son llegan justo
before the
antes de la
breakup, just before
ruptura justo antes
and before and it's and it's those conversations
y antes y es y es esas conversaciones
when he realized those
cuando él se dio cuenta de esas
conversations are everything that uh started
conversaciones es todo lo que eh empeso
the whole story, damn it, do you understand what they
toda la historia [__] entiendes es que
are and as a result of this, how are they
son y a raíz de esto cómo son
infidelity? So no,
infidelidad Entonces no
uh, let's see, I never saw this person
eh A ver yo nunca la la vi esta persona
so you understand why she lives in
para que entiendas porque ella vive en
Miami and I live in Madrid, it's
Miami y yo vivo en Madrid se ha sido
only been a few messages, okay. What happens is
solamente unos mensajes vale Qué pasa
that as a result of this, uh, they
que a raíz de esto eh ella se han
separated, okay. And then she began to
separado vale Y ella luego empezó a
realize that her husband had
darse cuenta que su marido le había
cheated on her with dozens of
puesto los cuernos con decenas de
women, that he had orias and threesomes in his
mujeres que hacía orias y tríos en su
company, the company that he had with
empresa la empresa que que tenía con con
her, that he had girlfriends, that he paid for
ella que tenía novias que le pagaba
cosmetic surgeries,
operaciones estéticas alquilares de
apartment rentals and that basically  cheated on her for
pisos y que básicamente le engañaba
years you know And that she
desde hace años entiendes Y esa eso ella
made it public and because she
lo ha hecho público y porque ella lo ha
made it public he got revenge on her he
hecho público él para vengarse a se ha
left the way he could with our
vado de la forma que podía con nuestras
Instagram conversations eh because that's
conversaciones de Instagram eh porque es
the only thing she has because I
lo único que tiene porque yo esta chica
never saw this girl in person you know [ __ ]
nunca la vi en persona entiendes hosti
So loico be clear he has
Entonces loico que ten claro él ha
taken he has gotten into her accounts
cogido se ha metido en sus cuentas
because he could get into her accounts
porque él podía meterse en sus cuentas
no and he has captured everything and he has started
no y ha ha capturado todo y ha empezado
publishing everything no no no no no no no no no
a publicar toda la no no no no no no no
no he went into her account one day he
no no no se puso en su cuenta él un día
took his wife's cell phone Yeah he had the
cogió el móvil de su mujer Ajá tenía el
code for her cell phone he saw the
código de su móvil vio las
conversations that a conversation of
conversaciones que una conversacion de
two days he took her cell phone to him and took pictures
dos días tomó su móvil a él y tomo fotos
of the cell phone
del móvil
Ah I mean he captures it from his cell phone okay
Ah o sea lo captura desde su móvil vale
but
pero
eh Now I ask myself a question I don't know
eh Ahora yo me hago una pregunta no sé
if you can answer me So if she does
si me sabrá responder Entonces si ella
n't end up flirting with you no she never
no llega a coquetear contigo no nunca se
found out I mean if she doesn't end up
enteró O sea si ella no llega a
flirting with you it doesn't occur to her
coquetear contigo no le da por por
that her husband
enterarse de que el marido también le
is also cheating on her that's that's
está poniendo los cuernos a ella eso es
the point let's see maybe one day one
eso es el punto a ver igual un día un
day He would have found out but  maybe not
día se Hubiera enterado pero igual no
because what you have to know is
porque ella lo que tienes que saber Es
that she since she was 15 16 years old she's been
que ella Desde que tiene 15 16 años está
with this man she lives in a house She's already
con este hombre vive en una casa Ya es
a girl who doesn't leave the house she
una chica que no sale de la casa que
's always recording videos
está todo el tiempo grabando vdeos
preparing her next videos and it's and it's
preparando sus próximos videos y es y es
him that travels a lot that he flirts for everything
él que él viaja mucho que liga por todo
that he has a double life She is a
que tiene el doble vida Ella es una
girl who well that that I thought that she
chica que pues que que que pensaba que a
told me that this man was that he
mí me decía que este hombre es que
was not only sexual that he was a
solamente no era sexual que era un
very good man who was very faithful because
hombre muy bueno que era muy fiel porque
he had not done anything with her sexually
él no hacía nada con ella sexualmente
for a long time and I told him at the
desde hace mucho tiempo y yo le dije al
beginning when I talked to him and I said No it
principio cuando hablé con él y dije No
's that he has other girlfriends and he tells me
es que tiene otras novias y él me dice
no no no no no no no He only has
no no no no no no no Él solamente tiene
eyes for me and you And you why did you
ojos para mí y tú Y tú por qué
suspect
sospechabas de
him because a man like him who
él porque porque un hombre como él que
is with a woman like her and who does
está con una mujer como ella y que que
n't touch him because no I don't know if you have
no le toca porque no no sé si habéis
seen the woman the woman is spectacular
visto la mujer la mujer es espectacular
okay there are two solutions either it's
vale to hay dos soluciones o es
important or okay it could be or he
importante o vale que puede ser o le
's cheating on her because when
está poniendo los cuernos porque cuando
a man cheats on his wife and
un hombre pone los cuernos a su mujer y
has sex with many other women
que tiene sexo con muchas otras mujeres
then he doesn't want to touch her anymore  his wife of course
pues ya no quiere tocar su mujer claro
arrives and is served of course if you There is
llega está servido claro sea si tú Hay
a very vulgar saying forgive me in the ch for what I'm
un dicho muy vulgar perdonad en el ch lo
going to say but there is a very
que voy a decir pero hay un dicho muy
vulgar saying that goes like if you eat it was when he
vulgar que es como si t comes era cuando
gets home well he comes already eaten no I
llega a casa pues ya viene cenado no O
mean like he's not hungry anymore and but of
sea en plan ya no tiene hambre y pero
course I mean the thing is that without
claro o sea la movida es que ella sin
knowing that he was also unfaithful to her What a
saber que él también le era infiel Qué
shame of a marriage No she without knowing that
pena de matrimonio No ella sin saber que
he was unfaithful was having
él le era infiel estaba teniendo
explicit conversations with you
conversaciones explícitas
yeah let's see This really started see this
contigo sí a ver Esto empezó a ver esto
started because the grp was going
realmente empezó porque la gración iba
terrible okay it was going terrible he had been in
fatal vale iba fatal él llevaba meses en
Venezuela for months okay And I started to get to know her
Venezuela vale Y yo la empezo a conocer
at a time where well they have been like that for
en un un momento donde pues llevan eso
two TR years where they never do anything they
dos TR años donde nunca hacen nada
just fight they only talk about
solamente pelean solamente hablan de
work and that's it okay And then Well at
trabajo y punto vale Y entonces Bueno
first she tells me no no I have I
ella al principio me dice no no yo tengo
have a partner I don't know how it is Okay but
tengo pareja no sé qué tal Bueno pero
well little by little we continued talking and it's
bueno poco a poco seguimos hablando y es
true that we have a lot of things in
verdad que tenemos un montón de cosas en
common Okay so well little by little
común Vale entonces bueno de poco a poco
we start flirting a little you know what I
vamos tonteando un poco sabes lo que yo
say yes you have chemistry you have you
decir sí tú tienes química tú tienes tú
have with her the chemistry that the husband
tienes con ella la química que el marido
however he no longer has with her they
sin embargo ya no tiene con ella ellos
have only the business and of course and
lo que tienen sol el negocio y claro y
I  and of course and I tell her I tell her let's see
yo y claro y yo le digo le digo a ver es
you have to get a divorce Because if
que tú te tienes que divorciar Porque si
at 30 you have such a bad reaction
con 30 años tienes una reación tan mala
[ __ ] You don't waste any more time in your life
[__] No pierdes más tiempo en tu vida
because we have a life what do you want to
porque tenemos una vida qué quieres
wait 35 40 years How good if a mu
esperar 35 40 años Qué buena si una mu
very good that eh Very good very good
muy bueno eso eh Muy buen muy buen
thought It's that also that it is
pensamiento Es que además que sí da
very sad when a marriage already because
mucha pena cuando un matrimonio ya por
of being married or having children or
el hecho de estar casado o tener hijos o
whatever you endure the relationship when in
lo que sea aguanta la relación cuando en
reality You would love to be messing around
realidad Te encantaría estar picando con
with other people Damn You're not going to
con otra gente [__] Que no vas a volver
live again live it like you want to live it
a vivir vívela como como quieres vivirla
and she was she told you that she felt
y ella estaba ella te decía que sentía
for
por
you sorry she she recognized some
ti perdón ella ella te reconocía algún
kind of feelings towards you or It
tipo de sentimientos hacia ti o
was only sexual No no Let's see quite the
Solamente era sexual No no A ver todo lo
opposite in the end the sexual became much
contrario al final el sexual llegó mucho
more to see sexual we have never seen each other
más a ver sexual nunca nos hemos visto
then m yes Well but the
entonces m sí Bueno pero la
conversations are I understand yes yes yes no
conversaciones son entiendo sí sí sí no
no but at the beginning she Really it's
no pero al principio ella Realmente es
like she fell a little in love with me Yeah because
como se enamoró un poco de mí Ajá porque
well I'm the second man that she has
pues soy el segundo hombre que ha
met in her life you understand of course
conocido en su vida entiendes claro
then for her er everything is new I am
entonces para ella er todo nuevo yo soy
a boy well we have a lot of things
un chico pues tenemos un montón de cosas
in common then  well And then
en común entonces bueno Y luego pues una
once she started to have a little bit of
vez que empezó a tener un poco de
always thinking about me calling me like she
siempre pensar en mí llamarme como no
couldn't and such Well then well
podía y tal Pues luego pues Viene un
the game comes up obviously because two
poco el juego no obviamente porque dos
adults send each other messages
personas adultas pues se mandan mensajes
there a little hot hot you know what I
ahí un poco hot hot sabes lo que quiero
mean and thank goodness because if I've been at 30
decir y menos mal porque si llevo con 30
years old I can't tell a girl what she would
años no puedo mandar a una chica lo que
like to do if there was someone
le gustaría hacer si esty hubiera deun
in my bed is that H I don't know something is wrong
en mi cama es que H no sé algo está mal
in my life no Also apart from one thing that I
en mi vida no Además aparte una cosa que
think is that the unfaithful one there is her
yo pienso es que ahí la infiel es ella
eh you no you don't have a partner I mean it's
eh tú no tú no tienes pareja o sea es
her no no Of course I don't have a partner I
ella no no Claro yo no tengo pareja Yo
'm single okay In any case In any
estoy soltero vale En todo caso En todo
case yes Look if we hadn't
caso si Fíjate que si no hubiéramos
discovered that the man was Satan
descubierto que el hombre era Satanás
okay I had said well eh obviously
vale yo había dicho pues eh obviamente
keichi wouldn't have had to send
keichi no hubiera tenido que mandar
these messages it was bad okay yes and I would have been
estos mensajes ha sido mal vale sí y yo
able to not flirt with a with a
hubiera podido no ligar con una con una
person who Tena that had a husband
persona que Tena que que tenía un marido
I would run away from him I recognized it without a problem you
eso yo lo huía reconocio sin problema
know that's what I mean what happens
sab es lo que quiero decir lo que pasa
is that I can't say this when the
es que yo no puedo decir esto cuando el
man eh cheated on her with
hombre eh le puso los cuernos con
many girls and you know  the worst of
muchísimas chicas y sabes lo peor de
all without a condom being able to infect her
todo sin condón pudiendo infectar a ella
with diseases that he was going to contract with
de enfermedades que iba a contratar con
other girls you know is that yesterday when I
otras chicas sabes es que yo ayer cuando
was watching the video I was like I don't
estaba viendo el vídeo me tío o sea no
know if I don't know if you are very into
sé si no sé si tú estás muy puesto en
gossip and all that But of course I saw the
los salseos y demás Pero claro yo vi el
video uh these days that we were
vídeo eh estos días que estuvimos
reacting to her video and seeing it
reaccionando al vídeo de ella y al verlo
with that edition with that dramatization And
con esa edición con esa dramatización Y
with those cuts I believed that it was
con esos cortes yo me creía que era
content but of course now knowing
contenido pero claro ahora conociéndote
you uh I'm starting to take this
a ti eh estoy empezando a tomarme esto
pretty seriously this is a
bastante en serio esto es una historia
true story no no no no that let's see I've been
real no no no no eso a ver yo llevo
creating videos for a year now for me Look I
creando vídeos desce un año a mí Mira
just discovered that the
acabo de descubrir que lo las cuentas de
gossip accounts existed I don't like
de chisme existía yo a mí no me gusta el
gossip
chisme
and I make my own content
y hago mi contenido
eh And my private life or I know for me that's
eh Y mi vida privada o se yo para mí eso
all new you know I'm involved in it I did
es todo nuevo Sabes Yo estoy metido ahí
n't want to be involved in this Well I'm already
no quería estar metido en esto Bueno ya
involved in this okay And I'm going to
estoy metido en esto vale Y yo voy a
defend my honor and I'm going to tell the
defender mi honor y voy a contar la
truth like I've always said okay
verdad como siempre lo he dicho vale Yo
In all my videos and since I create
en todos mis vídeos y desde que creo
videos I will never lie to my
video nunca voy a mentir a mis
followers never never never  I mean, the
seguidores nunca nunca nunca o sea yo el
day I lie to my followers,
día que que mienta a mis seguidores que
say something that isn't true, I'll delete all my
diga algo que no es eh borro todas mis
accounts because I'm not like that in
cuentas porque yo no soy así ni en la
real life or in the videos that I make. Okay, so
vida real ni en en los vídeos que hago
there, uh, I'll tell my whole
Vale entonces ahí eh yo cuento toda mi
version, okay, so that people
versión vale para que la gente pues pues
know because I'm involved in this,
lo sepa porque yo estoy mitido en esto
but Tomy, one thing is based on: You've
pero tomy una cosa en base Tú llevas más
known her for a long time, talking to her, you
tiempo conociéndola hablando con ella
've had many hours of conversation
has tenido muchas horas de conversación
with her to make sure you're 100% sure that you
con ella para asegurarnos al 100% tú
're completely convinced that what's
estás completamente convencido de que
happening is a
esto que está pasando Es una historia
real story, I mean, it can't be that it's
real o sea no puede ser que sea
their content and you're a
contenido de ellos dos y tú seas una
victim of their content. No, no,
víctima del contenido de ellos dos no no
look, trust me because I, uh, think
a ver confía en mí porque yo eh piensa
that this happened in June and since
que esto ha pasado en junio y yo desde
June I've only had a
junio con ella Solamente tengo una
friendly relationship with her, in fact, we never
relación amical de hecho nunca no nos
message each other. Not anymore because,
mandamos mensajes Ya no porque yo a
apart from this, there was like a breakup for
parte de esto hubo como una ruptura para
me, but nevertheless, I'm her
mí pero sin embargo yo ahora soy su
friend now and every day I can tell you
amigo y todos los días te puedo decir
that I've been supporting her, every
que yo he estado apoyándola todos los
day, every day she's compared me to a
días todos los días me ha comparo un
lot of things and I can tell you that
montón de cosas y te puedo decir que
this is not a joke, that's very
esto no es ninguna broma eso es muy
serious. Because in addition to  all this
grave Porque además de todo esta
infinity the man eh stole
infinidades el hombre eh le robaba
money invested in opaque companies okay he
dinero invertía en empresas opacas vale
invested a little for bought things without
invertía un poco por compraba cosas sin
telling her anything and he put the debts in the
decirle nada y le ponía las deudas en el
girl's name yes what we were
nombre de la chica sí lo que Estuvimos
seeing in the And why do you think she
viendo en el Y por qué cre que ella Por
Why do you think she makes the video like that with that
qué crees que hace el vídeo así con esa
like with that edition with that music is
así con esa edición con esa música se
recorded crying let's see because she has been a
graba llorando a ver porque ella es
content creator for 15 years
creadora de contenido desde 15 años
so Well, she tells
entonces Bueno pues ella ella cuenta su
her story okay But I can
su historia vale Pero yo te puedo
assure you that the story is exactly as it is that
asegurar que la historia es tal cual que
later she does it in a little more
luego ella lo haga de forma un poco más
dramatic way a little more like a
dramática un poco más como una creadora
content creator is something else Okay, I did
de contenido es otra cosa Vale yo el
n't even watch the whole video, the video I saw the
video ni lo vi entero el videoo vi el
moment where she talks about me but I didn't see the
momento donde habla de mí pero no vi la
time of the video because because when she
hora de video porque porque cuando lo
published it all this was already out and I
publico ya estaba todo esto fuera y yo
had other things to do So I didn't even
tenía otras cosas que hacer Entonces el
watch the video you know my video you
videoo ni lo vi sabes yo mi videoo lo
can watch it later okay Because my video
puedes ver luego vale Porque mi video
only lasts 17 minutes and you will see
solamente dura 17 minutos y yo vas a ver
that there is no H exaggeration I
que no hay ninguna H exageración yo
tell things as they are there is a little
cuento las cosas tal cual hay un poco de
music in the background but very low but that's it
música de fondo pero muy bajita pero ya
I don't  I'm there you know what
está yo no estoy ahí de sabes lo que
I mean about dramatization okay and a
quiero decir de dramatización vale e una
question the first conversation that I
pregunta la primera conversación que yo
was watching was yours with oso oso
estaba viendo era tuya con oso oso te
contacts you to threaten you in some
contacta a ti para amenazarte de alguna
way that's oso he contacts me after
forma eso es oso me me contacta después
this he threatens me he says are you
de esto me amenaza me dice estás
ready for all the people uh I know
preparado para que toda la gente Eh se
you're a bad person for having
que eres una mala persona por haber
hooked up with his wife these
ligado con su mujer esto esas
conversations when we see the
conversaciones cuando veamos luego el
video later those conversations yes I can
vídeo esas conversaciones sí las puedo
put them no That one yes you let me put it
poner no Esa sí me dejas ponerla
no well the uh Let's see I would tell you no
no bueno la eh A ver Yo te diría que no
because I don't want it to be any you
porque tampoco quiero que sea ninguna
know what I mean I tell you I'll tell
sabes lo que quiero decir yo te digo yo
you the content of this
te digo el contenido de esta
conversation without a problem He sends me a
conversación sin problema Él me manda un
message like this in June or rather when
mensaje cuá esto en junio o sea cuando
he contacts you it wasn't now but in
él te contacta no ha sido ahora sino en
June no no months ago Yeah months What's
junio no no hace meses Ajá meses Qué
happening why does he bring all
pasa que él por qué Por qué saca todo
this out now why has he leaked all this
esto ahora por qué ha filtrado todo esto
now because
ahora porque
keichi has attacked him to denounce
keichi la ha atacado a él para denunciar
all these years that they have cheated on him and
todos estos años que le han engañado y
he to get ahead now end of
él para avanzarse ahora finales de
October well he brought out what he had but
octubre pues ha sacado lo que tenía pero
if Katy hadn't done this
si Katy no lo hubiera hecho esto
surely he wouldn't have brought it out Of course
seguramente él no lo hubiera
yes  Katy would have taken it
sacado Claro si Katy lo hubiera llevado
too why do you think that she has
también por qué crees que que ella lo ha
made everything public because it was not
sacado todo al público porque no hacía
necessary she could have made a statement whatever because because because
falta podía haber hecho un comunicado lo
eh You do
que sea que porque porque porque eh Tú
n't know everything Well when you are 30
no sabes todo Pues cuando tú tienes 30
years old and you have spent 15 years with a man
años y has pasado 15 años con un hombre
and this man has cheated on you
y que este hombre te ha engañado de
financially sentimentally sexually
forma económica sentimental sexual
for many years you are destroyed I
durante muchos años tú eres destruido o
mean I can tell you that Katy this
sea yo te puedo decir que Katy este
summer has been a destroyed woman and I don't even
verano ha sido una mujer destruida y yo
know how she is still standing now eh Because the
ni sé como ahora sigue de pie eh Porque
truth is that I might have jumped
yo la verdad que igual me hubiera tirado
off a bridge I mean I'm telling you the truth
de un puente o sea te lo digo de verdad
because it has to be I mean I
porque tiene que ser O sea a mí me
was cheated on when I was 17 my first Noa cheated on me okay she cheated on me two three times with a boy and I had a really bad time I had a really bad time for months but imagine when the person who is your husband the only person you have known in your life has done it with many
en tu vida lo ha hecho con muchísimas
women for many years Wow it's
mujeres durante muchísimos años Wow es
horrible So she needs to get
horrible Entonces ella necesita sacar
everything she has out and let everyone
todo lo que tiene y que todo el mundo
know What kind of man is because
sepa Qué clase de hombre es porque ella
what she can't do is not say anything and
lo que no puede hacer es no decir nada y
people  she believes that this man is a
que la gente crea que este hombre es una
good person because that would kill him
buena persona porque eso le mataría
you understand and you have been by
entiendes y tú has estado estos meses al
her side these months every day every
lado de ella todos los días todos los
day we are talking we do not always
días estamos hablando no siempre
talk about this but almost every
hablamos de de esto pero casi todos los
day I discovered something new every day I
días descubrí algo nuevo todos los días
had more evidence witnesses because she
tenía más pruebas testigos porque
also had detectives you know what I mean I mean
también tuvo detectives sabes lo que
This goes far
quiero decir o sea Esto va va mucho más
beyond just gossip I mean that is
allá de de simplemente chisme o sea eso
there are lawyers who are involved
es hay hay abogados que están implicados
the best lawyers in the United States
los mejores abogados de Estados Unidos
that it is costing her A lot of money K Angel I know this
que le está costando Una pasta K Angel
is a very serious issue are you
se ahí es un tema muy serio estás
in love no no like I told you I
enamorado no no como le he dicho yo
never saw her You know I don't
nunca la vi Sabes Yo no
uh now we have a friendly relationship
eh ahora tenemos una relación amical
you know what happens I never saw her I mean that's why it
sabes lo que pasa nunca la vi o sea por
seems like nonsense to me But well
eso a mí me parece tonterías Pero bueno
he is the only thing she has
él es lo único que tiene para para en
against her these chats where silly
contra de ella estos chats donde tonte
Yes but do you intend to
Sí pero tienes intención de
uh something in the future no no because because
eh algo en un futuro no no porque porque
first point I live on the other side of the
primer punto Yo vivo en la otra punta
world I do not think I will go live in the United
del mundo no pienso ir a vivir en
States and and simply I now
Estados Unidos y y simplemente yo ahora
the truth is that I have more tendency to
la verdad que tengo más tendencia a
want to uh forget this whole story than anything
querer eh olvidar toda esta historia que
else however now I am her
otra cosa sin embargo yo ahora soy su
friend I am not going to leave her I am not going to
amigo no la voy a dejar no la voy a
leave her  thrown away or anything, I mean, I've
dejar al tirada ni nada o sea yo la he
supported her every day and she's always going to have
apoyo todos los días y siempre va a
my affection, that one day the
tener mi cariño que un día un día la
situation will change and we live in the same
situación cambiar y vivimos en el mismo
country and we get to know each other. Well, we
país y nos conozcamos Pues bien nos
have a drink but in person we don't
tomamos algo pero igual en persona no
like each other that's what I mean, I
nos gustamos es es lo que quiero decir o
mean, we're not kids here it's not because
sea aquí no somos niños no es porque
someone chats with you that you're going to
alguien t teas por por chat que te va a
like each other in person. So you don't have to
gustar en persona Entonces tampoco hay
imagine things and when he
que imaginarse cosas y cuando él te te
contacts you to threaten you, he threatens you with
contacta para amenazarte te amenaza con
something more than just publishing the conversations
algo más que publicar las conversaciones
or it just stays that way that he's
o o simplemente se queda en eso en que
going to
te va a
ridicule you. Let's see when he contacts me,
ridiculizar a ver él cuando me contacta
uh, basically. Well, I thought he was going to
eh básicamente Pues yo pensaba que iba a
make a video telling
hacer un video diciendo contando las
things, let's see, what he wanted to do is, uh,
cosas a ver él lo que quería hacer es eh
reproduce what happened to Tami, to, I
Reproducir lo que pasó a a tami para es
mean, create a ton of content so
decir crear un montón de contenido para
that people, uh, have Pit of him being
que la gente Eh tenga Pit de él que sea
the victim and that a lot of people start
la víctima y que mucha gente le empieza
following him, the same thing that happened to para, uh, at
a seguir lo mismo que pasó a para eh en
Christmas, he wanted the same thing and he said it to
Navidad él quería lo mismo y lo dijo a
Katy, okay? Why didn't he do it because that's
Katy vale Por qué no lo hizo porque eso
the question, why didn't he do it before
es la pregunta por qué no lo hizo antes
Katy started to get to know  all
que Katy empezara a a a conocer todos
these dark years because he doesn't earn
estos años eh oscuros porque él no gana
money he doesn't generate money all the
dinero él no genera dinero todo el
money is generated by Kit Kit is a girl
dinero lo genera kit kit es una chica
with 20 million followers on
con 20 millones de seguidores en en
YouTube and he since he is her husband 50% of
YouTube y él como es su marido 50% de
everything he earns he earns it So
todo lo que gana lo gana él Entonces
for him he told her I'm not going to sue you
para él él le dijo no te voy a denunciar
But all your life you're going to give me half
Pero toda tu vida me vas a dar la mitad
of your income from YouTube and she
de tus ingresos en YouTube y eso ella le
told him well okay because she didn't know what to
dijo bueno pues vale porque ya no sabía
do but that but that how does he do
qué hacer pero eso pero eso cómo hace
that is the worst of all is that a man
eso es lo peor de todo es que un hombre
who knows because at the time he was the only one
que sabe porque a la época era el único
who knew that he had cheated on his wife
que sabía que había ha engañado su mujer
for 4 years with many women
durante 4 años con muchísimas mujeres
for some private Instagram messages he
por unos mensajes de Instagram privado
is threatening her with this and he is
le está amenazando con esto y le está
telling her that of all her income from
diciendo que todos sus ingresos de
YouTube of her entire life he is going to give
Youtube de toda su vida le va a dar la
half to him you imagine the kind of
mitad a él te imaginas la clase de
person he is but let's see is that not to
persona que es pero a ver es que eso no
me no let's see based on what he
me eso no a ver él en base a qué le
demands that half of
exige que la mitad de los ingresos de
her income go to him based on what
ellas vayan para él en base a qué en
based on what law because he said that
base a qué ley por porque él decía que
everything they have built he has
todo lo que lo han construido lo ha
built together that he helped her
construido juntos que él le ayudó a
grow that he helped her  in the procedures I do
crecer que él le ayudó en las gestiones
n't know how you understand Oh because they are
no sé qué tal entiendes Oh porque están
married when you get divorced you have to
casados cuando tú divorcias tienes que
yes of course let's see I don't know how it will be in the United
sí claro a ver no sé cómo será en
States but of course I understand that
Estados Unidos pero claro entiendo que
here in Spain Well now they get divorced and
aquí en España Pues ahora se divorcian y
suddenly everything they have they have to
de repente todo lo que tengan lo tienen
divide but of course what you
que dividir pero claro ya lo que tú
earn once separated not what you earn
ganes una vez separado no lo que tú
once divorced No I mean
ganes una vez divorciado No o sea una
something that now divides what they have in
cosa que reparta ahora lo que tengan en
the bank now my and but what I
el banco ahora mis y pero é lo que le
was telling him oh what I was telling him is that YouTube
decía é lo que le decía es que YouTube
is like a company okay And this company
es como una empresa vale Y esta empresa
the YouTube account is already like a
la cuenta de Youtube de ya es como una
company and if they get divorced they have to
empresa y si divorcian la tienen que
divide it in two what
dividir en dos qué
jea no but it's crazy it's crazy
jea no pero es una locura es una locura
I told him better delete your
yo le he dicho mejor borras tu canal
YouTube channel before giving half to
YouTube antes que darle la mitad a
this guy do you understand or what a cheek this guy is no and
este entiendes oa que jeta el tío no y
when when he contacts you and says
cuando cuando él te contacta y te dice
Hey well I'm going to
Oye pues te voy a
expose you he is listening a little to the
exponer está escuchando un poco lo los
audios that you have told him but if you
audios que le has dicho pero si lo
want to comment on it what you
quieres comentar tú que es lo que tú le
answer him yes yes yes I tell him let's
respondes a él sí sí sí yo le digo a
see have you heard the sound
ver se te ha oido el sonido
tomy Yes yes
tomy Sí sí
calm down
tranquilo
my goodness
mía
and now
y
now very quietly I don't know
ahora ahora muy bajito no sé por
why now now now perfect tomy I
qué ahora ahora ahora perfecto tomy te
was asking you I'll repeat it again The
preguntaba te vuelvo a repetir La
question was when he told you well
pregunta era que cuando él te bueno
basically what did you answer to those
básicamente que le contestaste tú a esas
threats okay to these threats I
amenazas vale yo a est amenazas le
say to him eh It's not going away Sorry tomy it's
digo eh No se te va Perdona tomy se te
going away your sound is going away I don't know
va se te va el sonido no sé por
why now now now yes let's see if it
qué ahora ahora ahora sí a ver si se
stays yes yes no maybe it wasn't
queda sí sí no igual no estaba bien
plugged in well of course I say well those are
enchufado claro yo digo pues eso son
just messages I don't know how
solamente mensajes no sé qué tal
obviously it hasn't been cool well and I
obviamente no ha sido cool bueno y yo le
recognize it I mean if I have no
yo reconozco O sea si yo no tengo
problem recognizing my mistake and then I
problemas a reconocer mi error y luego
tell him if you want me eh make a
le digo si tú me quieres eh hacer un
video eh explaining things to get
víde eh explicando las cosas para
revenge Do it I tell him because I'm
vengarte Hazlo le digo porque yo mis
going to recognize my mistakes to my
errores los voy a reconocer a mis
followers without lying I'm not going to
seguidores sin mentir Yo no le voy a
tell him No it's not true Such I'm going to
decir No no es verdad Tal yo le voy a
tell him I have arrived with a married woman
decir he llegado con una mujer casada
without problem you know what I'm going to say because
sin problema saes lo que vo decir porque
in life eh someone who recognizes their
en la vida eh alguien que reconoce su
mistakes is someone you can
sus errores es alguien en quien puedes
trust you understand and we all make
confiar entiendes y todos hacemos
mistakes in the end it hasn't been a mistake in the
errores al final no ha sido un error al
end it has been a blessing take clear
final ha sido una bendición toma claro
No but  besides it's like I'm telling you, I mean,
No pero aparte es como te digo o sea
for me
para mí la infidelidad la está
she's committing the infidelity, you're single, let's see if
cometiendo ella tú está soltero a ver si
he were your friend or something, yes, but if he
él fuera tu amigo o algo sí pero si él
's not your friend, you don't know him. You're welcome, what do I tell
no es tu amigo no lo conoces De nada tú
you? If I had a friend like that,
que te digo si tuviera un amigo así
of course, of course, and if I had a friend like that, I would
claro claro y si yo tuviera un amigo así
say to him. Look, man, he can't be your friend
le diría Mira tío no puede ser tu amigo
because of what you do. No, no, it's not like it can't
porque lo que haces No no es que no
be, I couldn't have a friend. That
puede ser yo no podría tener amigo Así
's tremendous, and the one who tells you because there, I
es tremendo y el que te dice porque ahí
only heard what you
solamente escuchado lo que tú le
answer. No, then he doesn't, he doesn't
contestas No Ah ahí luego él no me no me
tell me anything, he doesn't answer me, he doesn't tell you
dice nada no me contesta ya no te dice
anything anymore, I mean, he publishes
más nada o sea publica las
your conversations with her and no, no, no, no,
conversaciones tuyas con ella y no no no
no, because this was in June, eh. He
no no no porque esto era en junio eh Él
waits 4 months to publish things.
espera 4 meses para publicar las cosas
Ah, it's true, of course, I mean, he stays
Ah Es verdad claro o sea é se queda
quiet, he keeps it to himself, and then he publishes
callado se lo guarda y luego lo publica
everything. Of course, of course, and why do you publish
todo Claro claro y por qué publicas las
your conversations with him
conversaciones tuyas con él
too, well, I don't know why, because I don't know
también pues no sé porque porque no sé
why he wants to see that everything is
porque quiere quiere ver que todo es
true, I don't know what when I don't have
verdad no sé qué cuando yo no tengo
any problem, look, what I'm not going to
ningún problema yo mira lo que no voy a
say is, you're not a con. You're rigged,
decir es No estás conon Estás trucadas
just like I say.  no no I take responsibility for everything I do
tal yo digo no no yo asumo todo lo que
you know what I mean in
hago sabes lo que quiero decir en la
life you have to take responsibility for all your actions you
vida hay que asumir todos ts actos los
take responsibility and that's it no no but apart from what
asumes y ya está no no pero aparte que
you stop the most let's say Let's see you You have been
lo tu pares la más digamos A ver tú Tú
splashed because you have had
te has visto salpicado porque has tenido
that virtual roll with this girl But
ese rollete virtual con esta chica Pero
in the end that is the family it is Katti's
al final eso es la familia es de katti
the business problems and everything I mean
los problemas empresariales y todo o sea
the big move is theirs and they have
la movida gorda la tienen ellos y tienen
a huge move because see let's see I
una movida gordísima porque ver a ver yo
am eh I this does not affect me
yo estoy eh yo a mí esto no me afecta
really it does not affect me I have even gained
realment no me afecta Hasta he ganado
thousands of followers in this story
miles de seguidores en esta historia
Because because her followers are
Porque porque los seguidores de ella
now following me all So
ahora me están siguiendo todos Entonces
I could really say that that that that I am
yo realmente podría decir que que que
not coming out badly in this story but
que que no salgo mal esta historia pero
I do not like being involved like this I do not
a mí no me gusta estar metido así no me
like seeing my conversations you understand
gusta ver mis conversaciones entiendes
Yes yes I understand you I do not want to be in
Sí sí te entiendo yo no quiero estar en
the crossfire of the two well you are already
el crossfire de los dos pues ya estás
in you know No yes yes I am already in
dentro lo sabes No sí sí Ya estoy dentro
and then there is another girl also one
y luego hay otra chica también que una
of her lovers also who is in the
de sus amentes también que está en el
crossfire
crossfire
Yes but she has come out as denying it no I mean
Sí pero ella ha salido como negándolo no
she says that that no that she does
O sea ella dice que que no que ella sí
work but that she has not  done nothing
que trabaja pero que no ha hecho nada
with him yet but if you watch my video you'll see
con él ya pero si ves mi videoo verás
that it's not like that you know what I
que no que no es así sabes lo que quiero
mean because she she worked
decir porque ella ella trabajaba desde
with him for 4 years Yeah Okay and and the
hace 4 años con él Ajá Vale y y la
company belonged to both of them it was Keith's and her
empresa era de los dos era de keit y del
husband's and Katy never knew that she
marido y Katy nunca sabía que ella
worked with her husband and the husband
trabajaba con el marido y el marido
pressured the employees to never
presionaba las empleadas para nunca
say that they worked together and he
decir que le que trabaja juntos y él le
paid for her equipment computers cameras
pagaba equipamientos ordenadores cámaras
so that she could start creating content and
para que ya empezara a crear contenido y
the girl is a model she was an
la chica es un modelo era un modelo de
18 year old model at the time he is
18 años a la época él tiene
34 you know and when they
34 entiendes y ella cuando ellos han se
separated and they made it official a
han separado y lo han hecho oficial una
week later this girl uh puts
semana después esta chica eh pone en su
a statement on her Instagram saying that
Instagram un comunicado diciendo que por
finally uh she has made the decision to
fin eh ha tomado la decisión de de
work with the guy's company yeah because
trabajar con la empresa del chico sí car
her story her story is not coherent
su historia su historia no es coherente
because if you had been working
porque si tú llevabas 4 años trabajando
with this guy for 4 years as you have said as
con este chico como tú lo has dicho como
she has defended herself Why did you make a
ella se ha defendido Por qué haces un
statement a few months ago saying that
comunicado hace unos meses diciendo que
and the worst of all is that when she saw
y lo peor de todo es que cuando ha visto
the controversy that was beginning to be created
la polémica que que empezaba a crearse
uh a month later she said I'm leaving the
eh un mes después ha dicho me voy de la
company because I no longer  wants to be involved
empresa porque ya no quiere estar metido
in this and in the end she is the
en esto y al final lo está metido la
poor thing, you won't see it eh I'll tell you something
pobre no verás tú eh Te digo una cosa
that's coming to my
que se me está viniendo a la
head Katy publishes
cabeza Katy publica conversaciones
intimate conversations between an osprey and this
íntimas entre oso y esta
girl so those conversations are
chica entonces esas conversaciones son
real yes yes yes no I'm not telling you that they
reales sí sí sí no yo no te digo que no
are not real but that that is also the
sean reales pero eso eso también es el
problem is that instead of saying
problema es que ella en lugar de decir
yes I had a relationship with him I
sí tuve una relación con él me
regret it a lot I was very young eh For
arrepiento mucho era muy joven eh Para
me he promised to make me a
mí él me prometía de hacerme una
star to make me grow just like he
estrella de hacerme crecer igual que lo
did with Kat he let me deceive I mean you
hizo con Kat me dejó engañar O sea tú
say this That's it you don't have to
dices esto Ya está no tienes que
try to lie because besides her
intentar de mentir porque además e ella
trying to deny the facts she does it
intentando de negar los hechos lo hace
wrong and her story is not
mal y su historia no es nada
coherent at all That's why I say that sometimes it's
coherente Por eso digo que a veces es
better to admit when you're wrong than to
mejor reconocer cuando te equivocas que
try eh fix everything because you
intentar eh arreglar todo porque lo
do it wrong and a blanket is seen you know what I
haces mal y una mantia se ve sabes lo
mean Hey are you some
que quiero decir Oye le tienes algún
kind of afraid of this
tipo de miedo a este
boy Not of me I'm not afraid
chico No a mí Yo no tengo ningún miedo
of him I mean he He should be afraid
de de él o sea él Él debería tener miedo
of justice in the United States and in
de la justicia en Estados Unidos y en
Mexico in Venezuela where he lives okay
México en Venezuela donde vive vale
because because he has leaked
porque porque él ha filtrado
conversations and and what happens is that he  He
conversaciones y y lo que pasa es que él
also has sexual photos because
también tiene fotos eh sexuales porque
obviously he was her husband and what he
obviamente era un era su marido y él lo
has threatened is to have
que ha amenazado es de hacer filtrar
all of this leaked on the internet and that is very
todo esto en la en internet y eso es muy
very serious that could be he could go
muy grave eso podría ser podría ir
to jail for many years So he doesn't
muchos años en la cárcel Entonces él no
have to be afraid of me or not No he
tiene que tener miedo de mí o no No él
has to be afraid of what he's
tiene que tener miedo de lo que está
doing and also of all the debts
haciendo y también de todas las deudas
that he has that he has contracted in the
que que tiene que ha contratado en
United States because that is fraud okay
Estados Unidos porque eso es estafa vale
he has been scamming his wife because
él ha estado estafando su mujer porque
you can't contract debts without
tú no puedes contratar deudas sin
telling your wife so there are many
decirlo a tu mujer entonces hay muchos
issues he is is in Deep sheet what we
temas él está está en Deep sheet cu
say in English okay he eh is going to have
decimos en inglés vale él eh va a tener
many problems and I am one of the
muchos problemas y yo soy uno de los
last the only thing that I put myself and I
últimos lo único que yo me pongo y yo
intervene and I make my video because he
intervengo y yo hago mi video porque él
has attacked me he could make a
se ha atacado a mí él podía hacer un
video saying Kat Angel has had eh
video diciendo Kat Angel ha tenido eh
erotic messages eh boys with a
mensajes eh eh erótic chicos con un
boy I don't know what then Well he
chico no sé qué entonces Bueno pues lo
did it wrong too eh Well I [ __ ] eh
hizo mal también eh Bueno yo me follé eh
half of Latin America but she
la mitad de latinoamérica pero ella
sent a message to a boy from Spain
mandó un mensajes a un chico de España
okay she could do that without a problem
vale eso lo podía hacer sin problema
but from the moment she leaked my
pero a partir del momento que filtro mis
conversations she attacked me  And if he
conversaciones a mí me atacó Y si a mí
attacks me, I'll defend myself, you know? I mean,
me ataca yo me defiendo entiendes O sea
she has a firm idea that she's
ella tiene pensamiento en firme de que
going to go all out, no. I mean, she's not going to back down, she's going to report him for having, I mean, this is proven to be the threat to publish intimate photos of her. Of course because when he has left his tiktok, he says that he has, he puts in the
tiktok él dice que tiene él pone en las
Stories that he has 48 hours to
Stories que tiene 48 horas que tiel para
apologize publicly and if he doesn't
pedirle disculpa públicamente y si no lo
do it, he
hace él
uh takes out everything else that he has
eh saca todo lo que lo demás que le
left, how strong, man, well, that is very
queda qué fuerte tío pues eso es muy
serious, I mean, yes, it can be very serious,
grave o sea eso sí lo puede es muy grave
of course, but he, you know, he believes, let's see, he
claro pero él él sabes que cree a ver él
's not the smartest guy in the world,
no es el chico más inteligente del mundo
obviously, he believes that because he did it
obviamente él cree que por lo ha hecho
with another cell phone, with I don't know what, with noal,
con otro móvil con no sé qué con noal
that they won't go away, they will not track him, but it's
que no se van no le van a rastrear pero
that, but it's that it is not like that, be you, the
es que pero es que no es así sea tú la
police, uh, digital, there they can contact
policía eh digital ahí pueden contactar
meta, they can contact YouTube, they
con meta pueden contactar con YouTube
can contact the
pueden contactar con los proveedores de
VPN providers to find out exactly where and who has
VPN para saber exactamente dónde y Quién
used the devices that they have
ha utilizado los dispositivos que han
done, I mean, it is very stupid, I mean, it's not
hecho o sea es es muy tonto o sea no te
worth it to you, my This yes, yes, he
merece la pena mi Esto sí sí sí la ha
screwed up but well and she is
cagado pero bien y ella está
completely  firm or rather because maybe
completamente firme o sea porque A lo
when everything cools down And you talk
mejor cuando todo se enfríe Y se habla
to her or whatever then she
con ella o lo que sea luego ella se
backs down a little and says Okay well it makes me feel
achanta un poco Y dice Bueno Va pues me
sorry I'm not going to
da pena no lo
report him no no no because she can you
denuncio no no no porque ella te
imagine what he's done to her she'll never leave
imaginas lo que le ha hecho ella nunca
she'll never back down she'll go after him He's going to
se va nunca va a backd ella le va Le va
go after her because on top of that now she
a ir por todo porque ella además ahora
has to pay the debts that he
como tiene que pagar las deudas que él
contracted because the debts are in
contrató porque las deudas están en los
both of their names she's also she's
nombres de los dos ella también está
in [ __ ] and also in the
está en la [__] y además en el
divorce he asks her that he says in the
divorcio él le pide que él dice en el
divorce that he can't uh how do you say he can't
divorcio que no puede eh Cómo se dice no
support himself because he doesn't have
puede mantenerse solo porque no tiene
a source of income okay And
una fuente de ingreso vale Y que
then she I don't know what the
entonces ella no sé cómo se llama el
legal term is called but that she will have to
término legal pero que ella le deberá
give him alimony for her entire life he's what she
dar una pensión toda su vida él es lo
's trying to I mean the jerk with the
que está intentando o sea el morro del
name kills you that they screw you no yes yes yes yes
nombre mueta que te cagan no sí sí sí sí
but what's happening tomorrow he's going to release a
pero qué pasa que mañana va a sacar un
vde Dallas review that Dallas review has
vde Dallas review que Dallas review ha
been talking to this man I don't know
estado hablando con este hombre no sé
how long that this man has been able to
cuánto tiempo que este hombre le ha pod
tell him what he wanted for Dallas and
ido decir lo que le quería a Dallas y
Dallas is going to be his video but I'm telling you
Dallas va a ser su video pero yo te digo
that this video is going to be  [ __ ] you know
que este video va a ser bullshit sabes
what I mean No I don't know what that
lo que quiero decir No no sé qué
means
significa
it's going to be It's going to be all lies it's going to
eso va a ser Va a ser toda mentira va a
be [ __ ] it's the [ __ ] of the
ser bullshit es la la [__] de de de la
cow you know of course let's see of course he will have
vaca sabes claro a ver claro él habrá
told whatever he wanted to tell and and I do
contado lo que haya querido contar y y
n't know the truth I mean eh I don't know what will
no lo sé la verdad O sea eh No sé qué
come out of there the truth I don't know when it gets
saldrá de ahí la verdad no sé cuandoo se
up I don't know what he will say but of course
sube no sé qué es lo que dirá pero claro
he is obviously not going to say Hey
él evidentemente é no va a decir Oye
well I have threatened him with photographs or
pues le he amenazado con fotografías o
not I mean I imagine that he will try to
no O sea me imagino que le intentará
save himself no and and he will put you in a bad mood of
salvarse no y y te pondrá a ti verde cl
course let's see he's going to say No no it's
claro se a ver él va a decir No no es
that someone here my cell phone and I publish it I
que alguien aquí mi móvil y lo publico o
mean things that nobody is going to believe but
sea cosas que nadie se va a creer pero
it's what he would say officially
es lo que él diría de forma oficial
because he can't say yes yes it's me who
porque él no puede decir sí sí soy yo
has
que ha
left this because he goes to jail
quedado esto porque va a la cárcel
directly to say that If he is going to say
directamente dec eso Si él va a decir
that Dallas is going to cut him off
eso el Dallas le va a meter que corte
that he's freaking out I mean Dallas is not leaving I don't know Well I hope so I
que flipa o sea el Dallas no se va no se
hope so but that's not the
Pues eso espero Eso espero pero no es la
impression that I got Because there was
impresión que me que me ha dado Porque
no doubt well well I
habado ninguna duda pues pues yo eso
hope so because for me  Dalas has already
espero porque para mí Dalas ya lo ha
screwed up when I criticize alas
cagado cuando cuando critico a alas
sicora okay I made a Twitch
sicora vale yo hice un un Twitch
defending alas sicora eh I don't like
defendiendo a alas sicora eh No me gusta
what he's done very much So I hope
mucho lo que ha hecho Entonces espero
that he doesn't let himself be fooled by
que que que no se deja engañar por por
this man no no no no if this
este hombre no no no no si empieza este
man starts saying things like that I'll tell you that I'm
hombre a decir así cosas así ya te digo
sure he won't Also, the
yo que seguro que no Además a mí la
impression that he gave me in the tweet
impresión que me ha dado en el tweet
eh well now we could start
Eh bueno ya ya podríamos entrar en
debating what you said about how you didn't
debatir eso que has dicho de que no te
like that Lia sicora was criticized,
ha gustado que se critique a Lia sicora
for example, if I agree
yo ahí por ejemplo si estoy de acuerdo
with the d or rather what Lia sicora did, I mean I don't
con el d o sea lo que hizo Lia sicora o
know what you don't agree with
sea no sé en que no estás de acuerdo con
but if you want we can leave it for another
eso pero si quieres lo dejamos para otro
day but if this guy doesn't No but I'll
día pero si este tipo no No pero yo a
see Just to tell you
ver Solamente para decirte
eh that pen which is terrible but she doesn't deserve
eh que pen cual fatal pero no se merece
all the bullying eh on a scale like that She
todo el bullying eh a una escala así Eso
doesn't deserve it because she's a
no se lo merece porque es una chica de
20 year old girl she kissed another guy with
20 años se ha dado un beso con otro con
another guy in a nightclub you know badly but
otro chico en discoteca mal sabes pero
nobody deserves the reci Because if the
nadie se merece el reci Porque si la
girl kills herself no no but listen to me if the
chica se mata no no pero escúchame si la
girl  she kills herself she puts a rope around her
chica se mata se pone una cuerda en el
neck and kills herself because of all the bullying she
cuello y se mata por todo el bullying
's received you know what happens that all
que ha recibido sabes qué pasa que toda
these people who have bullied her
esta gente que le ha hecho el bullying
feel stupid and I'm telling you this
se siente tonto y te lo y te lo digo de
because my best friend when she was 20
verdad porque a mí mi mejor amiga con 20
years old put the rope around her
años se puso la cuerda alrededor del
neck and that's why I defended elcora
cuello y yo por eso defendí elcora
because it disgusted me to see the
porque a mí me daba asco de ver la la
reaction those are extreme yes it's
reacción esos son extremos sí que es
true that there are situations in which you do
verdad que hay situaciones en las que tú
n't know how someone is You never
no sabes cómo está alguien Tú nunca
know how someone is or whatever
sabes cómo está alguien o lo que sea
but let's see one but I talked I talked
pero a ver una pero yo hablé yo hablé
to her girl because I I told her
con ella chicora porque yo yo le dije
Hey how are you And you know what she told me she
Oye cómo estás Y sabes lo que me contó
told me that she was afraid to go out
me contó que ella tenía miedo de salir
on the street that she didn't do
por la por en la calle que ella no hacía
anything that she didn't eat she on her
nada que ella no comía ella en su
Instagram only posts photos and such and
Instagram solamente pone fotos y tal y
videos of her dancing and such But that's
videos de ella bailando Y tal Pero eso
a
es una
facade she has no empathy but let's
fachada no tiene ninguna empatía pero a
see that's a whole other debate Tomy if she
ver eso es otro debate aparte tomy que
wants we can do it but basically
si quiere lo hacemos per básicamente si
if a girl as famous as Lía sicora
si una chica tan famosa como Lía sicora
hooks up with other
se enrolla en plena con otros chicos
famous guys and on top of that she has a boyfriend then look at
famosos y encima Tiene novio pues a ver
the channels here  gossip and here all
aquí los canales de salseo y aquí todo
the gossip And all the
el chisme Y todos los medios de
media is going to comment and it's not going to
comunicación van a comentar y no va a
be good man if you're telling me
ser bueno hombre si me estás diciendo
that someone takes her and insults her humiliates her
que alguien coge y la insulta la humilla
throws stones or something like that then I'm telling you
la pedrea o algo de eso pues ya te digo
no but what buuuut yes
yo que no pero lo que perooo que sí que
the gossip is going to gossip to me Well then let
va a chisme a mí el chisme Bueno pues
the gossip go on for a few days
que tenga el chisme durante unos días
but for 40 months I continue receiving
pero que 4ro meses siga recibiendo
bullying every day for something I've
buling todos los días por algo que he
done for months in a final of a
hecho cu meses en una final de una
reaction over a kiss it doesn't seem right to me
reación por un beso no me parece bien ya
already but the Dallas video was two
ya pero el vídeo de Dallas fue a los dos
or three days ago it wasn't for four months there are
o TR días no fue a los cu meses ya hay
people today yes but Dallas in his video
gente de hoy sí pero Dallas en su vdeo
was starting to delay the whole life of deas
empezaba a retrasar toda la vida deas
sicora Making baseless theories
sicora Haciendo teorías sin fundamiento
without arguments and I This video was
sin argumentos y yo Este vídeo lo
denied by the era I dismissed him Point by
desmentía la época lo despí Punto por
point because a person eh who has
punto porque una persona eh que tiene
clear ideas cannot eh Can't
las ideas claras no puede eh No puede
agree with what you say in
estar de acuerdo con lo que dic daras en
the videos because there is no
los vídeos porque no hay ninguna
argument he looks at things Looks at
argumentación él mira cosas Mira cosas
superficial things like she went with this
superficiales como a ha ido con este
guy and then he  gone with this guy and
chico y luego ha ido con este chico y se
makes up theories Okay but there's no
hace teorías Vale pero no hay ninguna
valid argument you understand what I'm
argumentación vlida entiendes lo que
saying yeah but let's see the main theory
digo sí pero a ver la teoría principal
of that video the first thing I think was just
de ese vídeo lo primero que creo que era
another video more humorous than anything else
un vídeo más más humorístico que otra
and in the end the culprit of the
cosa y al final son la culpable de la
story is her she's the one who
historia es ella que es la que pone los
cheats on the other guy and in the end the
cuernos al otro chico y al final la
main theory of the video if I
teoría principal del vídeo si mal no
remember correctly was that Jonathan did
recuerdo era que al Jonathan pues como
n't like him that much or rather a person
que no lo quería mucho o sea una persona
who turns him on plus with these
que le pone los cueros además con los
two twins who were here the other day
dos gemelos estos que el otro día
and that he laughed at the
estuvieron aquí y que que se Río del
boy Or rather the sicora mess Uh yes she's
chaval O sea la lía sicora Eh sí está
suffering a lot of bullying now and people
sufriendo ahora mucho Bullying y que se
laughing at her or whatever but she didn't
rían de ella o lo que sea pero no le
care that they were laughing at the boy
importó que se rieran del Muchacho
because she was she was laughing at the
porque te estaba se estaba riendo del
boy throughout the club and the whole
muchacho en toda la discoteca y que toda
club but it's you but it's
la discoteca se pero es que tú pero es
you don't know because she said that
que tú no lo sabes porque ella dijo que
the relationship was over and and he
la reación se había acabada y y él
said it too then But
también lo dijo entonces Pero eso eso
who believes that But but if they
quién se lo cree Pero pero si ellos te
tell you you can't say no no and he
lo dicen tú no puedes decir no no y él
was obviously sad about one thing
obviamente estaba triste por una cosa
but but it's that it's  Their private life you
pero pero es que es la vida Privada de
understand Yes yes and he and she says
ellos entiendes Sí sí y él y ella dice
that you have not cheated on her Well you have to
que no le has puesto los cuernos Pues
believe them if both
que hay que creerlos si los dos lo
say so already Well you have to believe it people have
dicen ya Bueno hay que creerlo la gente
people have freedom of course it's
tiene la gente tiene libertad claro es
another topic but people have the
otro tema pero que la gente tiene la
freedom to think what they want but
libertad de pensar lo que quiera pero
I personally did not see man if you
que yo personalmente no vi hombre si me
had told me another video but
hubieras dicho otro vídeo pero
precisely the video of dalan I did not see it
precisamente el vídeo de dalan no lo vi
as if it were a crushing to her
yo como que fuera un machaque a ella un
bullying or anything like that I saw it as a
bullying ni nada por el estilo lo vi una
criticism but you start to say that she takes
crítica per empiezas a decir que ella se
advantage of all the men she
aprovecha de todos los hombres con quién
is with to grow in social networks and
está para crecer en las redes sociales y
that you prove it by A + B it does not
que lo demuestras por a+ B a mí no me
seem right to me because no it is not like that but
parece bien porque que no no es así pero
I have that debate with other people
ese debate lo tengo yo con otra gente
who even also e well This is a
que incluso también e bueno Esto es una
long personal story that I have
historia larga personal que que tengo
that debate in another place because I
ese debate en otro sitio porque yo
also have said it about many people hey well
también lo he dicho de mucha gente oye
this person has become famous for
pues esta persona se ha hecho famosa por
being with this one just like there are people like
estar con este igual que hay gente como
for example Juan Guarnizo who has
por ejemplo Juan guarnizo que se ha
become famous for being with Ari but it
hecho famoso por estar con Ari pero es
seems that realities bother
que parece que las realidades molestan
let's see if the girls have boosted
vamos a ver si las chicas ha impulsado
being with chic  listen to me listen to me take
estando con chic escúchame escúchame haz
my advice l sicora Eh she had nothing to
mi caso l sicora Eh no tenía nada de
gain by getting in touch with Zlatá
ganar en ponerse en relación con zlatá
because she already had her brand made eh
porque ya tenía su marca hecha eh la
half of her audience are men who
mitad de su público es hombres que la
see her as super pretty who might like to
ven super guapa que igual le gustarían
be with her who are in love with
estar con ellas que están enamorados de
her when she puts on a sentence and
ella cuando ella se pone una oración y
makes it public it might hurt her more
lo hace pública igual le perjudica más
than that her and sicora grew a lot I mean she's
que eso ella y sicora crecía un montón o
a pretty girl who does Gaming
sea es una chica guapa que hace Gaming
who does Twitch she has it all I mean she did
que hace Twitch lo tiene todo O sea ella
n't need anyone to grow so the fact that
no necesitaba nadie para crecer entonces
she grew at the same time
que ella haya crecido al mismo tiempo
that she's been with a partner Well
que ha estado con una pareja Pues bien
but it's not because of that I mean she has a
pero no es por eso o sea ella tiene
lot of potential and I've done very well and
mucho potencial y lo he hecho muy bien y
I sicora I've never seen it not even in my
yo le sicora nunca la he visto ni en mi
friend I see everything from one point of
amiga yo lo veo todo de un punto de
view and outside but what I don't
vista e fuera pero a mí lo que no me
like is the injustice you know you have to be
gusta es la injusticia sabes hay que ser
tough as you have to be tough but you also
duro como hay que ser duro pero también
have to see things from a distance and I
hay que ver las cosas con distancia y yo
think that sometimes on tiktok on YouTube on
creo que a veces en tiktok en YouTube en
Twitch people are so head
Twitch la gente está tan la cabeza
stuck in their hole that they forget some
metida en su hueco que olvida algunos
very important values ​​and above all to
valores muy importantes y sobre todo de
keep a cool head and take  distance
tener la cabeza fría y tomar distancia
on things to be able to analyze
sobre las cosas para poder analizar las
things intelligently what happens tomy
cosas con inteligencia lo que pasa tomy
is that I think that's where the one who skips
es que yo creo que ahí la que se salta
the values ​​​​elas cor hooking up with
los valores elas cor enrollándose con
another person in a nightclub But you but you
otro en una discoteca Pero tú pero tú
but you never put the cuos on
pero tú nunca te pusiste los cuos a
anyone man of course everyone the
nadie hombre claro todo el mundo los
cuos on everyone but of course but if
cuos a todo el mundo pero claro pero si
I am viral and I am famous and it goes viral
soy viral y soy famoso y se hace viral
that I have cheated on my
que le he puesto los cuernos a a mi
girlfriend because I did it in a
novia porque lo he hecho en una
nightclub then I will have to eat the
discoteca pues me tendré que comer las
criticism okay Yes but yes if the two of them
críticas vale Sí pero si si los dos te
tell you that the thing is that the two of them
dicen que la cosa es que los dos han
said that they were no longer together at the
dicho que ya no estaban juntos a el
time that he still had feelings
momento que él seguía con sentimientos
for her yes he was sad to
por ella sí que él ha estado triste de
see that shortly after she was kissing another
ver que poco después estaba besando otro
boy Yeah but if the two of them say that they are not
chico Sí pero si los dos dicen que no
together we don't then yes Yes you
están juntos nosotros no pues sí Sí
are together it's just that it's impossible Well
estáis juntos es que es imposible Bueno
I think that was a little bit the way out
yo creo que eso fue un poquito la salida
But then you have more empathy with
Pero entonces tú tienes más empatía con
Lia than with him no no no no no no that's it that
Lia que con él no no no no que va que va
I feel that he was sad
que que yo siento que él estaba triste
first he was sad about the breakup and
primero él estaba triste de la ruptura y
then he was sad to see that she was hooking up
luego estaba triste de ver que se liaba
with the other boy obviously I have
con el otro chico yo obviamente tengo
a lot of empathy for him you know  that's what I
mucha empatía por él sab es lo que
want to say, I mean, I have empathy for
quiero decir o sea yo tengo empatía por
everyone, I'm not here, I have empathy for
todos yo no estoy yo tengo empatía por
Jonathan and for Yasora, because they're different,
Jonathan y por yasora poraz es distintas
but what I don't like is if you
pero a mí lo que no me gusta sea si me
knew me. It's that I don't like uh
conocerías Es que a mí no me gusta eh
hurting people. Or in fact, the
hacer daño a la gente O de hecho la
complaint that I'm going to make, the creators, I
denuncia que voy a hacer los creadores
make it uh without wanting to do it, but I
la hago eh sin querer hacerla pero la
do it to send a message, you know, to
hago para mandar un mensaje sabes para
send a message to all those tiktokers
mandar un mensaje a todos esos tiktokers
that when they're going to publish
que cuando van a publicar conversaciones
private conversations about me, you know, or anyone else, let them
privadas de mí de ti o de cualquier
know the damage they do and let them
persona que sepan el daño que hacen y
know that there are
que sepan que a los actos Hay
consequences for their actions, that's why I do it because otherwise I wouldn't do it because I do
consecuencias por eso lo hago porque si
n't like
no no lo haría porque a mí no me gusta
uh [ __ ] people, you know, I'm not like that.
eh [__] personas sabes yo no soy así A
Who have you reported? They know each other, they're
quién has denunciado se conocen son
known, I mean, who are you going to report?
conocidos o sea quién vas a denunciar
Well, I didn't know them, but I can
buenoo yo no les conocía pero te puedo
tell you the names because I have the
decir los nombres porque ahí tengo las
folders all made. Let's see, tell me, let's see
carpetas todas hechas a ver dime a ver
if it doesn't sound right. Okay, Castellanos,
si no suena vale al Castellanos
Yasen, Carmin, Sas, Michel, and Vargas, Yulis,
yasen carmin Sas Michel y Vargas yulis
are the five that I'm going to report tomorrow,
son los cinco que voy a denunciar mañana
well, I have no idea. Thank goodness I got away with it,
pues ni idea Menos mal que me he Librado
uh, well, listen to me, from now on, you  Do you
eh buen escúchame a partir de ahora tú
think that bear will see this interview that
crees que oso verá esta entrevista que
you have done and tell you something what
tú has hecho y te dirá algo qué
interview this talk that we have had
entrevista esta charla que hemos tenido
no because this talk when you see my
no porque esta charla cuando tú veras mi
video this talk is nothing I mean there is
vídeo esta charla no es nada O sea no
nothing that I don't say in my YouTube video
hay nada que no diga en mi vídeo YouTube
Ah okay it's true because you have uploaded a
Ah vale es verdad porque has sube un
video I mean is there something that you have said in
vídeo O sea hay algo que hayas dicho en
the video that we have not talked about No
el vídeo que no hayamos hablado No
because in the video I am 100%
porque yo en el vídeo digo 100% de
true and I say everything that I have to
verdad y digo todo lo que tengo que
say So now no I am not going to be
decir Entonces ahora no no te voy a
able to invent or add more things because
poder inventar o Añadir más cosas porque
if I hadn't said it in the video Of course of course it
si no lo hubiera dicho en el video Claro
makes sense It's that in fact,
claro tiene lógica Es que de hecho
in addition to not knowing you, I have seen that
además que no te conocía he visto que me
something of a galen has come out of me, it may be Yes
ha salido algo de galen puede ser Sí
but you in reality, what do you do
pero tú en realidad a qué te
Until a year ago I was a
dedicas Yo hasta hace un año era
marketing professional, I was a marketing
profesional de marketing era marketing
manager, I have a master's degree in
manager tengo un máster de
business administration and I worked
administración de empresas y trabajaba
as a customer relationship manager eh
como customer relationship management eh
in multinational companies a year ago I
en empresas multinacionales hace un año
started making videos okay to
empecé a hacer videos vale para
share my knowledge about
compartir mis conocimientos sobre los
dogs and animals Okay and well I
perros y los animales Vale y bueno me
became very veral now I have accumulated more than 4
hice muy veral ahora acumulo más de 4
million followers on all my
millones de seguidores en todas mis
networks and I also create videos in French and
redes y además creo videos en francés y
in English okay as a result of this it has always
en inglés vale a raíz de esto siempre ha
been  a dream of mine is Got Talent and
sido un sueño para mí es el Got Talent y
now I've been on Got Talent dude
ahora pues he salido en Got Talent tio
four s in the Spanish edition they
cuatro s en la edición española me han
contacted me Got Talent America and well that's
contactado Got Talent América y Bueno
something I do with my Perita
pues eso es algo que hago con mi Perita
and that I like a lot Hey well meen you have to
y que me gusta mucho Oye pues meen me
introduce me Paula Echevarría No
tienes que presentar Paula Echevarría No
now that I'm thinking galen you have to
ahora que que estoy yo pensando galen me
introduce me to Chavarría leave me with the
tienes que presentar la Chavarría déjame
parrots and things like this for me
de loras y de cosas de estas a mí
Introduce me to Paula well let her
Preséntame a la Paula
know if she can
pues le se le se le diere si puede
get into an interview of yours next
entrar en tu una entrevista tuya próxima
time I see her then yes Hey man Well nothing
vez que la veo pues sí Oye tío Pues nada
nice to meet you tomy I wish you
encantado de conocerte tomy Te deseo
the best of luck delighted because I'm already following you
mucha suerte encantado pues ya te sigo
on Instagram Anyway now I'm returning it to you
por Instagram Igualmente ahora te lo
thank you very much for
devuelvo que muchísimas gracias por
uploading and clarifying the
haber subido y habernos aclarado la
story for us the truth is that there's nothing better than
historia la verdad que nada mejor que
having the protagonist here I say Look I
tener aquí al protagonista digo Mira yo
tell you now I'm very aware of
te digo ahora estoy muy pendiente de
this and very nervous So at
esto y muy nervioso Entonces yo al
first I went into your live I saw that you
principio Entré en tu directo vi que
were going to put my conversations I prefer to
ibas a poner mis conversaciones prefiero
say because I had been able to not say
decir porque yo había podido no decir
anything and wait and then I can't
nada y de esperar y luego no te puo
tell you man be careful because I've been here
decir tío ten cuidado porque yo estoy
for three days  that I don't eat it's been three
hace tres días que no como hace tres
days since I've been fed up with all
días que estoy hasta el [__] de todo
this and that everyone who's
esto y que todos los que me están
screwing me over, I'm going to screw them twice as much So
jodiendo les voy a a [__] el doble
I told you a lot of anxiety eh you
Entonces yo te dije mucha ansiadas eh
're so anxious that you [ __ ] yourself No right
estás con una ansiedad que te cagas No
now you are Of course because because
ahora mismo estás Claro porque porque
look at me a year ago I didn't have
fíjate que yo hace un año No tenía
any followers anywhere and
ningún seguidor en ningún sitio y de
suddenly Now I'm in a
repente Ahora estoy en una polémica
worldwide controversy eh everyone is talking about
mundial eh de todo el mundo habla de
this
esto
when Well of course let's see that clo
cuando Bueno claro es que a ver que clo
the content that you do is more
el contenido que tú haces está más
detached but for example they've
despegado pero yo por ejemplo de me han
published conversations with 17 million
publicado conversaciones con 17 millones
views and I'm so so chill at
de visitas y yo tan tan chill por la
night doing live it's that's what
noche haciendo directo es que ya es lo
you get but don't give it so much
que te da pero no le des tanta
importance really I mean because there's
importancia de verdad o sea porque
nothing there's nothing no no there's
tampoco hay que tampoco nada no no hay
nothing let's see I do no no Like I
nada a ver yo s no no Yo como te he
told you it doesn't harm me or quite the
dicho no me perjudica ni todo lo
opposite but on principle I'm not going to
contrario pero por principio yo no voy a
let them insult me ​​to my face
dejar que me que me insultan en la cara
you know what I'm saying when a few days go by
sabes lo que digo cuando pase unos días
you'll laugh about this and you'll move on and you won't even
te reirás de esto y pasarás y ni te
get into it or anything Maybe
meterás en jugado ni nada A lo mejor
against the other Yes okay I think you have to
contra el otro Sí vale que yo creo que
that's not  know me well
tienes que eso no es conocerme bien
because I tell you one thing is that eh
porque yo te digo una cosa es que eh
when I started something I finished it to the
cuando empezó algo lo terminó hasta el
end and I can assure you that the
final y te puedo asegurar que que los
processes that I'm going to start eh if it's
los procesos que voy a empezar eh si se
necessary to put 20,000 of my money I'm going
hace falta poner 20.000 de mi dinero voy
to put 20,000 of my money until there is a
a poner los 20.000 de mi dinero hasta
trial, so I have no
que haya juicio o sea yo ahí no tengo
problem there because eh I'm like a
ningún problema porque eh yo soy como un
pitbull I mean if I have the prey in my
pitbull O sea si tengo la presa en la
mouth I don't let go you understand Because these
boca no lo suelto entiendes Porque esta
people have harmed me a lot they have
gente me ha perjudicado muchísimo me ha
insulted me a lot and I'm going to do
insultado muchísimo y yo voy a hacer
everything to ensure that there is justice you understand
todo para que haya justicia entendes
why they have been laughing at
porque han pues se han estado riendo de
you they haven't been
ti no se han est te han estado
insulting you and such while they saw it
insultando y tal mientras que lo veían
no and they
no y lo
heard it because every person who saw
escuchaban porque cada persona que veía
these conversations thanks to these
estas conversaciones gracias a estos
content creators Yeah well that's
creadores de contenido Ajá pues eso es
their fault because because it was already
la culpa de ellos porque porque ya se
going quite viral on the account queada
hacía bastante viral en la cuenta queada
okay there was no need for this So
vale no se hacía falta de esto Entonces
they have helped and I'm talking about millions
ellos han ayudado y te hablo de millones
of views I'm talking about five or 6 million
de vistas te hablo de cinco o 6 millones
views thanks to these
de vistas gracias a estus
creators And how much has it reached
creadores Y cuánto ha llegado a alcanzar
on Katy's account I do
en la cuenta de de
n't remember but millions
Katy no me acuerdo pero millones de
people also millions no and she What has he
personas también millones no y ella Qué
said to you has he said something
te ha dicho a ti te ha dicho algo así
like I'm sorry for having splashed you or
como lo siento por haberte salpicado o
something like that
algo por el
No I already in his day when because
estilo No yo ya en su día cuando porque
I what you have to know is that eh I
yo lo que hay que saber es que eh yo le
had told him I hope that you see our
había dicho Espero que vres nuestras
conversations because this man if one
conversaciones porque este hombre si un
day finds out you're going to get in trouble and
día se entera te vas a poner en líos y
so yes yes yes what happens is that a little
así sí sí sí lo que pasa es que un poco
distracted Then I The day he
despistada Entonces yo El día que me
calls me to tell me eh Ah well look he has
llama para decirme eh Ah pues mira ha
taken photos of our conversations
tomado fotos de nuestras conversaciones
and he tells me crying Well I am super
y me lo dice llorando Pues yo está super
angry with her but anadim but I
enfado con ella pero anadim pero yo esto
knew this was going to happen because he
sabía que iba a pasar porque él me
threatened me but they are not photos I mean he are
amenazó pero no son fotos o sea él son
screenshots with the screen
cápsulas de pantalla con la pantalla
recorded on the mobile I mean it's not like from
grabada en el móvil o sea no es como de
one mobile to another but he has I mean he
un móvil a otro sino que él tiene o sea
takes screenshots maybe he
él hace captura de pantalla a lo mejor
sends it to his mobile because no no no no
se lo manda a su móvil porque no no no
he the only screenshots he
no él las únicas capturas de pantalla
has are his conversation with him
que tiene es su conversación a él
with me the others are eh videos from a
conmigo lo las otras son eh vídeos de un
mobile they are I have
móvil
not realized well they
son no me he dado cuenta pues me han
seemed to me let's go they seemed to me capture
parecido vamos me han parecido captur
capture cl then  you edit you put it right and you
captur cl luego lo editas pones bien y
put it right Ah Hey well I'm going to
lo pones bien Ah Oye pues te voy a
follow you to see if my dog ​​pays attention to
seguir a ver si me hace caso mi perro
me man because my dog ​​doesn't pay any [ __ ] attention to me and he's teasing me now I'm watching here a little of these the r that are coming out of yours And he says Well are you going to give me advice to splurge man
dar consejos para espil arme tío
anything you need
cualquier cosa que te haga falta
anything you need if you
cualquier cosa que necesites si te
want to another day you have to upload
quieres en otro día tienes que subir
clarify something whatever well here is
aclarar algo lo que sea pues aquí está
your house okay King okay perfect well
tu casa vale Rey vale perfecto pues
thanks for inviting me and Sorry for
gracias por invitarme y Perdona por
having added me at the beginning because I
haberme anado al principio porque te he
told you it's a sensitive subject for me and and that's it
dicho es un tema sensible para mí y y ya
and well I wish you the best in your in
está y bueno Te deseo lo mejor en tu en
your live I see that there are many people there I
tu directo veo que están muchas personas
greet all your followers and nothing
les saludo a todos sus seguidores y nada
if you want to learn things about dogs eh
si queréis aprender cosas de perros eh
My channels are perfect if you want
Mis canales están perfectos si queréis
gossip my channels no they are not for that
chisme mis canales no no son para eso
because I like to talk about other
porque a mí me gusta hablar de de otras
things so each one has their own thing and
cosas entonces cada uno lo suyo y yo lo
mine is animals Well a pleasure tomy, hope it
mío son los animales Pues un placer tomy
goes well okay a big hug
que te vaya bien vale un abrazote
pleasure let's see it has fallen on me Majo The kid
placer a ver me ha caído Majo El chaval
many impressions  many impressions
muchas impresiones muchas impresiones
Eh well except for the alias
Eh bueno menos en lo del tema aliás lo
Lora issue No, I don't
del tema Lora Ahí no ahí no estoy nada
agree with him at all but but many
de acuerdo con él pero pero muchas
impressions
impresiones
wow wow wow
wow
many impressions man I mean what a
wow wow muchas impresiones tío O sea qué
big move what a big move
movida tan gorda qué movida tan gorda
eh what a move man I mean but
eh qué movida
what
o sea pero qué
moves Here watching the gossip Med
movidotas Aquí viendo el chisme Med
cell phones there's nothing my cell phones there's
celulares no hay nada me celulares hoy
nothing today the protagonist has already come
no hay nada ya ha venido el protagonista
here but this is huge no this is
aquí pero esto es enorme no esto es
huge Wait I'm going to talk to
enorme Espérate que voy a hablar con
Andy
Andy
God
Dios
[Music]
[Música]
Karime
Karime
tremendous Karime tremendous
tremendo Karime tremendo
Andy it's been a while,
Andy hace rato
[ __ ] of course
cabrón
Wait I'm talking to Andy eh
claro Espera estoy hablando con Andy eh
we'll be back in a jiffy okay in a
volvemos en un periquete vale en un
jiffy I'm giving him
periquete que le estoy dando
instructions to upload
instrucciones para para subir
this
esto
[Music]
[Música]
and I don't understand why everyone
e yo no entiendo por qué tod
what how and it's what I said before he
qué cómo y es lo que he dicho antes
has to do exactly the same thing as
tiene que hacer exactamente lo mismo que
with me he went to aer again he went on an
conmigo ha ido otra vez a aer ha ido a
adventure with It's that I think he has that
puer aventura con Es que creo que me ha
another for a story things
otra por un cuento cosas
if you knew who you would say that to
si supierais con quién diríais eso de
New exclusive the n n  that
Nueva exclusiva el n n que
one says something for some exclusive of
uno diga algo para alguna exclusiva de
Javi but no
Javi pero que no
and a
y
lie but let's see man what
mentira pero vamos a ver tío que me
have you sent me that Ali has been that I
habéis mandado que el Ali ha estado que
mean it's that we just started watching
o sea es que acabamos de empezar a ver
this and
esto y
cameo we just started watching this there's already a
cameo acabamos de empezar a ver esto ya
cameo I mean we just started the bu
cameo o sea acabamos de empezar los bu
changes in the first 30 seconds and I
camios en los primeros 30 segundos y le
told him that I have
he dicho que tengo
rogues sent
picaros mandado
imagine What do they tell me Who are
imaginas A mí que me digan Quiénes son
those I have no idea contact hitmen
esos no tengo ni idea contact sicarios
dear
querid
no what happened with Ricky was brutal when he said about
no lo de Ricky fue brutal cuando dijo lo
the hitmen
de los sicarios
eh loo a lot because I'm
eh loo mucho porque estoy
km from
a km de
zar in with
zar en con
him you have to fall
él hay que caer
low look how I've fallen low but that's
bajo mira que yo he caído bajo pero eso
already that you
ya
've fallen
es que has caído
down but every time you surpass yourself you go from
abajo pero cada vez te superas vas de
bad to better man it's that I've always
mal a mejor hombre es que yo siempre
been like he
estado
's a son of a [ __ ] that he's
en que es un hijo de [__] que esty
trying to prove friendship with me with
intentando probarme amistad con con
money say
dinero decir
something [ __ ] man But how are you going to say that
algo [__] tío Pero cómo vas a decir
how does it go But I don't know why this
eso cómo va Pero yo no sé por qué este
guy has turned against me if he
chico se ha puesto como en contra mía si
got along like very well with me I don't
se llevaba como muy bien conmigo yo no
know why he has turned against
sé por qué se ha puesto como en contra
me But if I have  treated very well it's so-so
mía Pero si yo lo he tratado muy bien é
there the truth But he was the one
a aí regulín la verdad Pero él fue el
who proposed me Hey and if I speak and what I do do you
que me propuso Oye y si yo hablo y qué
understand I mean what are you
hago me entiendes O sea qué me estás
telling me they put me in all the mess Eh they
contando me meten en todos los saros Eh
put me in all the mess But if I have
me meten en todos los saros Pero si yo
n't done anything you who are a [ __ ]
no he hecho nada tú que eres un [__]
pain that I'm
pesado que te estoy
talking to you
hablando
tell me what's wrong what are you [ __ ] that I'm talking to you
dime qu jode a qu jodes que yo te estoy
no when have I done that with you you
no cuándo he hecho yo eso contigo no
have no enemies have Laura and exclusive
tenéis enemigos tener a Laura y exclusiv
J Olivera
J Olivera
tell it content Javi must feed
cuéntalo contenido Javi debe alimentar a
his
su
family his son pas
familia a su hijo pas
plan literally has to feed
plan literalmente tiene que alimentar a
his son his cousin his mother his wife he
su hijo a su primo a su madre a su mujer
has to feed the whole family that's why he
tiene que alimentar a toda la familia
gets [ __ ] from everyone
por eso saca [__] de todos sin
however he feeds me until me he told me
embargo me alimenta hasta m que me dijo
that he was going to give me 200 bucks for Laura's [ __ ]
que me iba a dar 200 pavos por [__] de
and I told him how it hurts
Laura y yo le dije que cómo me duele
man and I'll let you count it I mean
hombre y te dejo que lo cuentes o sea
1000 and I don't think about you or my mother
1000 y no pienso ni en ti ni en mi madre
that I give him 1000 come here that I
que le doy 1000 vente para acá que yo te
give you the 1000 twenty  over here I'll
doy los 1000 vente para acá que yo te a
see where this guy is that
ver dónde está este chico que me ha
blocked me of course I mean he came to me Hey
bloqueado claro o sea él me vino Oye
but if I do an interview how much do you
pero si yo hago una entrevista cuánto me
give me how much do I charge and I'll give him the
das cuánto cobro y yo le yo le voy
low price of course I'll give him the low price
tirando por lo bajo claro yo lo voy
now he starts haggling but he
tirando ahora ya se va regateando pero
says for 1000 come here for
que dice que por 1000 vente para acá por
1000 come here for 1000 come
1000 vente para acá por 1000 vente para
here for 1000 and we do it and Lali 2000
acá por 1000 y lo hacemos y la Lali 2000
come
que venga para
here I'm sorry but no buo for example at
acá Lo siento pero no buo por ejemplo en
this time of the month I'll say 2
estos momentos de este mes lle a decir 2
and I say that I don't give
y digo que
money free wine
dinero vino gratis
ehin free it's that people are
ehin gratis es que está la gente
wanting him to talk or to put out [ __ ] and
deseando el que hable o sacar [__] y
have the exclusive
tener la exclusiva
of exclusive You're going to have It's that I
de exclusiva la Vais a tener Es que os
would show you
enseñaría
ass I think Ali doesn't want to talk anymore
culo yo creo que Ali ya no quiere hablar
because because it would look bad I mean what
porque porque ya quedaría mal O sea qué
is she going to say I mean I think
es lo que va a decir o sea yo creo que
she doesn't want to anymore she doesn't want to talk
ella ya no quiere no quiere hablar
because it would look bad obviously
porque ya quedaría mal evidentemente
then no why
entonces no ya para
Why did she hit an elderly person
qué Porque le peg a una persona de
Javi had problems in  his town because he
Javi tuvo problemas en su pueblo porque
hit an elderly person,
le pegó a una persona de la tercera edad
the context is unknown, but apparently he
no se sabe el contexto pero al parecer
was a relative of his and the lawyer who
era familiar suyo y el abogado que le
helped him was an acquaintance of
ayudó el conocido de
Dallas, but like, what the [ __ ] is
dala pero comoo que Pero qué [__] es
this? They just brought my criminal record to light.
esto acaban de sacar a la luz mis
You,
tú
eye, eye to this.
ojo ojo a esto
You. What the
Tú Pero qué
[ __ ]? Javi had problems in his town,
[__] Javi tuvo problemas en su pueblo
in the town, that's when I was in the
en el pueblo eso cuando estaba yo en el
town,
pueblo
okay, Javi had
vale que
problems in his town because he
Javi tuvo problemas en su pueblo porque
hit an elderly person,
le pegó a una persona de tercera edad no
the context is unknown, but apparently he was a
se sabe el contexto pero al parecer era
relative of his and the lawyer who helped him
familiar suyo y el abogado que le ayudó
is an acquaintance of
es conocido de
Dallas. That lawyer rescued me.
Dallas me rescató ese abogado
That was when I had the habit of
eso era cuando yo tenía el vicio de
hitting
pegarle
people. Grandmas,
abuelitas
fam. The
fam la
sign, the alley,
laal
said, I'll catch him on the street, I'll destroy him.
m ha dicho yo le Pillo por la calle le
[Music]
[Música]
never, really, TR, in a few more weeks you can
nunca en verdad TR semanas más te puedes
buy a pee there are people saying, [ __ ],
comprar un pis hay gente diciendo [__]
but it's really good, the
pero está muy bueno la
truth is,
verdad
every time I
meda cada ve
interp, no, no, the verge, it's that I don't sti when I
interp no no la ver es que no sti cuando
was est. Lali has been saying for a
estaba est Lali lleva ya diciendo unos
few days now regarding, I don't know if she's
cuantos de días respecto a no sé si se
referring to the Lifan or what,
referirá a los lifan o qué vale
eh, she makes a lot of money, dude  Hey
eh que gana muchísimo dinero tío Oye
leave the grandparents alone man,
dejar ya a los abuelos tranquilos tío
sometimes things like they don't know
señoreros veces las cosas como no sepan
the jokes and the lords eh poor thing, poor thing,
las bromas y los lores eh pobre la pobre
poor thing at all Because here it is more you
la pobre del todo Porque aquí es más te
can fail Oh sorry, there is a need for a fund but much
puedes fallar Ay perdón hace falta fondo
more well, it's that well, what's
per mucho más bueno pues es que pues que
coming as soon as the Tudor trial is over, I
que viene en cuanto acabe juicio tudor
already
ya me
got another one who could die, I
subí otro que se podría morir me c me
fell on me It's not a
cayó No pasa
problem, he could die,
nada se podría morir
honey, I mean, Lali Lali says no, not about that one I mean,
cariño o sea Lali Lali dice que de ese
but let's see
no O sea pero vamos a ver
Lali, next month there's a trial with the
Lali mes que viene un juicio con el
Tudor and you're there saying,
tudor y estáis ahí diciendo
eh, another one who could die and he says Shut up,
eh otro que podría morir y dice Cállate
well, nothing's a problem with that one and no, I'll
bueno de ese no pasa nada y no ya lo
kill him and I'll take care of it. You defended
mataré y ya me encargaré tú defendías
everything that you do now, it's that you fantasize
todo lo que ahora haces es que vo fantas
what moment he defended nothing, well if he
qué momento ha defendido ya nada pues si
defended it, it's not that on top of that,
lo defendía no es que encima lo escrito
the [ __ ] wrote it wrong. I should have
mal el [__] Tendría que haber
put you criticized what you did, what you
puesto tú criticaba lo que hacías lo que
do. Aha, but he's stupid, my poor thing,
haces Aha pero que es tonto pobre mío
the fat guy died, your [ __ ] mother died,
más murió el gordo murió tu [__] madre
son of a [ __ ],
hijo de la grandísima
people are a pain in the ass you
la gente toca los huevos ustedes se
would let yourselves be caught for a million.
dejarían [__] por un millón de
euros H me for
euros H yo por
200 is what you're
200 es lo que te
missing It's not my turn God go Well neither
falta No me toca Ni dios vaya Bueno ni
god nor God
dios ni Dios
no let's see but it has nothing not this
no a ver pero no tiene nada no este
direct noob 25 there is no gossip in
directo noob 25 no hay nada de chisme en
this direct no how much does your account cost
este directo no cuán cuesta tu cuenta
that charged people have so many
que cobrado la gente tiene tantos
balls and then It depends on what you want to
huevos y ya luego Depende lo que quieras
see if you want it or pay for it you get in
ver si lo quieres o lo pagas te metes
that
que
loado information everyone already knows
loado información ya lo sabe todo el
that it's normal it's that all the
mundo que es normal es que todas las
chas first
chas primero
amarer as it has been leaked tuado you will have to make
amarer como se ha filtrado tuado tendrás
an offer like the one that has been leaked
que una oferta como la se ha filtrado
But in the end in the end it has been
Pero al final al final se ha
leaked and what's more what has been
filtrado y que encima lo que se ha
leaked is not even 5% of my
filtrado no es ni un 5% de de mi
content that has been leaked to you all the Yes
contenido que te ha filtrado todo el Sí
and it's what I said before you have to
y es lo que he dicho antes tiene que
do exactly the same as with me it has
hacer exactamente lo mismo que conmigo
gone again aer it has gone aer adventure
ha ido otra vez aer ha ido aer aventura
with It's that I think another one that
con Es que creo que me bloque otra que
was leaked blocked me of course I'm in the
se filt nor claro yo ahora estoy en el
spotlight now because of all this and
foco por toda esta y la
people there is a group on telam that is all there is
gente hay un grupo en telam que está tod
nothing [ __ ] I have eaten 7
no hay nada cabrón me he comido 7
minutes I have eaten 7 minutes of Ali not
minutos me he comido 7 minutos de Ali no
saying anything he is chatting with  the other
diciendo nada está Charlando con el otro
kid and that's
chaval y
it, I mean the funniest thing they
punto o sea lo más divertido que han
said is that he I mean I liked
dicho Es que le O sea me ha gustado más
the comment that someone posted
el comentario que le ha puesto alguien
in the chat more than anything that I hit the grandmothers haha
en el chat que le pego a las abuelas ja
tomorrow the town already has a topic Javi the peg
maana pueblo ya tiene tema Javi el peg
grandmothers Javi threw my
abuelas Javi aventó a mi
grandmother Javi threw my grandmother no [ __ ]
abuelita Javi aventó a mi abuelita no
[ __ ] but he didn't say anything luar
[__] [__] pero no ha dicho nada luar
what the [ __ ] did you send me don't even take an
qué [__] me has mandado no saques
excerpt of this
extracto de esto
okay listen to me one thing
siquiera vale escúchame una cosa
aiden ev
aiden
What text to see for the thumbnail and for
Qué texto a ver para la miniatura y para
the title of the interview with the
el título de la entrevista con el El
kid are we going to put eh On one
chaval vamos a poner eh Por un
side on one side in the
lado por un lado en la
thumbnail hot conversations
miniatura conversaciones
okay for the title maybe I'm going to put I
vale de título a lo mejor voy a poner
saved Katy's life Angel interview
salvé la vida de Katy Ángel entrevista
with Tommy and scadi I imagine I'll put
a Tommy y scadi me imagino que pondré
listen to me
escúchame
eh about this no we don't take the excerpt
eh lo de esto no no sacamos el extracto
not of what we just saw of what we
no de lo que acabamos de ver de lo que
just saw no excerpt or anything no
acabamos de ver ni extracto ni nada
of what we just saw no excerpt
no de lo que acabamos de ver ni extracto
or anything no there was nothing no I mean the
ni nada no no había nada no O sea lo
worst thing about the grandmothers But
peor lo de la lo de las abuelitas Pero
Javi  Would you believe me if I told you that I know where you
Javi me creerías si te digo que sé dónde
live And that when I see you I'll kiss you Of
vives Y que cuando te vea te besaré Por
course I believe it It wouldn't be the
supuesto que me lo creo no sería la
first time that this happens to me
primera vez que me pasa a
Brutal eh
ver brutal eh
how strong no Hey Javi Everything is very
qué fuerte no Oye Javi Todo está muy
calm move the viper man Well, we
tranquilo mueve la vipero hombre pues
just had We just had
acabamos a tener acabamos de tener aquí
the interview of the moment here but it's that I
la entrevista del momento pero es que es
forgot to tell the
más se me ha olvidado decírselo al
kid But well I'm not going to say it
chaval Pero bueno no lo voy a decir
yet in case it comes
todavía por no vaya a ser que
out I'm not going to say it yet in case it
salga no lo voy a decir todavía no vaya
comes out but maybe something big comes out ok maybe
salga pero a lo mejor sale algo gordo
something big comes out ok you'll
vale a lo mejor sale algo gordo vale ya
see ok Yes let's go I wanted to see this I
veréis vale Sí vamos quería yo ver esto
wanted to see about the interview that
quería ver sobre la entrevista que ha
Rodinger's cat did r
hecho la gata de rodinger r
Vidal start again luare Javi I
Vidal empieza otra vez luare Javi te
wanted to introduce you to my grandmother but seeing
quería presentar a mi abuela pero visto
what we've seen I don't know Hey, the subject is here No, the subject is here
lo visto no sé yo Oye ya está el tema no
No, the subject is here Let's see, let's see more
no ya está el tema A ver vamos a ver más
things because in the end, the extract
cosas porque al final extracto solamente
we have only done the extract we have only
hemos hecho extracto solamente hemos
done the first thing about Ali we have not
hecho lo primero lo de Ali no hemos
done anything else because then I was going to
hecho más nada porque luego iba a
start seeing the boy's thing The boy has
empezar a ver lo del chico El chico ha
uploaded
subido
eh blessed is the person who sent me the
eh bendita la persona que me mandó el
email with the conversations of the guy
email con las conversaciones del chico
that finally ended up in an interview
que al final ha terminado en entrevista
Javi this m you see in person with Dallas Yes
Javi este m ves en persona con Dallas Sí
if I'm not mistaken this month I'll see
si no me equivoco este mes me veo en
Dallas in person a couple of times I think
persona con Dallas un par de veces creo
listen to me eh I want to see something that I've been
escúchame eh que quiero ver una cosa que
dragging on for days and in the end I didn't
llevo días arrastrándola y al final no
see it but I'm going to see it on Sergio's Channel
la vi pero la voy a ver en el Canal de
of a white guy Why Well
Sergio de un tío blanco etero Por qué
because he also uploaded it to his
Pues porque lo ha subido además a su
main channel he uploaded it to his
principal lo ha subido a su canal
main channel wait the excerpt is not valid
principal espérate no vale el extracto
the excerpt is not valid I didn't remember I
no vale el extracto que no me acordaba
had the camera
que tenía la cámara
here okay okay We start over We start over
aquí vale vale Volvemos a empezar
luar now okay I've been
Volvemos a empezar luar ahora sí vale
trying to drag on for days I've been
que llevo días intentando arrastrar
wanting to see for days and dragging on
Llevo días queriendo ver y arrastrando
an interview that
el una entrevista que ha hecho la gata
Rodinger's cat did Rosu Vidal with a guy that
de rodinger rosu Vidal en un chaval que
I follow Malber that is about topics of the
yo sigo malber que es de temas de la
gentlemen it's working again a
señoreros se vuelve a funcionar un
bit the kids
poco se vuelve a fusionar la chavalería
and the
y la
gentlemen are merging again people well especially about
señoreros gente pues sobre todo de
Sálvame and those things and he has interviewed
sálvame y esas movidas y ha entrevistado
Rodinger's cat it turns out that he
a la gata de rodinger resulta ser que él
already  I put up like an ad the other day not
ya puso como un anuncio el otro día no
with some headlines the chocas
con algunos titulares el chocas me
used me J redhead cried at me so I would
utilizó J pelirrojo me lloró para que yo
delete I don't know what video anyway So
borrara no sé qué vídeo en fin Entonces
I just know those
yo nada más que a ver conozco mucho esos
two guys a lot, specifically the one with J redhead
dos lores precisamente el de J pelirrojo
The thing with J redhead The thing about the courses, that was
Lo de J pelirrojo Lo de los cursos eso
exclusively revealed to the guy, that was
lo sacó en exclusiva al menda eso fue
exclusive to the guy The cat then
exclusiva del menda La gata luego me
wrote to me and said Oh I'm going to make a
escribió y me dijo Ay voy a hacer un
video about J redhead and like and
vídeo de lo de j pelirrojo y como que y
like it was attributed to her I'm not saying it was
como que se se le adjudicó No digo que
her because she mentions me in the video
ella porque ella me menciona en el vídeo
eh but like it was attributed to her I mean
eh pero como que se le adjudicó o sea
everyone treated it like a
todo el mundo lo trató como un tema de
cat issue and like but if I brought it up I mean that
la gata y como pero si lo he sacado yo o
was my move about JP red and the
sea eso fue movida mía lo de JP rojo y
shocka thing well she jumped on the
lo del shocka pues ella se subió al
bandwagon
carro
[Music]
[Música]
of the
de
chocas thing she jumped on the bandwagon of
lo del chocas ella se subió al carro de
the trick I mean she signed up there
lo del trucazo o sea se apuntó ella allí
for the face I mean she says the chocas
por la cara o sea dice el chocas me
used me and it's like but if it was you it
utilizó y es como pero si fuiste tú
was you who got involved in an issue
fuiste tú a darte a meterte en un tema
that  it was yours for what
que no era tuyo para para lo que hace
she does, I mean, take advantage of the
ella o sea aprovechar los momentos
controversial moments with Choque. Rocio Vidal talks about
polémica con el chocar Rocío Vidal habla
her controversy with Choque, she used me, let's
su polémica con el chocas me utilizó a
see, I imagine she's referring to the
ver yo me imagino que se refiere a la
controversy with Choque that Choque
polémica con el chocas de que el chocas
made that comment, that's a trick, eh, they
hizo aquel comentario eso es trucazo eh
started to denounce him very Beastly and that
le empezaron a funar muy Bestia y ese
same day he called Rocio Vidal,
mismo día llamó a Rocío Vidal a la gata
Roding's cat, she was the one who removed you as a
de roding era la que te quitó como
feminist and said let's discuss this
feminista y dijo vamos a discutir esto
as I want, she told me and let's
como yo quiero me dijo y vamos a
clarify it and such and they had a talk
aclararlo y tal y hicieron una charla
that lasted like an hour or something like that and
que duró como una hora o algo así y
then now she put like a tweet
entonces ahora ella puso como un twit
then. Of course, she, well, I don't know if
entonces Claro pues ella pues no sé si
the tweet went viral or not, but she
el tet se viralizó mucho o no pero ella
put up a tweet criticizing what
puso un tweet criticando lo que dijo el
Choque said as is normal, I
choca como es normal
mean, I don't understand. I mean, Choque
o sea yo no entiendo O sea el chocas
can apologize later, can he
luego puede disculparse puede
explain himself? Hey, well, I was unlucky
explicarse Oye pues estuve desafortunado
because what I wanted to say, what was
pues lo que quise decir lo que se
understood was not what I wanted to
entendió no era lo que yo quería
convey, whatever, a thousand things are okay,
transmitir lo que sea mil cosas vale
but he did it terribly, honestly. I mean, in
pero lo hizo fatal la verdad O sea en
that sense, Choque did it terribly, the
ese sentido el choca lo hizo fatal el
trick  it was a trick it doesn't have much of a
trucazo fue el trucazo no tiene mucha
solution okay And for whatever reason I don't know
solución vale Y por lo que sea no sé
how it came about I don't know if Chostas
Cómo surgió no sé si el chocas la
contacted her let's see what she
contactara vamos a ver qué es lo que
says oh malber
dice ah malber
interviewed rodinger's cat and they say it's
entrevistó a la gata de rodinger y dicen
now
que es ahora
malbert malber it's that Of course malber
malbert malber es que Claro que malber
is very well known in the
es muy conocido en la
señoreros Yes well he did an
señoreros Sí bueno la ha hecho
interview he's now working
entrevista es que ahora está trabajando
at podimo so at podimo he's
en podimo entonces en podimo pues está
interviewed everyone from the
entrevistado a todo el mundo de la
television factory to Jorge to David
fábrica de la tele al Jorge a a David
valde pera anyway we've already seen some
valde pera en fin hemos visto ya algunas
things in am romeira He interviewed her
cosillas en a am romeira La entrevistó
also interviewed rodinger's cat
también entrevistó a la gata de rodinger
and they say that Chostas used her how
y dicen que el chocas la utilizó qué
false that is Well if
falso eso Bueno pues si se ha
what you said has been misinterpreted then
malinterpretado lo que tú has dicho pues
what a shame But the reality is there are
qué putada Pero la realidad es que hay
a lot of people who use alcohol
muchísima gente que utiliza el alcohol
to take advantage of women that there is that that
para aprovecharse de mujeres que hay ese
is a pattern of harassment and
eso es un patrón de acoso y de y de
rape very common in men so
violación muy común en hombres entonces
for you to say that your friend the one who doesn't
que tú digas que tu amigo el que no se
get blind is the one who manages to pick up
pone Ciego es el que consigue ligar con
drunk women well that's horrible
mujeres borrachas pues está horrible
let's see is that you continue with  the same
vamos a ver es que seguís con la misma
story this guy it's so obvious if you have
historia esta tío es tan obvio si tienes
a minimum of cordiality when it comes to
un mínimo de cordialidad a la hora de
understanding the words that chocas says
entender las palabras que dice el chocas
that he wasn't talking about how
que no estaba hablando hablando de que
his friend was taking advantage of women
su amigo se estaba aprovechando de tías
to abuse them when they were
para abusar de ellas cuando estaban
drunk but he was saying that
borrachas sino que estaba diciendo que
his friend by not drinking is someone who is
su amigo por no beber es alguien que es
more articulate and is more aware
más articulado y que está más consciente
during the night Beyond the people who
durante la noche Más allá de la gente
have six or seven drinks that they
que se mete seis siete copas que muchas
often need as a sort of
veces necesita como una suerte de
social lubricant and there are people who
lubricante social y hay gente que
manage to go out and have fun and flirt without
consigue salir y divertirse y ligar sin
drinking that choca expressed himself badly it's
beber que el choca se expresó mal es una
obvious man but stop going around in circles
obviedad tío pero dejar de darle vueltas
stop insisting stop beating yourself up
dejar de insistir dejar de machacar cara
kid Oh well bad luck Well if it was
chaval Ay pues mala suerte Pues si se ha
misunderstood then bad luck but
entendido mal pues mala suerte pero es
the networks are like that mother the
que las redes somos así madre el amor
beautiful love man what a bug are you flirting with
hermoso tío qué chinche sois ligar con
drunk women well it's horrible
mujeres borrachas pues está horrible
but then basically with that he was like
pero entonces básicamente con eso se
that I had defended her let's
quedó como que yo la había defendido a
see what choca said was terrible I
ver el choca lo que dijo era terrible o
mean he also said something
sea además dijo algo así
like Rio de I mean for me he was already
como a Río de o sea para mí ya fuera
part of it because you can explain yourself badly okay
parte porque te puedes explicar mal vale
but of course for me one of the things
pero claro para mí una de las cosas
So it gave it a tone  the thing is that the matter
Así que le daba un tono chungo al asunto
was when he said something like when the waters are
era cuando dijo algo así como a río
troubled, the
revuelto ganancia de
fishermen make a profit, that was the [ __ ]. But oh well, that's
pescadores eso fue la [__] Pero bueno
it, but I think it's people who didn't
ya está pero yo creo que es gente que no
watch the live stream because I used the whole
vio el directo porque yo utilicé todo el
live stream to raise awareness about something else,
directo para concienciar sobre lo otro
but don't you think he had
pero y no crees que él tuvo la
enough opportunity to
oportunidad suficiente como para
explain himself, apologize, or understand
explicarse pedir perdón O entender de
what the situation was about, because let's see,
qué iba la situación ya que a ver el
Chostas didn't apologize, Chostas said it
chocas no pidió perdón el chocas dijo
was a speech he had prepared
que era un spe que él tenía preparado
to raise awareness, to make
para concienciar a la gente para
kids aware that they
concienciar a los chavales de que se lo
could have a good time without drinking, in other words, he
podía pasar uno bien sin beber o sea él
said it was a speech he had
dijo que era un speech que tenía
prepared against alcohol, let's see,
preparado contra el alcohol vamos a ver
man, don't say that, damn it, let's see, I've
tío No digas eso [__] [__] vamos a ver
screwed up, I've screwed up the way I
la he cagado la he cagado de la forma
explained it, it seems like my friend is
que lo he explicado parece que mi amigo
going to hunt drunks, I've screwed up, that's not what I mean, what I mean
va a cazar borrachas la he cagado eso no
is like what
decir es como lo que acaba de decir
Sergio Perfecto just said, it's okay, I mean, I
Sergio Perfecto no pasa nada o sea lo
understand that all of Spain was angry, he
entiendo que toda España se le ech lo
explained it once, he explained it twice, he
explicó una vez lo explicó dos veces lo
explained it 200 times, but there are people who don't
explicó 200 veces Pero hay gente que
give a damn about what
directamente que suda huevos de lo que
Chostas says  or what I stopped saying
diga el chocas o de lo que deje de decir
he had enough opportunity he had
él tuvo la oportunidad suficiente tuvo
the opportunity and he did it I mean he's not
la oportunidad y lo hizo o sea no es
someone who would ignore the subject and say Oh I don't know
alguien que pasase del tema y dijese Ah
And such But well these
lo ignoro Y tal Pero bueno esta gente
Zulander people here explain something else to us I
zulander aquí nos explica otra cosa Yo
understand that a lot of people really
entiendo que a mucha gente le cae muy
dislike Chosas and such it seems to me that he
mal en chocas y demás a mí me parece que
's a good guy in general It
es un buen tío en líneas generales Me
seems to me that at least right now he doesn't
parece que por lo menos ahora mismo le
give a damn about the image that
suda un poco los huevos la imagen que se
people can get of him he's cured
puede hacer la gente de él está curado
now Chosas doesn't matter to him I mean it happens to him
ya el chocas le da igual o sea le pasa
a little like it happens to many of us no I mean they
un poco como a muchos nos pasan no O sea
have to do something really
ya te tienen que hacer algo gravísimo
serious to you for you to even
gravísimo para que te para que se te
move a hair you understand But that did
mueva un pelo me entiendes Pero eso sí
bother him I mean of all the controversies
le molestó o sea de todas las polémicas
that one and the one with Katy vipi are the ones that
esa y la de Katy vipi son las que más
really bother him the most Why do they
realmente le molestan Por qué le
bother him because he's not right I mean what
molestan porque no tiene razón o sea lo
with Katy vipi what she did was no
de Katy vipi lo que hizo fue no Salud
Mental Health I'm getting out of here I don't know what I don't know
Mental me quito de aquí no sé qué no sé
how much I go there to therapy she went on
cuánto voy ahí a terapia se fue una
vacation for a week and came back and also came back
semana de vacaciones y volvió y además
and came back as if nothing had happened After a while I don't
volvió y volvió como si nada Al poco no
know what to see  I'm not saying it's good or
sé qué a ver yo no digo que sea bueno ni
bad, I've seen a lot of things that are a
malo yo he visto muchas cosas que son
bit strong from him, I mean, we've discussed them
fuertecitos de él o sea aquí las hemos
all here, there are a series of behaviors
todas hay una serie de comportamientos
that he should control himself,
que se deberían de controlar él mismo
learn to control himself, without more, I
aprender a controlar a sí mismo sin más
don't know if it's good or bad, I don't think it is, maybe he's
no sé si es bueno o malo yo no creo que
not bad, I mean, there are a
sea a lo mejor no es malo o sea hay
lot of people who say he's a very good
mucha gente que dice que es muy buen
kid, well, those who know him will be
chaval pues lo será los que lo conozcan
okay. But that comment, he didn't have a
vale Pero ese comentario No tuvo defensa
good defense the next day, damn, don't go out the
buena al día siguiente [__] no salgas al
next day if you don't have it well
día siguiente si no lo tienes bien
prepared, okay, but to go and say that it
preparado vale pero [__] y decir que
was a speech that I already had, then with
era un speech que yo tenía ya luego con
time he has been polishing it, I mean,
el tiempo si lo ha ido puliendo o sea ya
the apology, yes, he has been polishing it over
la disculpa si la ha ido puliendo con el
time, but that's
tiempo pero es
what Javi changes the lions. Yes, yes, I'm
lo Javi cambia los leones Sí sí los
going to change the lions at some
leones los voy a cambiar en algún
point, I don't know when, but I'm going to change the lions, I mean, I think that it does
momento no sé cuándo pero los leones los
n't fit anymore, no, we lions, we have to
no pega no los leones tenemos que
find the one we put crabs in. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
buscarnos el que ponemos cangrejos no no
no, I'll
no nada de animalitos no vamos ya
think about it,
pensaré
eh, what Choc said the first few
eh lo que dijo el choc a los primeros
days was that it was a speech that he had
días era que era un speit que tenía
prepared against alcohol, he's like, man  you
preparado contra el alcohol es como tío
're taking me for an idiot, I mean let's
me estás tomando por idiota o sea vamos
see, that was in response to a
a ver eso fue en respuesta a un
comment in the chat, I was
comentario del chat no estaba
absolutely unprepared, don't you
absolutamente nada preparado no te
kid me, get right in my face,
cachón des de m en mi cara
man, what refers to the
hombre lo que se refiere a las
foundations and all that and it's way
fundaciones y demás y está muy por
above this superficial thing that
encima del rollo este superficial que se
all these troops are up to, man, and you shut
trae toda esta tropa tío y tú te callas
the [ __ ] up enough to
la [__] boca suficiente como para
explain yourself, apologize, or understand
explicarse pedir perdón O entender de
what the situation was about, since all of Spain was on his
qué iba la situación ya que toda España
back, he was even mentioned
se le echó encima incluso fue mencionado
in an Irene Montero campaign, I think it
en una campaña de Irene Montero creo que
was about equality, of course. I mean,
era de la igualdad claro Eh quiero decir
when they mentioned it in the
que cuando lo mencionaron en la campaña
equality campaign, they made reference to what
de igualdad hicieron referencia a lo que
Chose said and I found
dijo el choca y a mí me hizo mucha
the indignation very funny. Let's see,
gracia la la indignación A ver
first of all, I empathize and I understand that you can't
primero yo empatizo y entiendo que no se
point the finger at a citizen who is
puede señalar a un ciudadano que te está
paying you, I mean, that citizen is
pagando los o sea ese ciudadano te está
paying for that video, how are you going to point the finger at
pagando ese vídeo cómo vas a señalar a
someone when everyone is going to know
alguien que todo el mundo va a saber a
who they're pointing at and everyone is going to
quién está señalando y todo el mundo va
say, look at Chose, pa pa pa, machaca,
a decir mira el choca pa pa pa machaca
Chose. Not with his own pacha. Okay,
el choca No con su propia pacha Vale
but no, it wasn't the truth. In that
pero no no era la verdad en esa campaña
Irene Montero campaign, there was precisely
de Irene Montero precisamente se hizo
a manipulation of what  Pablo
una manipulación de lo que dijo Pablo
Moto said there was a manipulation of
moto se hizo una manipulación de varios
several of the cases that he put, everything was
de varios de los casos que puso de todo
manipulated, but what he said about
manipulación pero es que de lo que dijo
Choca is that they said it literally, they
del choca es que lo dijeron literal de
fell short because what
se quedaron cortos porque lo que dijo el
Choca said, Centero was worse, you know, it was like
choca el centero era peor sab era como
everyone else. Ah, but what are you
todo el mundo Ah pero qué estás
manipulating? And it's like [ __ ], for once, for
manipulando Y es como [__] para una vez
once they put something
para una vez que ponen una cosa de
literally,
manera literal
you know, there was a stir, he had
sabes hubo un revuelo tuvo medios
enough means to justify himself or
suficientes como para justificarse o
ask for forgiveness, he did it, he did a
pedir perdón lo hizo lo hizo hizo un
live show with Rodinger's cat, he
directo con la gata de rodinger estuvo
talked about it at length What do you
hablando de ello largo y tendido Qué
want from him? I have no [ __ ]
quieres de él es que no tengo ni [__]
idea, of course, what else is he going to do, quite the opposite, he didn't do it, let's
idea tí claro qué más va hac ya todo lo
see, let's see, do you want from him? I have no [ __ ] idea, man,
hizo a ver a ver quieres de él es que no
quite the opposite.
tengo ni [__] idea tío todo lo
This will be a lie, no, I mean, the
contrario Esto será mentira no o sea los
encores can be sent with another name, no, he didn't
bis se pueden mandar con otro nombre no
do it, he really made it worse, did you come in
no lo hizo lo empeoró realmente entraste
with the intention of making him open his
con la intención de hacerle abrir los
eyes? Oh, I've got him muted, Jorge.
ojos Ay lo tengo silenciado Jorge
Forgive me, wait, I'm going to put it back on, man, I've
Perdóname espera lo voy a volver a poner
got him muted. Rey, forgive me, or
tío lo tengo silenciado Rey perdóname o
had I muted him for the interview
lo había silenciado para la entrevista
with the
del
kid Javi. Good night, sorry to
chaval Javi Buenas noches siento
interrupt, but we can still
interrumpir Pero igual podemos
react in the next retro salseo
reaccionar en el siguiente retros salseo
to your video or presentation to big brother
a tu vídeo o presentación a gran hermano
if you still have it clear a big hello and
si aún lo tienes claro un gran saludo y
hug Jai I don't have a [ __ ]
abrazo Jai yo eso no tengo ni puñetera
clue about that I don't have a [ __ ] clue I
idea yo eso no tengo ni puñetera de idea
mean if it's somewhere it's in the
o sea si está en alguna parte está en el
canijo on some occasion that I have
canijo en alguna ocasión que lo haya
put it here we have
puesto yo aquí hayamos
reacted if it's
reaccionado si está en alguna
somewhere I have no [ __ ] idea there were many
parte ni putísima idea hubo muchos
videos like that eh personal jobs that
vídeos así eh curros personales que los
I had saved somewhere I lost them I
tenía yo por ahí guardados los perdí
made a video dude eh [ __ ] that really pisses
hice un vídeo tío eh [__] que eso sí
me off and also I think it was the
que me jode y además creo que fue el
first video that I had uploaded to
primer vídeo que tenía yo subido a
YouTube or the second I had uploaded to the
YouTube o el segundo lo tenía subido al
Channel and I deleted it
Canal y lo borré
instead of putting it private I deleted it and it
en vez de ponerlo en privado lo borré y
was a piece of video that I cured at
era un pedazo de vídeo que me curé en
my grandmother's house because when my
casa de mi abuela porque cuando mi
grandmother passed away I was like
abuela falleció como que estuve yo
pending on when the apartment was for
pendiente de cuando estaba el piso a la
sale because I was the one who went and
venta pues era yo el que iba y lo
showed it and all that stuff no And
enseñaba y todo el rollo ese no Y
then I came up with a really cool video
entonces me ocurrió un vídeo guapísimo
with beautiful music really cool the
con una música preciosa chulísimo el
video in which I arrived p arrived at
vídeo en el que yo llegaba p llegaba a
my grandmother's house also with some shots
casa mi abuela además con unos planos
like that arriving down the street  of my grandmother
así llegando por la calle de mi abuela
the stairs Pin and now as I was
las escaleras Pin y ahora conforme iba
entering my grandmother's house there
entrando por la casa de mi abuela pues
were like superimposed photos
había como fotos super puestas
eh In the same place of my grandmother When I was a
eh En el mismo sitio de mi abuela Cuando
girl my mother when I was a girl my grandmother
chica mi madre cuando chica mi abuela
with my grandfather when they were young in the same
con mi abuelo de jóvenes en los mismos
places for example I passed by the door
sitios por ejemplo pasaba por la puerta
of the house well a superimposed photo
de la casa pues una foto super puesta
with the photo you know what I mean I entered
con la foto me entiendes o sea entraba
the house well a photo of her
dentro de la casa pues una foto de ella
at the door of the house or rather a video
en la puerta de la casa o sea un vídeo
was the best man I would put it up man and I don't
era la [__] tío os lo pondría tío y no
have it man I deleted it from my channel I
lo tengo tío lo borré de mi canal lo
had it on the principality channel the second
tenía en el canal principado el segundo
third video I have it uploaded I deleted it
tercer vídeo lo ten ha subido lo borré
when because I had some videos
cuando porque yo tenía algunos vídeos
So they were personal and I deleted them
Así que eran personales y los borré
because when I started to grow up I said this
porque cuando empecé a crecer dije esto
no man you know the only one I left was
no hombre sabes el único que dejé fue es
from my cousin's wedding and I deleted that video
ser de la boda de mi prima y ese vídeo
and I don't have it man anywhere
lo borré y no lo tengo tío en ninguna
man what a great video it was man what a great
tío qué pedazo de vídeo era tío qué
video it was
pedazo de vídeo era
man or scratch
tío o de rascar
Followers scratch followers my mother
Seguidores rascar seguidores madre mía
impossible how can you think that
imposible cómo se te puede ocurrir que
a youtuber slash influencer does something
un youtuber barra influencer haga algo
to gain followers
para ganar seguidores
impossible but not even from Fly per because I
imposible pero ni de Fly per porque yo
know that those things  they bring me nothing good
sé que esas cosas no me traen nada bueno
And they also bring me a lot uh a lot of
Y además me traen muchísimo eh muchísimo
pain I mean I'm very sensitive and
dolor o sea yo soy muy sensible y a mí
the comments and the criticism affect me
los comentarios las críticas me afectan
quite a bit I regret it because I don't know how to
bastante me arrepiento porque no sé
handle those I mean I don't know how to be tough
gestionar esas o sea no sé ser dura
straight it's always happened to me when I do
directo me me ha pasado siempre que hago
debates I am I am I don't know how to be very very tough
debates Soy soy No sé ser muy muy dura
with the person then I should have not
con la persona entonces tendría que hab
known the guy so much it's that you
no haberle conido tanto al ch es que no
weren't in a debate I don't think so and should
estabas en un debate No creo yo y
have told him more clearly uh should have been
haberle dicho más claro eh haber sido
tougher God I can't anymore
dura Dios no puedo yo ya tío no me
man I don't remember how the cat went but it sounds to me like she left Chosco to say whatever he wanted I don't know I don't remember here we reacted to that but I don't remember I can't man there's nothing left of the girl that I once met at
la chica que yo un día conocí en la gata
Rodinger's cat bro the truth is I didn't know how to
de rodinger bro la verdad es que no supe
be tough enough you think
ser lo suficientemente dura crees
So she used you Yeah yeah of course that's
Entonces te utilizó Sí sí claro eso
for sure you sons of
seguro hijos de la gran
[ __ ] It's okay but of course Yeah yeah
[__] No pasa nada pero claro Sí sí
obviously she says okay a woman Eh
obviamente dice vale una mujer Eh
feminist how about I don't know what I'm going to
feminista qu tal no sé qué la voy a
put her in Here I'm going to whitewash myself I mean
meter Aquí voy a blanquearme O sea tú
on the one hand you're trying to do the  English:
por un lado estás intentando hacer la
least technical reading possible of no no
lectura menos técnica posible de no no
I didn't get involved to scrape followers
yo no me metí por rascar seguidores
Of course you do everything out of a kind of
Claro tú todo lo haces por una suerte de
altruism and great goodwill Of
altruismo y gran buena voluntad Por
course I didn't go to the Stream at a
supuesto que no fui al Stream en un
time of maximum controversy of one of the
momento de máxima polémica de uno de los
biggest Spanish-speaking streamers
streamers más grandes de habla hispana
to in the chocas Stream in all his
para en el Stream del chocas en toda su
controversy of trucazo the cat of rodinger uploaded there We
polémica de trucazo subió ahí la gata de
would have to see the social Blade
rodinger Habría que ver el social Blade
What happens is that we can't see that anymore
Lo que pasa que ya eso no lo podemos ver
scraping followers would not occur to me It
rascar seguidores no se me ocurriría
was all a totally
Todo fue un gesto totalmente
disinterested gesture And you went to the chocas live stream
desinteresado Y fuiste al directo del
as you could have gone to
chocas como podías haber ido al directo
Pedro el de los palotes' live stream with 200
de Pedro el de los palotes con 200
subscribers 100% it was like that I believe it
suscriptores 100% fue así me lo creo
okay Rocío I believe it but nevertheless
vale Rocío me lo creo pero sin embargo
at the same time you do affirm that the
al mismo tiempo tú sí que afirmas que la
chocas mentality of taking you to that
mentalidad del chocas de llevarte a ese
live stream was due to a kind of whitewashing of
directo era por una suerte de blanquear
his image to bring in a feminist
su imagen para dar traer a una feminista
for such a totally cynical
para tal una cuestión totalmente cínica
strategic and deliberate issue You know while
estratégica y deliberada Sabes mientras
you did everything from a superbad point of
que tú todo lo hiciste desde un punto de
view disinterested altruistic
vista supermal desinteresado altruista
is the best dude  how are you dude How are
es la [__] tío cómo sois tronco Cómo
you macho it's that I listen to you man and it's
sois macho es que os escucho tío y es
[ __ ] arrogance and arrogance without stopping
[__] soberbia y arrogancia sin parar
macho Franco of
macho Franco de
God stupid it's amazing how
Dios estúpido es alucinante lo
in love you are with yourselves
enamorados que estáis de vosotros mismos
and the measuring stick that I then use is
y la vara de medir que luego utilizo es
a bastard okay But to me knowing it
un cabrón vale Pero a mí que lo sepa
internally proves it but it does
interiormente lo demuestra pero sí que
prove it haven't you seen 5000 clips
lo demuestra no habéis visto 5000 clips
of Chosas admitting that he was wrong to
del chocas admitiendo que se equivocó al
express what he was expressing in that
expresar lo que estaba expresando en ese
live you haven't seen any and here's
directo no habéis visto ninguno y aquí
dude Ben Steer from Hacendado
está tío el Ben steer de hacendado
saying The truth is I haven't
diciendo Yo la verdad es que no lo he
seen it You're a [ __ ] moralist of a thousand
visto Eres un [__] moralista de mil
pairs of balls and that's something that
pares de cojón y eso es algo que me
seems fine to me but if you're a [ __ ]
parece bien pero si eres un [__]
moralist you should be aware of what it
moralista deberías ser consciente de lo
affects on a mental level when you say
que afecta a nivel mental que le digas
stupid things to people you should not
burradas a la gente deberías de no
denigrate and slander people even
denigrar y calumniar a la gente aun
when they make a mistake because that's not
cuando cometan algún error porque ese no
your [ __ ] job you are not the judge of
es tu [__] trabajo tú no eres juez de
anything and the things that you say in front of your
nada y las cosas que tú dices ante tu
audience affect people on a mental level
audiencia afectan a nivel mental a las
especially in things  in which they
personas sobre todo en cosas en las que
know they have failed and one day I told an
saben que han fallado y un día conté una
anecdote and I told it wrong and I will
anécdota y la conté mal y estaré
regret it all my [ __ ] life is that what he
arrepentido toda mi [__] vida es que
said Here chocas which is one
esto que ha dicho Aquí chocas que es un
more moment repeated like 100,000
momento más lo repetido como 100,000
times And we still have this Zulander here is
veces Y todavía tenemos aquí al zulander
that to me he knows that he
este es que a mí que él sepa que lo ha
said it wrong or that he failed And such But
dicho mal o que ha fallado Y tal Pero
that he does not recognize it is that to me it does not
que no lo reconozca es que a mí como que
mean anything to me brother man mortgage the
no me dice nada hermano tío hipoteca el
brain [ __ ] the mother who gave birth to me you
cerebro cabrón la madre que me parido tú
to me that he knows but that he does not say it and
a mí que lo sepa pero que no lo diga y
such [ __ ] cynical liar of the balls
tal [__] mentiroso cínico de los [__]
stupid man he is that you have to
tío estúpido el es que hay que
inform yourself to do an interview
informarse para hacer una entrevista
you have to inform yourself and know what you
tienes que informarte y saber de lo que
are going to talk about and know well all the or
vas a hablar y saberte bien todos los o
rather you see that I simply eh
sea fíjate tú que yo simplemente eh
when I saw the headlines that he published I already
cuando vi los titulares que publicó Ya
knew who the interview was with man an
supe a quién era la entrevista tío una
interview that has nothing to do
entrevista que no tiene nada que ver
with me and that I have not done okay if you
conmigo y que no he hecho yo vale si tú
go there there to give your opinion on chocas and the
vas ahí ahí a opinar del chocas y de la
choca controversy you have to know
polémica del choca tienes que saber
about all the most current How it turned out  and
sobre todo lo más actual Cómo quedó y en
what happened And what did he say and and and that's it Okay
qué quedó Y qué dijo y y y ya está Vale
dude and the disgust that
chazo y la repugnancia que me genera
these people generate in me is something that is beyond
esta gente es algo que está fuera de
any limits man doubt that arises
todo límite tío duda que se me plantea
in my wonderful little head if you are
en mi maravillosa cabecita si estás en
against machismo you are against The
contra de machismo estás en contra de El
sexism of the abuse of the
sexismo del abuso de la cultura de la
rape culture you are against everything that
violación estás en contra de todo lo que
chocas has promoted that is what
ha promovido el chocas eso es lo que ha
chocas has promoted you keep saying that
promovido el chocas sigues diciendo que
well you consider yourself used I think that
pues te consideras utilizada Yo creo que
the headline has already given it to him with he
el titular ya se lo ha dado con el me
used me but here he is trying like
utilizó pero aquí está intentando en
Why not have you not considered
plan Por qué no no te has planteado en
making a video create more for seo let's see
hacerle un vídeo crear más al seo a ver
in that message he was giving a
el en ese mensaje estaba dando un
bad message that he later
mensaje malo que luego se haya
apologized and that he regretted it and that he
disculpado y que se haya arrepentido y
realized okay my
que se haya dado cuenta vale opinión mía
personal opinion on that subject that I am not taking it out
personal sobre ese tema que no lo estoy
He is taking it out okay
sacando yo lo Está sacando la gata vale
my opinion is that chocas after
la opinión mía es que el chocas después
saying that nonsense that he believed he
de soltar esa burrada que él creía que
was saying it and that nothing was happening
lo estaba soltando y que no pasaba nada
that it was just another conversation like 80 that he
que era una conversación más como 80 que
has every day in I don't know how many hours of
tiene cada día en no sé cuántas horas de
live the tan  normal at that moment
directo el los tan normal en ese momento
but then when it happened to him
pero ya luego cuando se le hecho la
people did realize the atrocity
gente sí se dio cuenta de la barbaridad
that he had said okay then the
que había dicho vale que luego la
real anecdote is in another way and he will
anécdota real sea de otra forma y él se
express himself badly well well that's it because
expresará mal pues bueno pues ya está
if he says it why would I believe
pues si él lo dice por qué voy a creer
the opposite okay okay Yes surely
lo contrario vale vale Sí seguramente yo
in fact what I think if you want me to
de hecho lo que yo pienso si queréis que
be sincere what I think is that he
sea sincero lo que yo pienso es que él
wanted to tell it as something funny like
lo quiso contar como algo gracioso como
a joke and surely maybe he doesn't
una gracia y seguramente a lo mejor no
even have any friends who don't get
tiene ni ningún amigo que que no se
drunk or maybe he has a
emborracha o a lo mejor mejor tiene un
friend who once got us drunk and he got
amigo que una vez nos emborrachó y él
us drunk and hooked up with someone who
nos emborrachó y ligó con alguien que
was more drunk or more drunk and he
que iba Más bebido o más bebida y él
drank and to do the Stream eh the
cogió y para hacer el Stream eh la
performance well he exaggerated it a little to
performance pues lo exagero un poco para
tell it as a joke and it went wrong
contarlo como una gracia y le salió mal
That's what I think happened Okay
Eso es lo que yo creo que pasó Vale
now what cli said by cli is an
ahora lo que dijo cli por cli es una
outrage I mean it's nonsense there's no
barbaridad o sea es una burrada no hay
way to grab it you
por dónde cogerlo me
understand me exactly I mean there's no way to
entiendes tal cual O sea no hay por
grab it anywhere not a
dónde agarrarlo por ninguna parte no a
jumbled river fishermen's profit
rí revuelto ganancia de pescadores
Because yes Normally they see me as  in
Porque si Normalmente me ven como en
four Well I take this one and he sees me like
cuatro Pues yo cojo a esta y me ve como
a seven you know what he
un siete me entiendes de lo que se dio
realized is that people see the
cuenta es de que la gente ve las
nonsense he says no that
barbaridades que dice no de que era tan
what he said was as serious as he said it Lady I
serio lo que dijo como lo dijo Lady yo
do believe that he has realized she has no choice you
sí creo que se ha dado cuenta no la ha
know but I think
quedado otra me entiendes pero yo creo
that at the moment he said it he didn't
que en el momento que lo dijo él no lo
see it as bad he saw it as something Look look at
vio malo él lo vio como algo Mira mira
the guy let's see how he flirts you know he's not
el cabrón a ver cómo liga sabes no va
drunk the others Yes I think because to
borracho las otras Sí yo creo porque a
me with the way the way he had of
mí con la forma la forma que tenía de
telling it so naturally so at
contarlo así tan natural tan así de
first Yes I saw it that he saw it as
primera Sí yo lo vi que él lo vio como
something normal but come on under no
algo normal pero vamos bajo ningún
circumstances the excuse he made the first
concepto la excusa que puso la primera
time I mean the next day the chocas
vez O sea al día siguiente el chocas
when he came out he didn't apologize as such he
cuando salió no se disculpó como tal él
said it was a speech and over time he has
dijo que era un speech ya con el tiempo
been apologizing like in this
sí se ha ido disculpando como en este
clip that we have seen but he said it
clip que hemos visto pero él dijo que
was a speach he had prepared I mean that's
era un speit que tenía preparado o sea
like when I said with
eso es como cuando yo di dije con lo de
Juanjo When I made peace with him that I
Juanjo Cuando hice las pases con él que
said it wasn't a test I don't know what I don't
dije no era una prueba no sé qué no
remember what I made up you know
acuerdo que es lo que me inventé sabes
how no man I mean I went to do  I made peace
como no tío o sea fui a hacer las pases
with him, I was pissed off with the other guy, I went to
con él estaba picado con el otro fui a
make peace with him, thinking it was
hacer las pases con él creyéndome que
going to turn out well, and two or three days later I
iba a salir bien y a los dos o tres días
saw him again roasting La Patita and it
ya le vi otra vez asando La Patita y no
couldn't be, you know what I mean? But this is the
pudo ser me entiendes Pero esto es lo
same, I mean, tell the truth, man. Well, yes, I
mismo o sea di la verdad tío Pues sí no
hadn't realized the nonsense, but it
me había dado cuenta de la burrada pero
's not a speech against alcohol that I
no es un speech contra el alcohol que yo
had prepared,
tenía preparado
damn, you're
[__] vas a tener preparada una cosa que
going to have something prepared that came out improvised on the live show, kid, make a video The Hidden Face of Chocas, not the dark side of Chocas, that would be a very good video, Rocio. Think about it. So, doesn't it seem a little incoherent to you to be part of this Circus by following him on
siguiéndole en
Instagram? Wow, he follows me on
instagram Wow que me sigue
Instagram. Holy crap, man, this turkey,
Instagram Dios santo tío este pavo en
seriously, you know one of the
serio tronco sabes una de las personas
most repulsive people I've ever read on
más repelentes que he leído yo en
Twitter in my life, but seeing that he
Twitter en mi vida pero viendo que
also has a show and listening to
encima Tiene un programa y escuchando en
the show, you know the repulsiveness and let's see,
el programa sabes la repelencia y a ver
malver, I liked it, I
malber a mí me me gustó me gustaban
really liked the videos he made on his
mucho los vídeos que él hacía en su
main channel, here we've probably seen some
canal principal aquí hemos visto alguno
and I've cracked up with,
seguramente y yo me he descojonado con
with malver  uh I mean I was
con con malver eh o sea yo me he
laughing my ass off but when the whole
descojonado pero cuando empezó todo el
docuseries thing started dude all of a sudden he
tema de la docuserie tío de repente
started saying some
empezó a decir
really awful things that didn't fit with other
barbaridades que no casaban con otras
things he'd said previously
cosas que había dicho él anteriormente
awful things okay let's see I think that
barbaridades vale a ver yo creo que el
Malver's ideological profile we don't
perfil ideológico de malver no hace
need to do an exam or a
falta que hagamos aquí un examen ni un
sketch to find out what it is and we can
croqui para averiguar cuál es y podimos
already know you know that we can always
ya sabéis ya sabéis que podimos siempre
have the same line both with the
tiene la misma línea tanto con los
programs that he has and the
programas que tiene como los
presenters like the majority of the
presentadores como la mayoría de los
guests yes it's true that on
invitados sí que es verdad que en
some occasions there are sessions but
algunas ocasiones hay sesiones pero por
generally on podimo you know and
lo general en podimo ya sabemos Y de
somehow this guy uh they start
alguna manera este chico eh empiezan a
calling him from telec I mean he defends
llamarlo de telec o sea él defiende a
Rocío Carrasco and they start calling him from
Rocío Carrasco y empiezan a llamarlo de
telec they put like a program on my
telec le pusieron como un programa en mi
TV I think it was and then they put
tele creo que fue y después le pusieron
this on podimo and he's interviewed everyone
esto en podimo y ha entrevistado a todos
from salvame on podimo I think there's
los de salvame en podimo yo creo que hay
something clear obviously I mean you guys I
algo claro evidentemente o sea ustedes
think that that program no I'm not going to
yo creo que ese programa no no lo voy a
say it I'm not going to say it I'm not going to say
decir no lo voy a decir no voy a decir
one thing because it's going to look bad on my
una cosa porque va a quedar mal por mi
part but not him to me  He made me
parte pero a mí él no a mí él me ha
laugh a lot before it happens
hecho mucha gracia anteriormente pasa
that it is true when he started to him
que sí que es verdad cuando empezó a le
when he started with the dukus series I already
cuando empezó con la dukus serie ya
started to get used to I started to get used to
empecé a habitu empecé a habitu de
disrespect from him to people to
faltas de respeto de él a la gente a
Rocío Flores some nicknames and some things you
Rocío flores unos motes y unas cosas
know what I said man you can defend
sabes que dije hombre tú puedes defender
a story eh I mean because in the end you
un relato eh o sea porque tú al final
can defend a story or we do not
puedes defender un relato o no estamos
agree I mean I believe I do not believe
de acuerdo o sea yo me cre yo no me creo
Roso Carrasco and you You can believe it
a roso Carrasco y tú Te la puedes creer
but there are things and there are things There are things
pero ya hay cosas y hay cosas Hay cosas
and there are things 9000 the [ __ ]
y hay cosa 9000 el medidor de [__]
repulsion meter explodes man When I hear
repelencia se me estalla tío Al escuchar
this turkey of this Circus following him on
este pavo de este Circo siguiéndole en
instagram Wow I follow him on
instagram Wow le sigo en
instagram I follow a lot of people no no no no
instagram sigo a muchísima gente no no
excuse the question doesn't it seem
no no excusa la pregunta no te parece
incoherent to belong to the circus that
incoherente pertenecer al circo que
you say so much you are against what is
tanto dices que estás en contra de qué
this man talking about what Circus are you talking to me
habla este señor de qué Circo me habla
[ __ ] following chocas on instagram that
cabrón seguir al chocas en instagram que
millions of people will follow him is to be
le seguirán millones de personas es
part of a circus I mean man if he
formar parte de un circo o sea hombre si
is yes he is here talking about that
está si está aquí hablando de que el
chocas used it that he is super
chocas la utilizó que está super en
against I don't know what well it is not  very
contra no sé qué pues no es muy
coherent that I
coherente que lo
follow it may be eh But it's true that I
siga puede ser eh Pero es verdad que yo
follow very very different people and with whom I do
sigo gente muy muy distinta y con la que
n't agree at all to kind
no coincido absolutamente nada para un
of see and follow because since I don't have
poco ver y seguir porque como no tengo
secondary accounts I follow everything with my
cuentas secundarias lo sigo todo con mi
main account so it's happened to me
cuenta principal entonces me ha pasado
many times that they've told me [ __ ] you
muchísimas veces que me han dicho [__]
follow this person dude Why do you
sigues a esta persona tío Por qué la
follow her and I'm okay it's that I follow to see a
sigues y yo vale es que sigo para ver un
little What's going on there then
poco Qué pasa por ahí entonces
surely I followed him on his But what are you
seguramente le seguí en su Pero qué
doing justifying yourself but seriously dude
haces justificándote pero en serio tío
how low have you fallen if it's Whoever you want
qué bajo has caído si es A quién te da
Rocío That's it if at the time you
la gana Rocío Ya está si en su momento
liked him The kid and you spoke well
te cayó bien El chaval y hablaste bien
to him You got on well with him or you continued
con él Quedaste bien con él o seguiste
then that's it
pues ya
What [ __ ] bottomless pit can
está En qué [__] pozo sin fondo se puede
someone get into like that
meter alguien como para que venga el
[ __ ] zulander comes to ask you for
putísimo zulander a pedirte
explanations of why you follow him you
explicaciones de por qué sigues al
crash on instagram I [ __ ] on my [ __ ]
chocas en instagram me cago en mi [__]
life and you instead of telling him to [ __ ] off
vida y tú en vez de mandarle a tomar por
start there well no Look, the thing is that
culo empieces ahí de bueno no A ver es
I follow a lot of people people who
que yo sigo a muchísima gente gente que
think in many ways like
que piensa de muchas maneras la del
critical thinking like long live
pensamiento crítico la de viva la
science giving explanations to  a man
ciencia dando explicaciones a un señor
dressed in neon lights asking why you follow the
vestido de neones de por qué sigues al
[ __ ] guy you crash on Instagram while he
[__] chocas en Instagram mientras él te
looks at you with a stern face there
mira de con con rostro Severo ahí por
why Why are you part of the Circus or rather
qué Por qué formas parte del Circo o sea
how someone with this face with these
cómo alguien con esta facha con estas
questions with that face has the
preguntas con esa cara tiene los santos
balls to tell anyone why they are
huevos decirle a nadie que por qué forma
part of the Circus I swear it's because I don't
parte del Circo yo te juro que es que no
look at Instagram beyond that I don't look at Stories
miro Instagram más allá no miro Stories
or
ni
anything and the other one justifying herself instead of
nada y la otra justificándose en vez de
telling him to [ __ ] off you know if I follow
mandarle a la [__] sabes si yo sigo a
whoever I want ask yourself Why do
quien me da la gana pregúntate Por qué
n't I follow you clown but if you do
no te sigo a ti payaso pero si sí que me
follow me look at it again a follow
sigues míralo otra vez un follow
[ __ ] come to your house it's gotten
[__] venga a tu casa
a little heated no that would have
se ha calentado se un poco no eso sí que
been an epic end to the interview
habría sido un final de entrevista épico
well it's hypocritical Obviously that I continue
bueno Es hipócrita Obviamente que siga
actively because I understand that follow
activamente porque entiendo que seguir
is a synonym
es un sinónimo
for let's see this move is
de a ver está movida es
true Let's see but how But how is it going to
verdad A ver pero cómo Pero cómo va a
be that the
ser que el tema
Cry topic breaks Twitch with Jerry mu and dasas
Cry rompe Twitch con Jerry mu y dasas le
attacks him in
ataca de la per
performance or rather whatever the topic dude whatever
forma o sea sea cu sea el tema tío sea
the
cual sea el
topic Cry and Jer rock it but I hate  to
tema Cry y Jer lo petan pero odio a
Dallas mother of all love beautiful uncle be
Dallas madre de la amor hermoso tío
of be
estar de estar
validating be but don't [ __ ] with me that in the
validando sea pero no me jodas que al
end So in the end Sergio hasn't
final O sea que al final Sergio no ha
touched the J redhead thing Well let's see I'm
tocado lo de J pelirrojo Pues a ver Me
going to go to malver I'm going to go to
voy a ir para malver me voy a ir para
malver and I'm going to start again eh luare
malver y voy a empea de nuevo eh luare
this for the part the reaction to Sergio
esto por la parte la reacción a Sergio
about the cat and utbh leave the
sobre la gata y utbh dejal la
part the mother who gave birth to me
parte la madre que me parió
you
tú
the mother who gave birth to me But how are you going to
la madre que me parió Pero cómo vas a
link Dallas with anything man I
enlazar a Dallas con cualquier cosa tío
mean how can you link Dallas with
o sea cómo puedes enlazar a Dallas con
anything
lo que sea
eh Let's see mam mia I don't know who this is going to
eh A ver mam mía esto no sé a quién va
[Music]
[Música]
eh and what do you think is more dangerous for
eh e qué crees que es más peligroso para
society the fentanyl pandemic or
la sociedad la pandemia del fentanilo o
the fooding of Carlos Ríos
el fooding de Carlos Ríos
[ __ ] let's see obviously Obviously the
[__] a ver obviamente Obviamente el
fentanyl front because they are the most
frent alilo porque son los problemas más
serious problems that we have right now
graves que que tenemos en la actualidad
with Carlos Ríos I also have is that
con Carlos Ríos también tengo es que
also No nobody I mean the thing with Carlos Ríos
también No nadie o sea lo de Carlos Ríos
is delicate because of course I have also
es delicado porque claro yo también le
dedicated a video to him we have spoken afterwards
he dedicado un vídeo hemos hablado luego
also privately and we get along
también por privado y nos llevamos
well you will be false or mean this makes the
bien serás falsa o sea esta hace los
videos  people and then they get along
vídeos a la peña y luego se llevan bien
I remember when I used to
Yo me acuerdo cuando yo antes me
follow each other but it was on the other account I think
seguía pero era en la otra cuenta creo
on this new one I think not I followed each other
en esta nueva creo que no yo me seguía
with Rocío on the previous Twitter
con Rocío en el Twitter anterior
because what was my thing with the cat
porque cuál fue mi movida con la gata
I have to have the emails and
tengo que tener por ahí los emails y las
things around here The thing was something like
cosas La Movida fue algo así como
my thing with Rodinger's cat
que la movida mía con La gata de
was that I did No what was it ha ha
rodinger fue que yo hice No qué es lo
with the cat was that
ja via con la gata fue
she made that video of the ones of
que que ella hizo el vídeo ese de las de
the Ay of the modern shamans it was no and it turns
la Ay de las chamanas modernas era no y
out that the whole script as is Pin
resulta que todo el guion tal cual Pin
Pin Pin Pin was from a forum taken from a
Pin Pin Pin era de un foro sacado de un
forum but even the jokes and then I
foro pero hasta los chistes y entonces
took eh I didn't say anything at first they
cogí yo eh Yo no dije nada al principio
sent me the information I kept quiet I don't
me mandaron la información me callé no
remember if I reacted to her video or
me acuerdo si reaccioné a su vídeo o
I made another video taking information
hice yo otro vídeo sacando información
from her video I don't remember okay And
del vídeo de ella no me acuerdo vale Y
she took it and left a comment on my
cogió ella y me puso un comentario en mi
video and she said something like she said
vídeo y me puso algo así como me puso
something like wow you copied
algo así como vaya me has copiado todo
the whole video I don't remember something like that they weren't
el vídeo no me acuerdo algo así no eran
the literal words but like with with
las palabras literales pero así con con
cachon deito no go me  you copied
cachon deito no vaya me has copiado todo
the whole video I don't know what how much no and what are you
el vídeo no sé qué cuanto no y ya qué me
telling me dad what are you
estás contando papa qué me estás
telling me that you took the whole forum
contando que le has sacado todo el foro
gossiping and I started Pin Pin Pin I put
cotilleando y empecé Pin Pin Pin le puse
all the screenshots of the whole script of
Todas Las capturas de todo el guión de
her video Pin Pin Pin Okay but people
su vídeo Pin Pin Pin Bueno pero la gente
endorsed her man I mean that video came out
la endosó tío o sea salió ese vídeo ese
so you can see the hypocrisy of
para que tú veas la hipocresía de la de
people with the ideology and this
la gente con la ideología y esto pasó
also happened to me with the redhead j thing and
también conmigo con lo de j pelirrojo y
it's not her fault in the end she's
ella no tiene la culpa al final ella
doing she's looking for a living
está haciendo está buscándose la vida
okay But it's not her
vale Pero ella no tiene la culpa la
fault it's society in general's fault
culpa la tiene la sociedad en general de
Twitter and networks and so on okay what
Twitter y de redes y demás vale lo que
ideology is and how one looks at
es la ideología y cómo se mira con unos
one person with certain eyes and at others with certain eyes okay I
ojos a uno y con otros ojos a otros vale
mean eh H blo that about that about that topic what
o sea eh el H blo eso de la eso del tema
the cat talked about at
ese de lo que lo que habló la gata en
that moment what the cat talked about in the
ese momento lo que habló la gata de en
modern weeks video that I don't
el vídeo de las semanas modernas que no
remember very well what hob
me acuerdo muy bien de lo que era el hob
blo was I had already commented on all that it happens
blo ya lo había comentado todo eso pasa
that H blo is H blo a gossip channel
que H blo es H blo un canal de salseo
how disgusting  I don't know what on top of that Jairo okay And
qué asco no sé qué encima Jairo vale Y
when the cat released the video the video went
cuando sacó la gata el vídeo el vídeo lo
viral I mean everyone Oh the
viralizaron o sea todo el mundo Oh el
video that has exposed it well I don't know what
vídeo que bien lo ha expuesto no sé qué
endorsing the [ __ ] video and with the thing about j
endosando el [__] vídeo y con lo de j
pelirrojo the same thing happened I mean with the
pelirrojo pasó lo mismo o sea con lo de
J pelirrojo thing
J pelirrojo
eh the J pelirrojo issue I released
eh el tema de J pelirrojo lo saqué
this this video this 30,000 to help
este este vídeo este 30.000 por ayudar a
his fan JP the new charlatan
su fan JP el nuevo charlatán eso lo
I released that And from there on
saqué yo Y a partir de ahí pues fueron
others started talking about the subject okay okay But that this
hablando otros del tema vale vale Pero
subject was mine the JP red subject
ese este tema fue mío el tema de JP rojo
was a subject of mine it went viral that it came out
fue un tema mío se hizo viral que salió
well the subject even had a cameo in the
bueno el tema tuvo hasta cameo en el
rewind but he had a cameo in the rewine
rewind pero tuvo cameo en el rewine
because La gata mentioned it I
porque lo mencionó La
mean and when I'm a loser I don't know
gata o sea y cuando soy una pringada no
who I don't know how much everyone talks about the
sé quién no sé cuánto todos hablan del
subject of j pelirrojo and the
tema de j pelirrojo y el cursillo de los
30,000 course they mention the cat when La
30.000 mencionan a la gata cuando La
gata in her own video mentions me
gata en su propio vídeo me menciona a mí
and gives the credits to
y me da los créditos a
me and it's the subject the ideology I don't know
mí y es la el tema la ideología no sé
what is worth it is the ideological subject and  that whole
qué vale es el tema ideológico y todo el
guy thing Let's
tío A
see tell me confine So then man I think if
ver dime confin Así luego tío pienso si
I'm the same as this H the
estoy igual esto H los de los
influencers who for me prostitute
influencers que para mí prostituyen la
Mental Health a eh social issue so
Salud Mental un eh tema social tan
necessary and
necesario e
important to say that you are dedicated to
importante decir que tú te dedicas a la
Mental Health when all you do is
Mental cuando lo único que haces es
copy four phrases that you have seen on
copiar cuatro frases que has visto en el
Pinterest and you are putting them And
Pinterest y te las estás poniendo Y
attributing them to yourself on your Instagram and
atribuyendo a ti en tu Instagram y
saying that you are dedicated to
diciendo que te dedicas a la salud
mental health for me is prostituting
mental para mí es prostituir la Salud
Mental Health taking advantage of it monetizing it
Mental aprovecharte de ella monetizarla
and not only that but trivializing
y no solo eso sino que frivolizar con
something as important as
algo tan importante como es la Salud
Mental Health and disrespecting all
Mental y faltarle al respeto a todos
those psychologists who really do
aquellos psicólogos que realmente sí se
dedicate themselves to Mental Health and not you piece
dedican a la Salud Mental y no tú pedazo
of clown and here let it be alluded to
de payaso y aquí que se de por aludido
Whoever has to give in I
Quien tenga que darse estoy de acuerdo
totally agree with you because in the end
contigo totalmente porque al final la
Mental Health seems to concern us
Salud Mental parece que nos atañe a
all but it concerns us as citizens no
todos pero nos atañe como ciudadanos no
how no how is it that I don't know who
como no como es que no sé a quién se
that issue is referring to I don't know this
está refiriendo ese tema no lo sé esto
is the controversy of the choca that we have already
es la polémica del choca que ya lo hemos
seen in the utbh video
visto en el vídeo de utbh
okay it doesn't have click about the jpelirrojo  there is no
vale no tiene click de lo de jpelirrojo
cli they haven't put up a cl of the J
cli no han puesto cl de lo de J
redhead thing but that's what I want to
pelirrojo pero si eso es lo que quiero
see Hey they told me that
ver Oye que me han dicho que la invitada
this week's guest is inside
de esta semana está metida dentro de
this box but she's alive I'm alive here I
esta caja pero está viva estoy viva aquí
am What's
estoy Qué
up dead or alive I'm complaining that I'm alive Well
muerta o viva quej que estoy viva Bueno
after this week's show I don't
después del programa de esta semana no
know how
lo sé yo qué
scary
miedo
Hey they have
Oye
n't put up a click of the J
no nos han puesto click de lo de J
redhead thing man Look J redhead spoke to me
pelirrojo tío Mira J pelirrojo me habló
privately to make me feel sorry for them and to remove
por privado para dar pena y que retirase
the video about his
el vídeo sobre su
scam [ __ ] dude well yeah yes it's on
estafa [__] macho pues ya si si es en
podimo we can't put it up I think
podimo no lo podemos poner creo
eh yes it's on podimo in theory I think it's
eh si es en podimo en teoría creo que es
paywalled of
de pago
course what a deal no What
claro qué movida no Qué
a deal it is Uh three I'm leaving there was going to be
movidotas es Uh las tres me voy iba a
more stuff but I'm leaving there was going to be
haber más cositas pero me voy iba a
more stuff but I'm leaving guys I'm
haber más cosas pero me voy chicos me
leaving I'm leaving the schedule must be
voy me voy que el horario hay que
respected but what a pain in the
respetarlo pero que te
ass just to get the 8
cagas justo justo para dormir las 8
hours of sleep that tomorrow I have to get up
horas que mañana me tengo que levantar
to record the
para grabar El
news
Noticiero
tomorrow I have to get up to record the
mañana me tengo que levantar para grabar
kids' news okay
el noticiero de los chavales vale
eh
eh
guys I'll leave it here I'll leave it here I
chicos lo dejo por aquí lo dejo por aquí
hope you  I liked the live, the
espero que os haya gustado el directo la
truth is that I think that today's live
verdad que yo creo que que el directo de
has not left anyone indifferent, these are
hoy no ha dejado indiferente a nadie son
things that only happen here, okay.
cosas que solamente pasan aquí vale
Eh So
Eh Así que
nothing, well I don't know what, well I don't know what to
nada pues no sé que pues no sé que
get, 6 hours is enough Javi No no no no
sacar con 6 horas basta Javi No no no no
no for the physical change and for everything I
no para el cambio físico y para todo lo
'm doing it has to be 8
que estoy haciendo tienen que ser 8
hours and the 2 liters of water to comply, you
horas y los 2 litros de agua cumplirlo
have to comply with everything, you have to sleep
hay que cumplirlo todo hay que dormir
well, you have to comply with
bien hay que cumplirlo
everything, guys, what I said okay eh I'll leave it for
todo chicos lo dicho vale eh lo dejo por
[Music]
[Música]
here I had to time a live that I
aquí tenía que minutar un directo que me
had left to time for one thing, man,
quedaba por minutar para una cosa tío
but it's already 3 o'clock, it went too long,
pero ya son las 3 se me ha alargado
man, the
mucho tío se me ha alargado mucho la
night went too long. Of course the interview is true.
noche Claro que la entrevista es verdad
Wow, but interview, no, we have had
Wow pero entreviste no que nos hemos
no
llevado no
family, interview for free.
familia entrevista por la cara
Come on, I mean, but interview for
Vamos o sea pero entrevista por la
free, the Lía sicora
cara lo de Lía sicora
extract, of course, luare, take that part
extracto claro luare cógete esa parte
and get an extract of
Y sácate un extracto de
that, no, and the Alali thing, I think also the
eso no y lo de alali yo creo que también
Ali thing, if we don't have anything
lo de Ali también si es que no tenemos
else, the Lali thing too and you put a
otra cosa lo de Lali también y le pones
title like that  Lali points to Javi
de título algo así como Lali señala jav
Oliveira for his exclusive or something like that, I don't
oliveira por su exclusiva o algo así yo
know Look luare, I'm going to tell you, I'm going to
sé Mira luare te voy a decir te voy a
tell you, look straight at it Lali points to Javi
decir mira a saco Lali señala a Javi
Oliveira for his exclusive and in the
oliveira por su exclusiva y en la
thumbnail you put me against Lali and and it
miniatura me pones a mí contra Lali y y
says all my grandma That's the
pone toda mi abuelita Esa es la
thumbnail, it's that you have to, it's that you have to
miniatura es que hay que es que hay que
take advantage of it, I don't know if I don't know if
aprovecharlo yo no sé si yo no sé si
Andy will put that part in the
Andy meterá ese trozo en el canal
main channel in the interview But well I
principal en la entrevista Pero bueno Me
imagine that I think he'll cut that part
imagino que yo creo que esa parte la
because it doesn't have much to do
cortará porque no tiene mucho que ver
with the subject but well, I don't know. I don't
con el tema pero bueno no lo sé No lo
know what Ali did was spectacular too
sé lo de Ali también fue espectacular
Man, today there's a clan, right?
Hombre está hoy han salido clan no
Because the first one came out about Ali
Porque ha salido el primero de lo de Ali
on Twitter against Ricky and so on, from there
en Twitter contra Ricky y demás de ahí
in the interview he's going to bring out the lias and
de la entrevista va a sacar lo de lias y
corora thing, I don't know what title you can give it
corora no sé qué título le puedes poner
to that Put a debate about Elías and corora
a eso Pon debate sobre Elías y corora
with the little friend
con con el amiguito
of with the little friend of Katy Ángel I
de con el amiguito de de Katy Ángel O
mean you have a title
sea tienes un titulo
no and in the thumbnail it says against
no y en la miniatura pone en contra de
Dallas and you put me the kid and in the
Dallas y me pones a mí al chaval y en
middle, okay, sicora
medio valí sicora
eh I'm giving it to you  more cada eh luar I
eh Te lo estoy dando más cado eh luar Te
'm giving it to you I'm giving it to you more
lo estoy dando te lo estoy dando más
expensive what else has happened
carísimo qué más haido
Javier about the cat about the
Javier lo de la gata lo de la
cat Only put the reaction to
gata Pon solamente la reacción a lo de
Sergio's the other one we did, don't
Sergio la otra que hemos hecho no lo
put it and that's it, there are the three
ponga y ya está ahí están los tres
extracts, no, we haven't seen anything else,
extractos no que no hemos visto más nada
no guys, I had a reaction here to a
no chavales tenía aquí una reacción a un
video of this from the elite but
vídeo de esto de los de la élite pero no
I didn't have time it's
me ha dado tiempo que son las
three o'clock that's for noti
tres eso para noti
no that's for the newscast places for
no eso para noticiero lugares para
tomorrow how
mañana qué
strong how strong Karime but it's that I'm not
fuerte qué fuerte Karime pero es que no
going to mention anything about those people they do
voy a mencionar nada de esa gente aquí
n't exist here Already
no existen Ya
fights Thank you very much thank you very much
luchis Muchas gracias muchas gracias
luchi Gustavo But that's not serious
luchi Gustavo Pero eso no es en serio
man I
hombre
understand guys huge kiss okay
entiendo chicos besote enorme vale
tomorrow we'll see you do you have the video on the
mañana nos veremos tenéis vídeo en el
main channel already uploaded okay go
canal principal ya subido vale irlo a
support the video While the
apoyar el vídeo Mientras que se sube el
other one is being uploaded okay because the interview is going to be
otro vale porque la entrevista se va a
uploaded on the main one
subir en el principal
eh the interview is going to be uploaded on the
eh la entrevista se va a subir en el
main one So while they have it go
principal Así que mientras que la tienen
support the newscast that is already
iros a apoyar el noticiero que ya está
uploaded the news is already uploaded
subido el noti ya está subido
okay brutal
vale brutal
eh brutal go to the main Channel main
eh brutal iros al Canal princi principal
to support the  newscast okay go to the
a apoyar el noticiero vale iros al Canal
main channel to support the newscast and in a
principal a apoyar el noticiero y en un
bit the
rato se sube la
interview will be uploaded a kiss guys rest
entrevista un beso chicos que descanséis
[Music]
[Música]
okay
vale